0021EB95-BC944D0B-8A6D2200-01D14375|kName|kDesc|Hollywood Hills House Ultimate Bundle|This Amazing Bundle Comes With All Four Versions Of The Hollywood Hills House As Well As The Following Items: 1) Hollywood Hills House Daytime Estate (with Home Theatre) 2) Hollywood Hills House Daytime Clubhouse (with Home Theatre) 3) Hollywood Hills House Nighttime Estate (with Home Theatre) 4) Hollywood Hills House Nighttime Clubhouse (with Home Theatre) 5) LOOT™ Active Camera 6) LOOT™ Active Light 7) 140'' LOOT™ EOD TV - Flatscreen 8) Aerial Swimming 9) LOOT™ Firepit 10) LOOT™ Outdoor Oven 11) LOOT™ Velvet Rope 12) LOOT™ Tiki Torch - Single 13) LOOT™ Tiki Torch - Double 14) LOOT™ Tiki Totem 15) Cabin Boy In Trout Trouble – Classic 16) LOOT™ Photo Telescope 17) LOOT™ Grandfather Clock 18) LOOT™ Searchlight 19) LOOT™ Fog Machine Create The Ultimate Party With Your Friends -- At Your Hollywood Hills House From LOOT™. PLEASE READ BEFORE YOU PURCHASE: Due To Contractual And Rights Agreements, Some EOD Channels Are Nation Specific. Crackle Content Is ONLY Available In United States, Canada, United Kingdom, And Australia. RadioIO Is ONLY Available In The United States And Canada. In Addition, Due To Rights Issues, Countries May Not Receive The Same Content Selections Within The Channels. Only One TV Can Be Active At A Time. The LOOT™ EOD Will Work In Any Private Space, UNLESS The Space Comes With A Video Screen You Cannot Turn Off.|Apt_Bundle|© LOOT™|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
00A1BD13-AC5F46D2-B2A9A70A-3E3D0C5B|kName|kDesc|Plum Tree Pavilion Mega Bundle|Available As A Single Purchase, The Plum Tree Pavilion Mega Bundle Includes The Apartment, Clubhouse, And Furniture Bundle For This Space. Now You Can Enjoy Everything This Elaborate Space Has To Offer!|Apt_Bundle|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
04D43019-2B44408E-B8309EBF-1BE778F7|kName|kDesc|Dream Forest Paradise Bundle|Dream Forest Paradise Bundle This Bundle Includes The Following: • Dream Forest Paradise • Dream Forest Paradise Clubhouse Your Dreams Come True With This Breathtaking Deluxe Home Amongst The Trees, A Luxurious Treehouse If You Will. Traverse The Treetop Bridges, Swim In The Lagoon, And Explore Your Lush Surroundings To Obtain Rewards. With A Magnificent View From Every Angle You'll Never Want To Leave The Dream Forest Paradise From Figment. Live The Dream!|Apt_Bundle|Lockwood|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
06A68487-C88540B9-BE2FBF6B-BE61CB05|kName|kDesc|Paradise At Sea Mega Bundle|Available As A Single Purchase, The Paradise At Sea Mega Bundle Includes The Apartment, Clubhouse, And Furniture Bundle For This Space. Now You Can Enjoy Everything This Elaborate Space Has To Offer!|Apt_Bundle|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.60.0.451.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
09DC9CFB-A51C4246-9E2D20C9-FD2C6E7E|kName|kDesc|Planetland Mega Bundle|Discover A Great New Collection Of Furniture Items And Clothing Items With This Amusing Mega Bundle. This One Of A Kind Bundle Includes The Planetland Apartment, 22 Furniture Items And 16 Clothing Items.|Apt_Bundle|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.55.0.155.BETA2|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
0D2A4545-8764403D-9EE4F6EA-45BE57DC|kName|kDesc|Pharaoh's Tomb Mega Bundle|Take A Trip Back In Time To The Era Of The Pharaoh. This Egyptian Themed Mega Bundle Includes Pharaoh's Tomb Apartment, 17 Furniture Items And 35 Clothing Items.|Apt_Bundle|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.55.0.155.BETA2|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
0D7BECF7-56CC4AC5-B04A0BB0-65BA2318|kName|kDesc|Dream Yacht Bundle|Dream Yacht Bundle This Bundle Includes The Following: • The Dream Yacht • The Dream Yacht Clubhouse Have The Lifestyle You Always Dreamed Of With The Dream Yacht From Figment. Three Decks Of Opulent Living, Two Hot Tubs And More Than 30 Collectable Rewards, Plus An Exclusive Commerce Point Only Available Through The Dream Yacht. Live The Dream!|Apt_Bundle|Lockwood|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
0F59D375-EBF34B4C-AFD7865E-D92D895B|kName|kDesc|Snow Globe Mega Bundle|Including Snow Globe Apartment, Snow-man, Snow-woman, Snow-boy, Snow-girl, 2 X Neon Ice Chair, 2 X Neon Ice Sofa, 2 X Neon Ice Table (purple And Green) And Exclusive Clothing Mrs Frost And Mrs Frost Hat And Mr Frost, Mr Frost Shoes And Mr Frost Hat.|Apt_Bundle|JAM Games Ltd|HDK_1.82.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
135D4301-8FFB4CC5-96702535-A5ACE91A|kName|kDesc|Dream Island Resident Pack|This Pack Includes The Following: • Dream Island • Lateral Pulldown Machine • Exercise Bike • Weights Rack • Vision TV And Stand • Guitar And Stand • Hi-Def Satellite Speaker - Small • Hi-Def Satellite Speaker - Large • Hi-Def Center Speaker • Hi-Def Subwoofer • Luxury Leather Sofa • Luxury King-Size Bed • Luxury Dining Table • Luxury Dining Chair • Luxury Floor Lamp Live The Life You Always Dreamed Of With Dream Island From Figment. Your Very Own Secluded Tropical Island Hideaway. Swim In The Ocean, Find The Hidden Cave And Discover The Island's Vibrant Wildlife To Obtain Rewards. Invite Friends To Visit You At The Island's Impressive Condo Or Host A Barbecue On Your Private Pier. Live The Dream!|Apt_Bundle|Lockwood|HDK_1.60.0.450.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
15AF9E1B-204F4866-8662BEBA-87AA6404|kName|kDesc|Ajagara's Peak Ultimate Bundle (for Female)|Ajagara's Peak Ultimate Bundle (for Female) This Pack Includes The Following: • Ajagara's Peak • Ajagara's Peak Dragon Scout Bundle (for Female) • LMO - Ajagara - Tsen The Dragon - Mount • LMO - Ajagara - Khambu The Dragon - Mount • LMO - Ajagara - Zugs The Dragon - Mount • LMO - Ajagara - Tsen The Dragon • LMO - Ajagara - Khambu The Dragon • LMO - Ajagara - Zugs The Dragon • Ajagara's Peak Furniture Bundle Nestled Atop A Steep And Perilous Mountain; Ajagara's Peak Is Only Accessible To A Select Few - Those Known As The Dragon Scouts. A Place For Diligent Training, Scholarly Pursuits And Deep Meditation; The Monastery At Ajagara's Peak Was Founded To Train An Elite Band Of Soldiers Who Keep Watch Over The Kingdom Of Ajagara. With 8 Daily Rewards And The Chance To Catch A Glimpse Of A Tame Dragon, This Truly Is A Unique Personal Space.|Apt_Bundle|Lockwood|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
1867ED5A-4D634821-8090BAD3-C479801C|kName|kDesc|Stately Home Bundle (Gothic)|The Stately Home (Gothic) Is The Perfect Personal Apartment Space For Those People Who Like The Finer Things In Life With A Slightly Darker Twist. With Its Large And Beautiful Grounds And A Direct Link Through To The Masquerade Ball - The Ballroom (Gothic), This Space Is A Must-have. Also Comes With Five Free Rewards. This Bundle Includes: * Stately Home (Gothic) * Stately Home Clubhouse (Gothic)|Apt_Bundle|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.82.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
1895C72E-DE41418D-98FAAE55-E531C3C1|kName|kDesc|Skyscraper Lounge: Ultimate Bundle|In The Sleek New Skyscraper Lounge From NDreams, You Can Wind Down, And Chill Out In Style! This Ultimate Bundle Includes: * Skyscraper Lounge: Apartment * Skyscraper Lounge: Clubhouse * Skyscraper Lounge: Stylish Chair * Skyscraper Lounge: Stylish Stool * Skyscraper Lounge: Stylish Table ※ Upon Purchase, All Items Will Be Added To Their Corresponding Categories.|Apt_Bundle|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.83.0.11.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
196F7FA5-877C4E26-BEB418B8-F2A27DEB|kName|kDesc|Halloween Tour Bus Mega Bundle|Including: Tour Bus, Kitchen - Corner Unit, Hob Unit, Oven Housing, Sink Unit And Standard Unit, Settee - Corner Piece And Straight Piece And Stool.|Apt_Bundle|JAM Games Ltd|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
19BDD570-32124127-8C882B05-6448EEC0|kName|kDesc|Acorn Meadows Park Apartment - Mega Bundle|This Bundle Contains: (1) Acorn Meadows Park Apartment (2) Acorn Meadows Park Apartment - Winter (3) Acorn Meadows Park Apartment - Autumn (4) Acorn Meadows Park Apartment - Rainy Day (5) Acorn Meadows Park Apartment - Dusk|Apt_Bundle|VEEMEE|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
1A16E6C0-4E98429B-9CA2BA4A-C4664A04|kName|kDesc|Country Chic – Tour Bus Basic Bundle|Including: Tour Bus, Kitchen - Corner Unit, Hob Unit, Oven Housing, Sink Unit And Standard Unit, Settee - Corner Piece And Straight Piece.|Apt_Bundle|JAM Games Ltd|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
1C633580-4A2C49BC-8D224F39-C0B4C627|kName|kDesc|Diamond Beach Mansion Bundle 1|Exclusive Diamond Beach Mansion Bundle! Contains: - Espresso Coffee Machine - Abstract Sculpture Number One - Classical Frame – One - Popcorn Machine - Samurai Statue – Bronze - Iced Skull Necklace - Goddess Bra - Goddess Weapon - White Leather Jacket With Red Hoodie - Flaming Chef's Hat - Big Money - Suit Jacket - Super Smart – Glasses.|Apt_Bundle|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
1F355D59-92674BA9-8B69A0D7-0FA22DDE|kName|kDesc|Acorn Meadows Park Apartment - Atmospheres Bundle|This Bundle Contains: (1) Acorn Meadows Park Apartment - Winter (2) Acorn Meadows Park Apartment - Autumn (3) Acorn Meadows Park Apartment - Rainy Day (4) Acorn Meadows Park Apartment - Dusk|Apt_Bundle|VEEMEE|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
1FDD44FB-46FD44AC-BE6AA29C-A29E3434|kName|kDesc|Stately Home Ultimate Bundle|The Ultimate Bundle For Those Who Like The Finer Things In Life. The Ultimate Bundle Come With All Variants Of The Stately Home Apartment And Clubhouse, Including Free Rewards. This Bundle Includes: * Stately Home * Stately Home Clubhouse * Stately Home (Gothic) * Stately Home Clubhouse (Gothic)|Apt_Bundle|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.82.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
23161444-07544277-A0578362-8BE94C45|kName|kDesc|Juggernaut Personal Space Super Value Bundle|Dive Into PlayStation®Home Real Estate With This Juggernaut Super Value Bundle Offering The Full Cutteridge Estate Experience Plus The Bramblenook Farm Personal Space At An Enormous Discount! Bundle Includes: • Cutteridge Estate • Cutteridge Ghost Stories Ultimate Bundle • Bramblenook Farm|Apt_Bundle|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
238202C7-68CB4840-A369383F-BA9CE5A7|kName|kDesc|Lake House Mega Bundle|Add A Sense Of Warmth And Comfort To Any Home With The Lake House Mega Bundle. This Bundle Has The Lake House Apartment And 19 Furniture Items.|Apt_Bundle|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.55.0.155.BETA2|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
24B1E427-73B2480F-9245C1AE-1A86DEC7|kName|kDesc|Rock Reveller – Tour Bus Basic Bundle|Including: Tour Bus, Kitchen - Corner Unit, Hob Unit, Oven Housing, Sink Unit And Standard Unit, Settee - Corner Piece And Straight Piece.|Apt_Bundle|JAM Games Ltd|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
25551A02-8113417F-BCB2426A-AC56435F|kName|kDesc|Moon Forest Mega Bundle|Available As A Single Purchase, The Moon Forest Mega Bundle Includes The Apartment, Clubhouse, And Furniture Bundle For This Space. Now You Can Enjoy Everything This Elaborate Space Has To Offer!|Apt_Bundle|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.60.0.450.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
260428F8-6B2746F9-88DBA1E7-99B7E1A0|kName|kDesc|Anime Apartment Mega Bundle|The Anime Mega Bundle Is A Must Buy For Any Anime Fan. With The Anime Apartment, 30 Furniture Items And 20 Clothing Items, Its A Great Way To Get To Know This Peculiar Art Style.|Apt_Bundle|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.55.0.155.BETA2|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
26383520-1FED4D9C-B1286B05-D403938D|kName|kDesc|PlayStation Legends Apartment Bundle| This Bundle Contains The Following Items: • Ratchet And Clank: Home Sweet Home • Loco Island • Uncharted Fortune Hunter's Apartment • MotorStorm Pacific Rift Camp • MotorStorm Monument Valley Camp • Visari Throne Room • LittleBigPlanet™ Pod Penthouse|Apt_Bundle|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
28C1DE47-B8414DA9-B313E132-E329E0C6|kName|kDesc|PlayStation Home Mansion Bundle|This Bundle Contains The Following Items: • Playstation Home Mansion - Ground Floor • Playstation Home Mansion - First Floor • Playstation Home Mansion - Infinity Pool • Playstation Home Mansion - Garage|Apt_Bundle|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
31528C8A-8A3545B3-99127061-F5B55D2A|kName|kDesc|Sodium Silicon Lounge Party Pack (for Female)|Sodium Silicon Lounge Party Pack (for Female) This Pack Includes The Following: • Sodium Silicon Lounge Personal Space • Toxic Green Contact Lenses (for Female) • Special Edition Animated Blooming Flower T-shirt - Red With Pink (for Female) • Animated Disco Rig With Moving Lights • Laser Light Show • Animated Flashing Disco Floor • The Sun Make A Statement And Become The Ultimate Party Host With The Sodium Silicon Lounge! Show Off Your Moves On The Interactive Dancefloor, Relax In The Hidden Underground Chill-out Area Or Send A Gift To A Friend With The Integrated Lockwood Gift Machine. Plus, Create The Ultimate Dance Party Setting And Look The Part Too With These Awesome Lockwood Furniture And Clothing Items.|Apt_Bundle|Sodium - Lockwood|HDK_1.50.0.238.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
31941E40-CBD84763-8CAEB0F1-5F3124FD|kName|kDesc|Hollywood Hills House Nighttime Clubhouse Bundle|Entertain Like An Industry Mogul In This Ultimate Clubhouse, Set In The Hollywood Hills Above The LA Skyline! Invite Your Friends Into Your Home Theater For A Social Viewing Experience With Videos, Trailers And Exclusive Content From Sony Pictures! Features Include: • Built-in Entertainment On Demand Theater System; • A Swimming Feature For The Infinity Pool! THIS Is Where The Party Is For You And Your Club. Purchase Of This Clubhouse Comes Bundled With The LOOT™ Active Camera And Active Light, So You Can Film Your Parties And Upload Them To YouTube At No Extra Cost! PLEASE READ: Due To Contractual And Rights Agreements, All Content May Not Be Available In All Countries. Content Availability Is Dependent On The Geolocation Of The Device. CRACKLE Content Is Only Available In US, CA, UK, And AU. RADIOIO Is Only Available In US And CA. Only One LOOT™ TV Or LOOT™ Radio Can Be Active At A Time.|Apt_Bundle|© LOOT™|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
3687CF16-1C1A44E3-BD7822F6-11404DB5|kName|kDesc|Serenity Lake Male Ultimate Bundle|Serenity Lake Male Ultimate Bundle This Bundle Includes The Following: • Serenity Lake (Apartment) •Serenity Male Oriental Jacket - Grey •Serenity Male Linen Trousers - Grey •Serenity Male Oriental Shoes - Grey •Serenity Lake Oriental Dance Pack For Male The Mystical Serenity Lake Is Said To Come With 8 Charming Rewards.|Apt_Bundle|Lockwood|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
36B6A58C-7670478D-8C67A8EA-D5642510|kName|kDesc|Masquerade Ball - Gothic Bundle|This Complete Bundle Includes Everything You Could Ever Need To Host A Gothic Themed Masquerade Ball; Clothing, Furniture And The Ballroom Itself. This Bundle Includes: * Masquerade Ball - The Ballroom (Gothic) * Masquerade Ball - The Ballroom Club House (Gothic) * Masquerade Ball - Ornate Chair (Gothic) * Masquerade Ball - Chaise Longue (Gothic) * Masquerade Ball - Ornate Rug (Gothic) * Masquerade Ball - Ornate Table (Gothic) ※ Upon Purchase, All Items Will Be Added To Their Corresponding Categories.|Apt_Bundle|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
36FE757F-A06C40B2-AED30A5F-942AE5A0|kName|kDesc|921 Acacia Drive Ultimate Bundle|921 Acacia Drive Ultimate Bundle This Pack Includes The Following: • 921 Acacia Drive • Ultimate Slice Furniture Set • Ultimate Luxury Furniture Pack • Cucumber Modernist Bedroom Set - Romance • Cucumber Country Kitchen Set - Gingerbread • Drey Noir Furniture Ultimate Bundle • Retro Modern Kitchen Pack • Cucumber Modern Lines Bathroom Set - Woodland • Cucumber Contemporary Bedroom Set - Rustic • Cucumber Country Kitchen Set - Liquorice • Cucumber Modern Lines Bathroom Set - Dazzle • Bayonne Furniture Pack - Brights • Cucumber Contemporary Bedroom Set - Vivid Live The Suburban Dream At 921 Acacia Drive! With A Range Of Spacious Rooms And 91 Bundled Furniture Items, Along With 8 Daily Reward Items That Give You The Essential Furniture Items, You Can Decorate Your Home To Suit Your Style.|Apt_Bundle|Lockwood|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
37B1DDD1-4BDE41D5-B95F34F9-03FBC8FC|kName|kDesc|Dream Universe Ultimate Bundle|Dream Universe Ultimate Bundle This Bundle Includes The Following: • The Dream Yacht • The Dream Yacht Clubhouse • Dream Island • Dream Island Clubhouse • The Dream Yacht: Arctic Voyage Clubhouse • Dream Hideaway Clubhouse • Dream Forest Paradise • Dream Forest Paradise Clubhouse|Apt_Bundle|Lockwood|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
3818FF01-70244271-B48E3959-81DB69AC|kName|kDesc|Personal Casino Bundle|Now You Can Take On The Roll Of Being A Casino Boss. This Bundle Include All Of Your Favorite Casino Games, Poker, War, Blackjack, Big Six, Craps, Roulette, Video Poker, Video Blackjack, And Slots. Not Only Will You Get All Of These Fantastic Games But You'll Also Get Your Own Casino Personal Space. It'll Be Like You're Running A Mini Version Of Paradise Springs For You And Your Friends.|Apt_Bundle|Digital Leisure|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
3A37DC89-246046A3-906512A0-6356A05E|kName|kDesc|Lock-a-doodle Pre-order Pack|Lock-a-doodle Pre-order Pack This Pack Includes The Following: • Lock-a-doodle Studio • Lock-a-doodle Studio (Clubhouse) • Lock-a-doodle • Lock-a-doodle Display Easel • Lock-a-doodle Giant Furniture Pack • Lock-a-doodle Doodle Pack - Jewel Of The Skies • Lock-a-doodle Doodle Pack - Sodium • Lock-a-doodle Doodle Pack - Spring Time • Lock-a-doodle Doodle Pack - Figment (pre-order) • Lock-a-doodle Doodle Pack - Stitchkins (pre-order) • Lock-a-doodle Doodle Pack - Iron Fusion (pre-order) • Lock-a-doodle Doodle Pack - Medusa (pre-order) • Lockwood Token Pack - 480 This Special Pack Allows You To Pre-order Forthcoming Doodle Packs At A Discounted Rate. Lock-a-doodle Is A Fun Social Drawing Game. Create Doodles For Your Friends To Guess, Accept Random Challenges From Other Players Or Unlock Doodle Mode And Doodle To Your Heart's Content. The More Lock-a-doodle Doodle Packs You Own, The More Stickers, Colours And Shapes At Your Disposal For Creating Incredible Works Of Art! Each Doodle Pack Contains New Colours, Stickers, Words And Shapes. Please Note: Doodle Packs Can Only Be Used In Conjunction With The Lock-a-doodle Mini-game Or Active Object, Or Lock-a-doodle Gift Edition.|Apt_Bundle|Lockwood|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
3C2F50EB-A04B4EBC-9CA9ED22-77EF03E2|kName|kDesc|The Secret Party Garden: Apartment And Clubhouse Bundle|Host Your Own Secret Party Within The Secluded Walls Of This Luscious Garden. This Bundle Includes: The Secret Party Garden: Apartment The Secret Party Garden: Clubhouse ※ Upon Purchase, All Items Will Be Added To Their Corresponding Categories.|Apt_Bundle|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
3C961576-C22543C3-9A13DA22-8303B0E7|kName|kDesc|Personal Space GZ Burger And Table, Character Panel Set|GZ Burger, A Hamburger Shop Neighboring A Large Lake, Is All Yours. The Interior Layout Of The Tables, Chairs, Etc. Is Up To Your Imagination. Create Your Own Unique Restaurant And Invite Your Friends! Includes Chair, Character Panels. This Set Includes The Following Items: - GZ Burger (Personal Space) - Restaurant Table (Round) (Table) - Restaurant Table (Round + Parasol) (Table) - Restaurant Table (Square) (Table) - Restaurant Chair (Chair) - Character Panel (Sitting Female Student) (Ornament) - Character Panel (Sitting Male Student) (Ornament) - Character Panel (GZ Burger Women Staff) (Ornament) - Character Panel (GZ Burger Men Staff) (Ornament) - Character Panel (Fashionable Women) (Ornament) - Character Panel (Fashionable Men) (Ornament) - Character Panel (Sitting Office Worker Men) (Ornament) - Character Panel (Sitting Office Worker Women) (Ornament) * Upon Purchase, Each Item Will Be Added To The Applicable Category.|Apt_Bundle|Granzella Inc.|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
3F1FCE31-4DA04AE9-9A2533B4-CF7AC1A6|kName|kDesc|Doctor Who - Wave One Bundle|This Bundle Comes With The Doctor Who TARDIS Clubhouse And Doctor Who TARDIS Private Space, And The Following Items: Doctor Who - The Eleventh Doctor Costume Doctor Who - The Eleventh Doctor's Sonic Screwdriver Doctor Who - Silent Costume Doctor Who - River Song Costume Doctor Who - River Song's PDA Doctor Who - Silurian Costume With Mask Doctor Who - Cybermat Companion BBC Active Camera BBC Active Light BBC Logo © BBC 1996. Doctor Who Logo © BBC 2013. Dalek Image © BBC/ Terry Nation 1963. Cyberman Image © BBC/Kit Pedler/Gerry Davis 1966. K-9 Image © BBC/Bob Baker/Dave Martin 1977. Licensed By BBC Worldwide Limited.|Apt_Bundle|BBC Worldwide Limited|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
4A931915-2CBB4B08-911A1C21-5EF2FDF4|kName|kDesc|Abbey Hill Cottage Ultimate Bundle|Abbey Hill Cottage Ultimate Bundle This Pack Includes The Following: • Abbey Hill Cottage(Apartment) •LMO - Side Saddled Trotter - Black With Brown Saddle • LMO - Side Saddled Trotter - Palomino With Brown Saddle • LMO - Side Saddled Trotter - Chestnut With Brown Saddle • LMO - Silk Fan - Cherry Blossom • LMO - Silk Fan - Azure • LMO - Parasol - Blush Begonia • LMO - Parasol - Moonlight Muse • Molly The English Setter • Rosie The English Setter • Libby The Lamb The Timeless Abbey Hill Cottage Is A Beautiful Period Home Containing 12 Unique Rewards.|Apt_Bundle|Lockwood|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
4AA14A24-359E4496-ABAFA660-6285A701|kName|kDesc|Pink Paradise - Tour Bus Mega Bundle|Including: Tour Bus, Vehicle Seat, Kitchen - Corner Unit, Hob Unit, Oven Housing, Sink Unit And Standard Unit, Settee - Corner Piece And Straight Piece, Stool, Acoustic And Electric Guitar Wall Hangings, Gold And Platinum Disc Wall Hanging, Exclusive Tour Bus Top, Trousers, Boots And Hat For Her And Cardigan Top, Trousers, Boots And Hat For Him!|Apt_Bundle|JAM Games Ltd|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
4B0F60A2-93FD4E5A-84525FF9-D18838BF|kName|kDesc|Halloween Ultimate Collection|This Bundle Contains The Following Items: • Gothic Manor Apartment • Dark Furniture Bundle: Skeleton Chair, Skull Posts, Spider Web Table • Black Cat Companion • Frankenstein Outfit (male) • Werewolf Outfit (male) • Skeleton Man Suit (male) • Flaming Skeletal Warrior Outfit (male) • Frozen Skeletal Warrior Outfit (male) • Spiked Demon Outfit (male) • Headless Horseman Bundle: Hat, Top, Legs, Hands (male) • Mechanical Abomination Suit (male) • Orc Warrior Outfit (male And Female) • Witch Outfit (female) • Witch Bundle: Hat, Top, Legs, Gloves (female) • Ghost Outfit (female) • Dark Sorceress Bundle: Head, Torso, Legs, Feet, Hands (female) Each Object Will Be Added To Its Relevant Wardrobe Or Furniture Category. Note: As This Bundle Contains Items Both Old And New, Some Items May Not Appear In Your Inventory Until Your Next Login.|Apt_Bundle|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
505D561E-727D484B-A9856A86-23081E97|kName|kDesc|Apartment Variety Bundle|This Bundle Contains The Following Items: • Lakeside Log Cabin • The Lost Dam Hideout • Tycoon Penthouse • Original Home Square Apartment • Japanese Apartment • Playground Apartment|Apt_Bundle|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
538DE3A2-A71D4AE5-87508803-91081A9E|kName|kDesc|Gothic Cathedral And Gothic Furniture Bundle|This Ancient Abandoned Cathedral On The Cliff Is A Sanctuary And A Place You Call Home.  Includes The Pew, Table, Chair, Bed, Throne, Rug And Statue.|Apt_Bundle|Konami Digital Entertainment, Inc.|HDK_1.65.0.139.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
5483A97B-3B7344D0-AD002C0A-9923D8C8|kName|kDesc|Apartment Bundle|Including: - The Painted Bare Studio	 - Country Chic - Tour Bus - 'Country Chic - Tour Bus' – Clubhouse	 - Rock Reveller – Tour Bus - Pink Paradise - Tour Bus - The Jam Jar Apartment - The Jam Jar Clubhouse	 - RaceOn Garage	|Apt_Bundle|JAM Games Ltd|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
57675757-1C6B41F9-890B88F9-5320787D|kName|kDesc|The Hangar Skatepark - Bundle|This Skatepark Is Housed Within A Huge Repurposed Aircraft Hangar! It's Open, It's Spacious, It's Everything An Avid Skater Ever Dreamed Of! With Ramps, Bowls, Grind Rails And Half Pipes, Its Time To Get On Your Deck And Skate Around This Large Skatepark! With Large Open Spaces There's Also Great Chance For Customisation With The Modular Skatepark Furniture Items Present Within The Bundle Along With Two Brand New Decks! This Bundle Contains: (1) The Hangar Skatepark (2) Arrows Deck - Kickflip (3) Plug N' Go Deck - Impossible (4) Modular Skatepark - Single Ramp (5) Modular Skatepark - Single Ramp And Rail (6) Modular Skatepark - Floor Piece (7) Modular Skatepark - Block Piece (8) Modular Skatepark - Quarter Bowl (9) Modular Skatepark - Rounded Corner Ramp (10) Modular Skatepark - Hard Corner Ramp (11) Modular Skatepark - Grind Rail|Apt_Bundle|VEEMEE|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
5A2DC5E8-F9244A69-B95E37BB-757F8A1B|kName|kDesc|Carla's Coffee Shop - Premium Bundle|Carlas Coffee Shop Apartment From NDreams Bundled With Some Of The Most Recent NDreams Items. Includes: * Carla's Coffee Shop Apartment * The Shimmer Sphere * Chameleo Glow - Chair * Chameleo Glow - Sofa * Chameleo Glow - Carpet * Chameleo Glow - Picture Frame * Chameleo Glow - Table * Chameleo Glow - Bookshelf * Pancho – Companion * Squid From Space - Companion ※ Upon Purchase, All Items Will Be Added To Their Corresponding Categories.|Apt_Bundle|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
5D4E141F-C5E542B1-9E03818D-E74A0EDF|kName|kDesc|Skyscraper Lounge: Apartment And Clubhouse Bundle|In The Sleek New Skyscraper Lounge From NDreams, You Can Wind Down, And Chill Out In Style! This Bundle Includes: * Skyscraper Lounge: Apartment * Skyscraper Lounge: Clubhouse ※ Upon Purchase, All Items Will Be Added To Their Corresponding Categories.|Apt_Bundle|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.83.0.11.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
5F0571D8-6CE34D26-8B015C61-DD4343F8|kName|kDesc|The Pearl Diver Mega Bundle|Available As A Single Purchase, The Pearl Diver Mega Bundle Includes The Apartment, Clubhouse, And Furniture Bundle For This Space. Now You Can Enjoy Everything This Elaborate Space Has To Offer!|Apt_Bundle|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
604EF031-F3F2467C-AFC7E5D2-77FFFA4A|kName|kDesc|The Best Of NDreams 2014 Bundle - Apartments|This Incredible Value For Money Bundle Contains The Following Items: * Luxury Lighthouse Apartment * Luxury Train Apartment * Inferno Apartment * Rooftop Terrace - Apartment * Joe's Boxing Gym Apartment * Cassie's Dance Studio Apartment * Skyscraper Lounge: Apartment * Stately Home * Stately Home (Gothic) * The Complex 2: Clubhouse * The Nightclub: Apartment * Masquerade Ball - The Ballroom * Masquerade Ball - The Ballroom (Gothic) * Savage Manor * Musicality Apartment * Ansadafone Apartment * Blueprint: Home (Apartment) ※Upon Purchase, All Items Will Be Added To Their Corresponding Categories.|Apt_Bundle|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
6745B2D5-545143CA-B6D38D63-21124690|kName|kDesc|Stately Home Bundle|The Stately Home Is The Perfect Personal Space For Those People Who Like The Finer Things In Life. With Its Large And Beautiful Grounds And A Direct Link Through To The Masquerade Ball - The Ballroom, This Space Is A Must-have. Also Comes With Five Free Rewards. This Bundle Includes: * Stately Home * Stately Home Clubhouse|Apt_Bundle|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.82.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
67EED0EA-45E6475C-BE8B03D2-8A1A11AD|kName|kDesc|Personal Space Bundle|It's The Personal Space Bundle! Includes The Summer House, Lakeside Log Cabin, And Japanese Apartment. **IMPORTANT NOTICE** This Personal Space Bundle May Contain The Items You Have Already Purchased. Only The Item Which Is Not Yet Purchased Is Added To [Navigator > Personal Links > Personal Spaces] And Same Purchased Item Will Not Appear In The Personal Space Twice. Purchased Special Bundles Are Not Refundable, Transferable Or Exchangeable, And Cannot Be Redeemed For Cash Or Credit.|Apt_Bundle|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.52.0.2.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
67F8157C-C43F4B62-9CD6C857-70974573|kName|kDesc|Boxing Gym And Dance Studio Bundle|This Great Value For Money Bundle Offers Two Great Apartments For A Fantastic Price. This Bundle Includes: * Joe's Boxing Gym Apartment * Cassie's Dance Studio Apartment ※ Upon Purchase, All Items Will Be Added To The Relevant Category.|Apt_Bundle|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
6E654226-D61F45C1-AF7FAF4B-78317686|kName|kDesc|Paradise Health Club: Ultimate Bundle|Relax And Re-energise In The Exotic And Picturesque Grounds Of Paradise Health Club! This Bundle Includes: * Paradise Health Club: Apartment * Paradise Health Club: Clubhouse * Paradise Health Club: LMO Swimming - Breaststroke * Paradise Health Club: LMO Swimming - Front Crawl * Paradise Health Club: LMO Swimming - Backstroke * Paradise Health Club: LMO Hand Fan * Paradise Health Club: Dance Pack 1 (Male) * Paradise Health Club: Dance Pack 1 (Female) * Paradise Health Club: Dance Pack 2 (Male) * Paradise Health Club: Dance Pack 2 (Female) * Paradise Health Club: Kimono (Male) (White) * Paradise Health Club: Kimono (Female) (White) * Paradise Health Club: Kimono (Male) (Black) * Paradise Health Club: Kimono (Female) (Black) * Paradise Health Club: Body Towel (Male) (White) * Paradise Health Club: Body Towel (Female) (White) * Paradise Health Club: Body Towel (Male) (Black) * Paradise Health Club: Body Towel (Female) (Black) * Paradise Health Club: Head Towel (Male) (White) * Paradise Health Club: Head Towel (Female) (White) * Paradise Health Club: Head Towel (Male) (Black) * Paradise Health Club: Head Towel (Female) (Black) * Paradise Health Club: Cooling Cucumber (Male) * Paradise Health Club: Cooling Cucumber (Female) * Paradise Health Club: Chair * Paradise Health Club: Table * Paradise Health Club: Yoga Poses 1 (Male) * Paradise Health Club: Yoga Poses 1 (Female) * Paradise Health Club: Yoga Poses 2 (Male) * Paradise Health Club: Yoga Poses 2 (Female) * Paradise Health Club: Yoga Poses 3 (Male) * Paradise Health Club: Yoga Poses 3 (Female) * Paradise Health Club: Yoga Poses 4 (Male) * Paradise Health Club: Yoga Poses 4 (Female) ※ Upon Purchase, All Items Will Be Added To Their Corresponding Categories.|Apt_Bundle|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
6F736865-FF81444C-8A46170E-FD1F2CFA|kName|kDesc|Greenhouse Bundle|This Bundle Contains: - The Greenhouse - Wicker Sofa - Wicker Chair - Wicker Table - Teapot Fountain - Big Bench - Grey Bench - Stone Fountain - Zen Pug - Zen Frog - Stone Hippo|Apt_Bundle|KOVOK LTD|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
74497366-1ABE4E24-BACCD255-71D544F2|kName|kDesc|Hollywood Hills House Daytime Clubhouse Bundle|Entertain And Meet With Your Club In This Ultra-exclusive Clubhouse, Set In The Hollywood Hills Above The LA Skyline! Features Include: • Built-in Entertainment On Demand Theater System; • A Swimming Feature For The Infinity Pool! THIS Is The Ultra-exclusive Retreat For The Discerning Club Owner. Purchase Of This Clubhouse Comes Bundled With The LOOT™ Active Camera And Active Light, So You Can Film Your Parties And Upload Them To YouTube! PLEASE READ: Due To Contractual And Rights Agreements, All Content May Not Be Available In All Countries. Content Availability Is Dependent On The Geolocation Of The Device. CRACKLE Content Is Only Available In US, CA, UK, And AU. RADIOIO Is Only Available In US And CA. Only One LOOT™ TV Or LOOT™ Radio Can Be Active At A Time.|Apt_Bundle|© LOOT™|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
7621206D-3AB44934-891320D5-A8512010|kName|kDesc|Luxury Racing Box Mega Bundle|Spend A Day At The Races With This Luxury Racing Mega Bundle. It Includes The Luxury Racing Box Apartment, 12 Furniture Items And 18 Clothing Items.|Apt_Bundle|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.55.0.155.BETA2|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
76ADE47C-94294D60-802993EA-0AACD092|kName|kDesc|Serenity Lake Female Ultimate Bundle|Serenity Lake Female Ultimate Bundle This Bundle Includes The Following: • Serenity Lake (Apartment) •Serenity Lady's Leggings - Grey •Serenity Lady's Tie-Front Blouse - Grey •Serenity Lady's Pumps - Grey •Serenity Lake Oriental Dance Pack For Female The Mystical Serenity Lake Is Said To Come With 8 Charming Rewards.|Apt_Bundle|Lockwood|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
7859EBE3-A2484378-982724EE-786B189D|kName|kDesc|Pub Mega Bundle|The Ultimate In Pub Entertainment. This Bundle Contains: (1) The London Pub (2) The Irish Pub (3) English Pool (4) American Pool (5) American Pool - Pink Table (6) American Pool - Green Table (7) American Pool - Yellow Table (8) American Pool - Blue Table (9) Skull Pool Table (10) Judge Dredd Pool Table (11) Darts Game (12) Darts Game With Skull Dartboard (13) Darts Game With Chromium Dartboard|Apt_Bundle|VEEMEE|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
7A573571-F2B64070-9769A1EE-6C31989C|kName|kDesc|921 Acacia Drive Interior Decorator Bundle - Executive|921 Acacia Drive Interior Decorator Bundle - Executive This Pack Includes The Following: • 921 Acacia Drive • Drey Noir Furniture Ultimate Bundle • Retro Modern Kitchen Pack • Cucumber Modern Lines Bathroom Set - Woodland • Cucumber Contemporary Bedroom Set - Rustic Live The Suburban Dream At 921 Acacia Drive! With A Range Of Spacious Rooms And 37 Bundled Furniture Items, Along With 8 Daily Reward Items That Give You The Essential Furniture Items, You Can Decorate Your Home To Suit Your Style.|Apt_Bundle|Lockwood|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
7C154EAD-088D4983-B7283D1C-BEDC9A5F|kName|kDesc|Seasons Apartment Bundle|This Bundle Contains The Following Items: • Summer House • Creek Falls • Winter Vacation Villa • Tree House Personal Apartment|Apt_Bundle|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
7CA89854-FC794037-AF467EFB-268B2BFF|kName|kDesc|Personal Space Japanese Teahouse & Tea Ceremony Tool Set|A Remote Mountain Location, With Abundant Vegetation And Water. A Small Teahouse Stands Past The Gate, Beyond The Garden Stepping Stones. The Confined Teahouse Built According To The Principles Of Wabi And Sabi Allows One To Draw Near To Visitors. Spend A Brief Moment In Silence Includes A 3-piece Set With A Japanese Teacup, A Japanese Teakettle And A Dango. This Set Includes The Following Items: - Japanese Teacup (Decoration) - Japanese Teakettle (Decoration) - Dango (Decoration) - Japanese Teahouse (Personal Space) * Upon Purchase, Each Item Will Be Added To The Applicable Category.|Apt_Bundle|Granzella Inc.|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
7D06A3F5-9B31425A-9576DF9C-1C9A8A98|kName|kDesc|Paradise Health Club: Apartment And Clubhouse Bundle|Relax And Re-energise In The Exotic And Picturesque Grounds Of Paradise Health Club! This Bundle Includes: * Paradise Health Club: Apartment * Paradise Health Club: Clubhouse ※ Upon Purchase, All Items Will Be Added To Their Corresponding Categories.|Apt_Bundle|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
7ED28064-E2514485-9CAD9B39-F219E3A0|kName|kDesc|Personal Space Japanese Teahouse & Tea Ceremony Tool Set|A Remote Mountain Location, With Abundant Vegetation And Water. A Small Teahouse Stands Past The Gate, Beyond The Garden Stepping Stones. The Confined Teahouse Built According To The Principles Of Wabi And Sabi Allows One To Draw Near To Visitors. Spend A Brief Moment In Silence Includes A 3-piece Set With A Japanese Teacup, A Japanese Teakettle And A Dango. This Set Includes The Following Items: - Japanese Teacup (Decoration) - Japanese Teakettle (Decoration) - Dango (Decoration) - Japanese Teahouse (Personal Space) * Upon Purchase, Each Item Will Be Added To The Applicable Category.|Apt_Bundle|Granzella Inc.|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
7FE08BFB-7C084887-A884825B-9DC18E46|kName|kDesc|Rock Reveller – Tour Bus Mega Bundle|Including: Tour Bus, Vehicle Seat, Kitchen - Corner Unit, Hob Unit, Oven Housing, Sink Unit And Standard Unit, Settee - Corner Piece And Straight Piece, Stool, Acoustic And Electric Guitar Wall Hangings, Gold And Platinum Disc Wall Hanging, Exclusive Tour Bus Top, Trousers, Boots And Hat For Her And Cardigan Top, Trousers, Boots And Hat For Him!|Apt_Bundle|JAM Games Ltd|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
849662D6-07244AEB-9AB0FAA9-5FC966C4|kName|kDesc|The Secret Party Garden: Ultimate Bundle|Host Your Own Secret Party Within The Secluded Walls Of This Luscious Garden. Look And Feel Part Of The Party With This Ultimate Bundle From NDreams! This Bundle Includes: The Secret Party Garden: Apartment The Secret Party Garden: Clubhouse The Secret Party Garden: Tattooed Torso (Male) The Secret Party Garden: Boho Bikini (Female) The Secret Party Garden: Boho Denim Shorts (Female) The Secret Party Garden: Boho Hat (Female) The Secret Party Garden: Boho Floral Crown (Female) The Secret Party Garden: Boho Rings And Flowers (Female) The Secret Party Garden: Boho Foot Jewels (Female) The Secret Party Garden: Decorative Cushion (Patterned) The Secret Party Garden: Decorative Cushion (Mosaic) The Secret Party Garden: Decorative Cushion (Fuschia) The Secret Party Garden: Decorative Cushion (Natural) The Secret Party Garden: Beanbag (Patterned) The Secret Party Garden: Beanbag (Furry) The Secret Party Garden: Hammock (Striped) The Secret Party Garden: Hammock (Natural) * The Secret Party Garden: Dance Pack 1 (Male) * The Secret Party Garden: Dance Pack 1 (Female) * The Secret Party Garden: Dance Pack 2 (Male) * The Secret Party Garden: Dance Pack 2 (Female) ※ Upon Purchase, All Items Will Be Added To Their Corresponding Categories. *These Are Portable Items.|Apt_Bundle|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
864D4455-84F642E1-A9FEDE73-0A9A0DD6|kName|kDesc|Personal Space Tea Room-The Spirit Of Harmony+tea Ceremony Set|Far Away From Cities And Towns, In A Mountain Surrounded By Green And Blue, Pass Through The Gate And Walk Through A Path Laid With Stepping‐stones And You Will Find A Small Tea Room. Designed To Be Small According To Japanese Aesthetics Wabi-sabi, The Distance Between You And Your Guests Shrinks In This Room. Let's Enjoy A Moment Of Tranquility. Bundled With Three Tea Ceremony Tools Including Tea Bowl. Tea Kettle And Dango. This Set Includes The Following Items. ・Tea Bowl (Ornament) ・Tea Kettle (Ornament) ・Dango (Ornament) ・Tea Room - The Spirit Of Harmony (Personal Space) *When Purchased, Each Item Is Added To Its Respective Category.|Apt_Bundle|Granzella Inc.|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
865D333E-C7CB4C7E-8428B49D-50106E8A|kName|kDesc|Sodium Silicon Lounge Ultimate Pack (for Male)|Sodium Silicon Lounge Ultimate Pack (for Male) This Pack Includes The Following: • Sodium Silicon Lounge Personal Space • Toxic Green Contact Lenses (for Male) • Special Edition Animated Growing Vines T-shirt - Black With Green (for Male) • Animated Disco Rig With Moving Lights • Laser Light Show • Animated Flashing Disco Floor • The Sun • Sodium Large Neon Cube - Purple • Sodium Large Neon Cube - Orange • Sodium Small Neon Cube - Blue • Sodium Small Neon Cube - Green • Sodium Persian Rug – Red • Sodium Neon Puzzle Piece • Sodium Hexagon Tile Throw The Party Of The Year With This Amazing Bundle Containing The Silicon Lounge Personal Space And An Incredible Set Of Furniture And Clothing Items! Show Off Your Moves On The Interactive Dancefloor, Relax In The Hidden Underground Chill-out Area Or Send A Gift To A Friend With The Integrated Lockwood Gift Machine. Plus, You Can Party With Style With This Amazing Range Of Silicon Lounge Furniture Items, Lockwood Party Accessories And Clothing Items.|Apt_Bundle|Sodium - Lockwood|HDK_1.50.0.238.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
868F870C-DE5F4685-91461DB6-E01DF069|kName|kDesc|Santorini, Greece Mega Bundle|Deck Your Apartment In Some Of Greeces Finest Looking Furniture. This Bundle Comes With The Santorini Apartment And 33 Furniture Items.|Apt_Bundle|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.55.0.155.BETA2|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
872F0ED8-7E934107-B6EAABB1-D5767D1E|kName|kDesc|50s Diner - Bundle|A Bundle Of The 50's Diner Items. This Bundle Contains: (1) VEEMEE's 50's Diner (2) 50s Diner - Jukebox (3) 50s Diner - Mini Table Jukebox (4) 50s Diner - Coffee Machine (5) 50s Diner - Cash Register (6) 50s Diner - Napkin Dispenser (7) 50s Diner - Milkshake (8) 50s Diner - Cola Bottle (9) 50s Diner - Cola Cup (10) 50s Diner - Burger & Fries Basket (11) 50s Diner - Hot Dog & Fries Basket (12) 50s Diner - Ice Cream Sundae (13) 50s Diner - Banana Split Ice Cream (14) 50s Diner - Diner Stool (15) 50s Diner - Stainless Diner Table (Square) (16) 50s Diner - Stainless Diner Table (Rectangle) (17) 50s Diner - Stainless Diner Chair (18) 50s Diner - Retro Vending Machine (19) 50s Diner - Retro Phone Booth|Apt_Bundle|VEEMEE|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
88CC6EE3-2D174BFF-9BA03900-FFABD894|kName|kDesc|Castle Greywold: Ultimate Bundle|Prepare For Winter With The Ultimate Castle Greywold Bundle From NDreams, Complete With All Items From The Great And Noble Houses, Langfrey, Alliker, Daederon, And Karus. This Bundle Contains: Castle Greywold: Apartment Castle Greywold: Clubhouse House Langfrey Throne House Langfrey Wingback House Langfrey Chair House Langfrey Dining Table House Langfrey Hanging Banner House Langfrey Standing Banner House Alliker Throne House Alliker Wingback House Alliker Chair House Alliker Dining Table House Alliker Hanging Banner House Alliker Standing Banner House Daederon Throne House Daederon Wingback House Daederon Chair House Daederon Dining Table House Daederon Hanging Banner House Daederon Standing Banner House Karus Throne House Karus Wingback House Karus Chair House Karus Dining Table House Karus Hanging Banner House Karus Standing Banner Castle Greywold: LMO Tankard Castle Greywold: LMO Chicken Leg Castle Greywold: LMO Noble Sword Castle Greywold: LMO Bow And Arrow Castle Greywold: LMO Dragon Hatchling * Castle Greywold: Dance Pack 1 (Male) * Castle Greywold: Dance Pack 1 (Female) * Castle Greywold: Dance Pack 2 (Male) * Castle Greywold: Dance Pack 2 (Female) Castle Greywold: House Langfrey Outfit (Male) Castle Greywold: House Alliker Outfit (Male) Castle Greywold: House Daederon Outfit (Male) Castle Greywold: House Karus Outfit (Male) Castle Greywold: House Langfrey Outfit (Female) Castle Greywold: House Alliker Outfit (Female) Castle Greywold: House Daederon Outfit (Female) Castle Greywold: House Karus Outfit (Female) ※ Upon Purchase, All Items Will Be Added To Their Corresponding Categories. LMO (Locomotion) Is A Portable Item. *These Are Portable Items.|Apt_Bundle|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
8BBB708C-1CDB4EF8-AF43A3E7-7E69AB76|kName|kDesc|Twingate Castle Mega Bundle|Including: Twingate Castle Apartment, 2 X Leather And Lace Shorts, 2 X Leather And Lace Top, 2 X Leather Gloves, 2 X Leather And Lace Boots And 2 X Hair (for Her). 2 X Leather Trousers, 2 X Leather Top, 2 X Leather Boots And 2 X Hair (for Him).|Apt_Bundle|JAM Games Ltd|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
8D32F82D-C0014423-8A7EA1A9-AC01CB69|kName|kDesc|Pub Apartments Bundle|The Perfect Places To Relax With Your Friends. This Bundle Contains: (1) The London Pub (2) The Irish Pub|Apt_Bundle|VEEMEE|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
8E7E4680-4BE4466C-B09F705A-BEF29908|kName|kDesc|Personal Space GZ Burger And Table, Character Panel Set|GZ Burger, A Hamburger Shop Neighboring A Large Lake, Is All Yours.The Interior Layout Of The Tables, Chairs, Etc. Is Up To Your Imagination.Create Your Own Unique Restaurant And Invite Your Friends! Includes Chair, Character Panels. This Set Includes The Following Items: - GZ Burger (Personal Space) - Restaurant Table (Round) (Table) - Restaurant Table (Round + Parasol) (Table) - Restaurant Table (Square) (Table) - Restaurant Chair (Chair) - Character Panel (Sitting Female Student) (Decoration) - Character Panel (Sitting Male Student) (Decoration) - Character Panel (GZ Burger Women Staff) (Decoration) - Character Panel (GZ Burger Men Staff) (Decoration) - Character Panel (Fashionable Women) (Decoration) - Character Panel (Fashionable Men) (Decoration) - Character Panel (Sitting Office Worker Men) (Decoration) - Character Panel (Sitting Office Worker Women) (Decoration) * Upon Purchase, Each Item Will Be Added To The Applicable Category.|Apt_Bundle|Granzella Inc.|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
924DBF93-CD754AB5-AF07C845-B6FA2997|kName|kDesc|Mega Bundle|This Bundle Contains: -Moonlight Room -Skull Bottle -Wooden Round Table -Wooden Bookshelf -Old Trunk -Marble Table -Bird Ornament -Raven Cage -Writer's Desk -Dining Table -Victorian Chair -Victorian Sofa -Silver Candlestick -Silver Large Candlestick -Striped Folding Screen -Black Marble Fireplace -Silver Bathtub -Horror Smile -Dining Chair -Raven Cross|Apt_Bundle|KOVOK LTD|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
97A824E1-A24D445C-BBE61756-DF7CE5A6|kName|kDesc|Studio Stage Set Open House Bundle|This Insane Open House Bundle Comes With The Private Space And The Following Items: 1. Amaterasu Passion Fruit Highball 2. Amaterasu Tall Potted Plant 3. Blackbeard Ornament Stand 4. Cube Couch - Black 5. Flat - Brick 6. Flower Vase 7. Ghostbusters™ Antique Desk 8. Glass Coffee Table 9. House Plant 1 10. House Plant 6 11. LOOTville Heights A 12. LOOTville Towers B 13. LOOT™ Air Ceiling 14. LOOT™ Air Overhead Compartment 15. LOOT™ Air Wall 16. LOOT™ Air Wing Base 17. LOOT™ Air Wing Body 18. LOOT™ Air Wing Tip 19. LOOT™ Longboard - Sky Blue 20. LOOT™ Mountain Bike - White 21. LOOT™ Night - Cityscape A 22. LOOT™ Night - Cityscape B 23. LOOT™ Night - Cityscape C 24. LOOT™ Night - Desk 25. LOOT™ Night – Guest Chair 26. LOOT™ Night – Host Chair 27. MIB™ - Boris Bike 28. MIB™ - Flying Bike (Full-size) 29. MIB™ - HQ Chair 30. MIB™ - Jetpack (Full-size) 31. Popcorn Bag 32. Portable Blue Screen From Loot™ 33. Potted Grass Plant 34. Potted Tropical Plant Green 35. Reception Chair 36. Reception Desk - Black 37. Red Directors Chair 38. Talents Director's Chair From Loot™ 39. Tube Couch - Black 40. Water Cooler 41. Window Flat - Brick 42. Window Flat – Mint 43. Witchblade Standee - Sara Pezzini 44. Cabin Boy In Trout Trouble – Classic 45. LOOT™ Searchlight 46. LOOT™ Photo Telescope 47. LOOT™ Grandfather Clock 48. LOOT™ Active Light 49. LOOT™ Active Camera|Apt_Bundle|©LOOT™|HDK_1.66.0.144.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
98878CCF-6E0D4707-82EBDC52-A6075845|kName|kDesc|Sodium Silicon Lounge Décor Pack|Sodium Silicon Lounge Décor Pack This Pack Includes The Following: • Sodium Silicon Lounge Personal Space • Sodium Large Neon Cube - Purple • Sodium Large Neon Cube - Orange • Sodium Small Neon Cube - Blue • Sodium Small Neon Cube - Green • Sodium Persian Rug – Red • Sodium Neon Puzzle Piece • Sodium Hexagon Tile Create The Ultimate Party Setting With The Silicon Lounge Personal Space And Furniture Collection. Show Off Your Moves On The Interactive Dancefloor, Relax In The Hidden Underground Chill-out Area Or Send A Gift To A Friend With The Integrated Lockwood Gift Machine. Plus, You Can Decorate The Space Just How You Like With This Amazing Range Of Silicon Lounge Furniture Items.|Apt_Bundle|Sodium - Lockwood|HDK_1.52.0.2.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
9ADDA5E2-C3B64D0C-B313C418-6F10F4B0|kName|kDesc|Dream Island Bundle|Dream Island Bundle This Bundle Includes The Following: • Dream Island • Dream Island Clubhouse Live The Life You Always Dreamed Of With Dream Island From Figment. Your Very Own Secluded Tropical Island Hideaway. Swim In The Ocean, Find The Hidden Cave And Discover The Island's Vibrant Wildlife To Obtain Rewards. Invite Friends To Visit You At The Island's Impressive Condo Or Host A Barbecue On Your Private Pier. Live The Dream!|Apt_Bundle|Lockwood|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
9C183E1C-414B405F-AD1287D4-7FB0F695|kName|kDesc|Dream Island Holiday Pack|This Pack Includes The Following: • Dream Island • Luxury Leather Sofa • Luxury King-Size Bed • Luxury Dining Table • Luxury Dining Chair • Luxury Floor Lamp • Vision TV And Stand • Guitar And Stand • Hi-Def Satellite Speaker - Small • Hi-Def Satellite Speaker - Large • Hi-Def Center Speaker • Hi-Def Subwoofer Live The Life You Always Dreamed Of With Dream Island From Figment. Your Very Own Secluded Tropical Island Hideaway. Swim In The Ocean, Find The Hidden Cave And Discover The Island's Vibrant Wildlife To Obtain Rewards. Invite Friends To Visit You At The Island's Impressive Condo Or Host A Barbecue On Your Private Pier. Live The Dream!|Apt_Bundle|Lockwood|HDK_1.60.0.450.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
9E8C9F66-F1734E7B-A053C501-E967AD4B|kName|kDesc|LKWD Venue Pack|LKWD Venue The Perfect Location For All Your Social Events, The Venue Includes: • Interaction Points Allowing You And Your Friends To Utilise Unique Animations • In Depth Customization Options Including Optional Features Like The Stage And The Runway • A Voting Minigame • Your Own Personal LKWD Store • An Integrated Lockwood Gift Machine • Default Customisation Options Be The Ultimate Host With The LKWD Venue. This Pack Includes The Following: • The Venue • LKWD Venue Customisation Pack - Hive|Apt_Bundle|Lockwood|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
A15D9FDD-718D49B5-A5F5203F-810FC398|kName|kDesc|Diamond Beach Mansion Bundle 2|Diamond Beach Mansion Bundle 2 Exclusive Diamond Beach Mansion Bundle! Contains: - Classic 40s Jukebox - Billionaire Sofa - Blue - Abstract Sculpture Number Two - Classical Frame - Two - Decorative Knight's Helmet – White - Goddess Bottoms -Sports Jacket In Cream With Blue Panels - Super Smart Glasses - Big Money - Suit Pants - Super Smart - Sweater Vest - Gentleman's Top Hat - Bed Time Night Cap|Apt_Bundle|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
A28BAE57-556649C7-81907C03-9F68E9E7|kName|kDesc|Disney Apartment Bundle|This Bundle Contains The Following Items: • Tron Apartment • Andy's Room|Apt_Bundle|Disney|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
A4D3DBF3-E1904B35-B1AA650D-48CFC5C5|kName|kDesc|Carla's Coffee Shop - Classic Bundle|Carlas Coffee Shop Apartment From NDreams Bundled With 19 Classic NDreams Products. This Bundle Includes: * Carlas Coffee Shop Apartment * Directors Chair (Seat) *Cinema Sign (Picture Frame) * Red Carpet (Flooring) * Giant Clapper Board (Ornament) * Paparazzi (Appliance) * Velvet Railing (Ornament) * Chris The Bodyguard (Ornament) * Party Seat (Purple) * Smoke Machine (Purple) * Balloons (Multicoloured) * Celebratory Present * Land Shark Pizzas * Fizzy Drink * Party Cake (Green) * Landshark Coffee: Chair * Landshark Coffee: Table * Landshark Coffee: Coffee Machine * Landshark Coffee: Coffee Grinder * Landshark Coffee: Sign ※ Upon Purchase, All Items Will Be Added To Their Corresponding Categories.|Apt_Bundle|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
A5D11975-BC764445-8E454854-26FA22A6|Name|Desc|Santorini Apartment And Yacht Value Pack|This Value Pack Includes Both The Santorini Greece Apartment And The Yacht Offered At A Discount! Act Now As This Deal Will Only Be Available For One Month.|Apt_Bundle|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.3.2.27.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
A7AE071F-EC5C4C5A-83B1A087-7201FF6E|kName|kDesc|PlayStation®Home Starter Set (Men)|Let's Start PlayStation®Home! This Starter Set Includes; *Green Military Jacket(Clothing) *Tartan Corduroy Jeans(Clothing) *Summer House(Estate) *Summer House Sofa(Furniture) <NOTE> In Order To Play With This PlayStation®Home Content, It Is Necessary To First Download And Install PlayStation®Home Or Dowload The Most Recent Online Update. This Program Or Data To Be Applied To Existing Program Is Only Compatible With Asia Version (official Product) Which Is Distributed By SCEI. Compatibility With Program Or Data From Other Region Is Not Guaranteed. Purchase Or Use Of This Item Is Subject To The PlayStation®Network Terms Of Service And User Agreement.|Apt_Bundle|Sony Computer Entertainment Asia|HDK_1.3.6.22.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
A7D6CDF3-A9EC4C90-B0E821B7-C2973F9B|kName|kDesc|Hollywood Hills House Daytime Estate Bundle|Live Like A Celebrity With A Mansion In The Hollywood Hills, Set Above The LA Skyline. Invite Your Friends Into Your Home Theatre For A Social Viewing Experience With Videos, Trailers And Exclusive Content From Sony Pictures! Features Include: • Built-in Entertainment On Demand Theatre System; • A Swimming Feature For The Infinity Pool! THIS Is The Estate To Own If You Want To Relax In The Lap Of Luxury With Your Friends. Purchase Of This Estate Comes Bundled With The LOOT™ Active Camera And Active Light, So You Can Film Your Parties And Upload Them To YouTube At No Extra Cost! PLEASE READ: Due To Contractual And Rights Agreements, All Content May Not Be Available In All Countries. Content Availability Is Dependent On The Geolocation Of The Device. CRACKLE Content Is Only Available In US, CA, UK, And AU. RADIOIO Is Only Available In US And CA. Only One LOOT™ TV Or LOOT™ Radio Can Be Active At A Time.|Apt_Bundle|© LOOT™|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
A82249B8-81804DED-A419F287-3A7DF237|kName|kDesc|St Patricks Day Value Pub Bundle|Irish Pub St Patricks Day Value Bundle Celebrate St. Patrick's Day In Style With This Massive Bundle Of Themed Items. As If That Wasn't Enough, We've Thrown In A Special St. Patrick's Themed Version Of The Pub, Complete With Darts Game, So You Can Enjoy Good Times And Great Craic With Your Friends. This Bundle Includes: ・The Irish Pub With Darts Game ・Giant Shamrock - Female ・Giant Shamrock - Male ・Pot Of Gold ・Massive Bow Tie - Female ・Massive Bow Tie - Male ・Born Lucky Waistcoat - Female ・Born Lucky Waistcoat - Male ・Green Top Hat - Female ・Green Top Hat - Male ・Leprechaun Beard - Female ・Leprechaun Beard - Male ・Leprechaun Trousers And Shoes - Female ・Leprechaun Trousers And Shoes - Male ・Leprechaun Jacket - Female ・Leprechaun Jacket - Male ・Leprechaun Hat - Female ・Leprechaun Hat - Male ・Leprechaun Shillelagh - Female ・Leprechaun Shillelagh - Male ・Leprechaun Companion|Apt_Bundle|VEEMEE|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
AAD09FD5-65E64CBD-99FB700A-A9D29D58|kName|kDesc|Dream Island Daytripper Pack|This Pack Includes The Following: • Dream Island • Luxury Leather Sofa • Luxury King-Size Bed • Luxury Dining Table • Luxury Dining Chair • Luxury Floor Lamp Live The Life You Always Dreamed Of With Dream Island From Figment. Your Very Own Secluded Tropical Island Hideaway. Swim In The Ocean, Find The Hidden Cave And Discover The Island's Vibrant Wildlife To Obtain Rewards. Invite Friends To Visit You At The Island's Impressive Condo Or Host A Barbecue On Your Private Pier. Live The Dream!|Apt_Bundle|Lockwood|HDK_1.60.0.450.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
B52E59F1-29DF4096-B4633DBE-2AD4DA56|kName|kDesc|921 Acacia Drive Interior Decorator Bundle - Classic|921 Acacia Drive Interior Decorator Bundle - Classic This Pack Includes The Following: • 921 Acacia Drive • Ultimate Slice Furniture Set • Ultimate Luxury Furniture Pack • Cucumber Modernist Bedroom Set - Romance • Cucumber Country Kitchen Set - Gingerbread Live The Suburban Dream At 921 Acacia Drive! With A Range Of Spacious Rooms And 32 Bundled Furniture Items, Along With 8 Daily Reward Items That Give You The Essential Furniture Items, You Can Decorate Your Home To Suit Your Style.|Apt_Bundle|Lockwood|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
B608C3F0-21F8407D-B5EC1C24-E61FCBD2|kName|kDesc|Santorini, Greece Yacht Mega Bundle|Experience The Joy Of Owning A Yacht, Or At Least Pretending To Own One. This Bundle Comes With Your Own Yacht, 7 Furniture Items And 32 Clothing Items.|Apt_Bundle|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.55.0.155.BETA2|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
B9811D84-E4FA479D-8E76113B-D04303E6|kName|kDesc|Diamond Beach Mansion First Floor|Enter The Most Luxurious Personal Space In PlayStation®Home. The Diamond Beach Mansion Is Packed With Special Features Befitting The Rich And Famous - From A Gifting Machine That Lets You Give Your Friends Exclusive Virtual Items (and Built-in Rewards For The Owner) To Fully-functional Appliances And Fun Interactives Like The Tropical Fish Tank Game And User-controlled Weather And Day/night Cycles. This Lush Island Paradise Even Includes A White Lion Pet That Guards Your Estate While You And Your Friends Party On ('til The Break Of Dawn). Collect All Four Levels Of The Diamond Beach Mansion To Unlock A Secret Area!|Apt_Bundle|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.60.0.450.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
BC2891BD-931B41A1-BC161023-BF287CBA|kName|kDesc|Men In Black™ Headquarters Private Space And Clubhouse Bundle|This Bundle Comes With The Men In Black™ Headquarters Clubhouse And Men In Black™ Private Space! Hang Out With Frank The Pug In The MIB™ Offices, Shop In The Armory And Relax In The Break Room! This Bundle Comes With 11 Exclusive MIB™ Furniture Items. So Suit Up And Get Ready For The Explosive Return Of Agents Kay And Jay In Men In Black™ III And The Epic New Video Game Men In Black: Alien Crisis™!|Apt_Bundle|MEN IN BLACK TM & © 2012 Columbia Pictures Industries, Inc. All Rights Reserved.|HDK_1.66.0.144.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
BDCC3146-529B4581-923A4E94-9E44550B|kName|kDesc|Pink Paradise – Tour Bus Basic Bundle|Including: Tour Bus, Kitchen - Corner Unit, Hob Unit, Oven Housing, Sink Unit And Standard Unit, Settee - Corner Piece And Straight Piece.|Apt_Bundle|JAM Games Ltd|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
BF5AEDA6-39604C16-BEA0E778-64994475|kName|kDesc|Hillside Mega Bundle|Available As A Single Purchase, The Hillside Mega Bundle Includes The Apartment, Clubhouse, And Furniture Bundle For This Space. Now You Can Enjoy Everything This Elaborate Space Has To Offer!|Apt_Bundle|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.60.0.450.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
C00621E5-313C4CD0-9B2227E2-0664A027|kName|kDesc|Luxury Train Mega Bundle|The Ultimate Bundle For Those Who Want The Most From The Luxury Train Apartment. This Bundle Includes: * Luxury Train Apartment * Interactive Bar (Black And White) * Corner Sofa (White) * Straight Sofa (White) * Low Chair (White) * Low Table (White) * Large Counter Top (White) * Small Counter Top (White) * Bed (White) * Corner Sofa (Black) * Straight Sofa (Black) * Low Chair (Black) * Low Table (Black) * Large Counter Top (Black) * Small Counter Top (Black) * Bed (Black) * Corner Sofa (Red) * Straight Sofa (Red) * Low Chair (Red) * Low Table (Red) * Large Counter Top (Red) * Small Counter Top (Red) * Bed (Red) ※ Upon Purchase, All Items Will Be Added To Their Corresponding Categories.|Apt_Bundle|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.82.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
C188EF95-7CD54729-B2985583-26CB3D0B|kName|kDesc|Ratchet And Clank Ultimate Bundle|This Bundle Contains The Following Ratchet And Clank Items For Playstation®Home: • Ratchet And Clank: Home Sweet Home™ Personal Space • Ratchet Hat (male) • Ratchet's Vest (male) • Ratchet Pants (male) • Ratchet Boots (male) • Captain Slag's Gloves (male) • Dr. Nefarious' Helmet (male) • Ratchet Hat (female) • Ratchet's Vest (female) • Ratchet Pants (female) • Ratchet Boots (female) • Captain Slag's Gloves (female) • Dr. Nefarious' Helmet (female) • Chimp-o-Matic • Groovitron Glove • RYNO V • Spiral Of Death • Ratchet Figure • Clank Figure • Talwyn Figure • Skid Figure • Zephyr Figure • Merc Green Figure • Cronk Figure • Big Al Figure • Drek Figure • Mutant ProtoPet Figure • Thugs4Less Leader Figure • Dr. Nefarious Figure • Lawrence Figure • Courtney Figure • Klunk Figure • Gleeman Figure • Shellshock Figure • Eviscerator Figure • Percival Tachyon's Throne Each Object Will Be Added To Its Relevant Wardrobe Or Furniture Category.|Apt_Bundle|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
C311F2FD-DB7249AA-8D152A3C-62EE039D|kName|kDesc|Sodium Silicon Lounge Ultimate Pack (for Female)|Sodium Silicon Lounge Ultimate Pack (for Female) This Pack Includes The Following: • Sodium Silicon Lounge Personal Space • Toxic Green Contact Lenses (for Female) • Special Edition Animated Blooming Flower T-shirt - Red With Pink (for Female) • Animated Disco Rig With Moving Lights • Laser Light Show • Animated Flashing Disco Floor • The Sun • Sodium Large Neon Cube - Purple • Sodium Large Neon Cube - Orange • Sodium Small Neon Cube - Blue • Sodium Small Neon Cube - Green • Sodium Persian Rug – Red • Sodium Neon Puzzle Piece • Sodium Hexagon Tile Throw The Party Of The Year With This Amazing Bundle Containing The Silicon Lounge Personal Space And An Incredible Set Of Furniture And Clothing Items! Show Off Your Moves On The Interactive Dancefloor, Relax In The Hidden Underground Chill-out Area Or Send A Gift To A Friend With The Integrated Lockwood Gift Machine. Plus, You Can Party With Style With This Amazing Range Of Silicon Lounge Furniture Items, Lockwood Party Accessories And Clothing Items.|Apt_Bundle|Sodium - Lockwood|HDK_1.50.0.238.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
C3A046E3-E3634145-B7BA835C-DD649C7E|kName|kDesc|The Ultimate Men In Black™ Collection|This Ultimate Men In Black™ Collection Comes With The Following List Of Items To Help You Protect The Earth From The Scum Of The Universe: 1. Men In Black™ Headquarters (Private Space) 2. Men In Black™ Headquarters - Clubhouse 3. MIB™ - Frank The Pug (companion) 4. MIB™ - Worm Guy (Companion) 5. MIB™ - Male Costumes: Agent, Worm Guy, Nakkadan, Nakkadan Elite, Alien Brain, Adorian Elite, Adorian Medium An Adorian Small. 6. MIB™ - Female Costumes: Agent, Worm Guy, Adorian Small. 7. MIB™ - HQ Chair 8. MIB™ - Boris Bike 9. MIB™ - Monocycle 10. MIB™ - Neurolizer (Male/Female Hands) 11. MIB™ - Agent Pistol (Male/Female Hands And Ornament) 12. MIB™ - Deatomizer (Male/Female Hands And Ornament) 13. MIB™ - Noisy Cricket (Male/Female Hands And Ornament) 14. MIB™ - Tri-barrel Plasma Gun (Male/Female Hands And Ornament) 15. MIB™ - Demoleculizer (Male/Female Hands And Ornament) 16. MIB™ - Adorian Crossbow (Male/Female Hands And Ornament) 17. MIB™ - Nakkadan Taser Gun (Male/Female Hands And Ornament) 18. MIB™ - Nakkadan Disintegrator Ray (Male/Female Hands And Ornament) 19. MIB™ - Adorian Sonar Gun (Male/Female Hands And Ornament) 20. MIB™ - Adorian Plasma Rifle (Male/Female Hands And Ornament) 21. MIB™ - Adorian Energy Blaster (Male/Female Hands And Ornament) 22. MIB™ - The Great Attractors Glover (Male/Female Hands) 23. MIB™ - Flying Car Bundle 24. MIB™ - Car Bundle 25. MIB™ - Nakkadan Elite (Ornament) 26. MIB™ - Nakkadan (Ornament) 27. MIB™ - Jetpack (Full-size) 28. MIB™ - Spaceship (Ornament) 29. MIB™ - Flying Platform (Full-size) 30. MIB™ - Flying Bike (Full-size)|Apt_Bundle|MEN IN BLACK TM & © 2012 Columbia Pictures Industries, Inc. All Rights Reserved.|HDK_1.66.0.144.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
CB44C216-B4754E65-97D2F663-C51B7126|kName|kDesc|Island Bungalow Mega Bundle|Available As A Single Purchase, The Island Bungalow Mega Bundle Includes The Apartment, Clubhouse, And Furniture Bundle For This Space. Now You Can Enjoy Everything This Elaborate Space Has To Offer!|Apt_Bundle|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.60.0.450.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
CB89BF8C-AAD84EC3-A12BE5B3-7324CD42|Name|Desc|Summer House / Log Cabin Value Pack|Purchase The Very Popular Summer House And Log Cabin Personal Spaces At A Discount For A Limited Time! This Value Pack Will Only Be Available Through The End Of The Month!|Apt_Bundle|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.3.2.27.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
D561F3A9-DB5F48EE-8BF0D417-9767380A|kName|kDesc|Sodium Silicon Lounge Party Pack (for Male)|Sodium Silicon Lounge Party Pack (for Male) This Pack Includes The Following: • Sodium Silicon Lounge Personal Space • Toxic Green Contact Lenses (for Male) • Special Edition Animated Growing Vines T-shirt - Black With Green (for Male) • Animated Disco Rig With Moving Lights • Laser Light Show • Animated Flashing Disco Floor • The Sun Make A Statement And Become The Ultimate Party Host With The Sodium Silicon Lounge! Show Off Your Moves On The Interactive Dancefloor, Relax In The Hidden Underground Chill-out Area Or Send A Gift To A Friend With The Integrated Lockwood Gift Machine. Plus, Create The Ultimate Dance Party Setting And Look The Part Too With These Awesome Lockwood Furniture And Clothing Items.|Apt_Bundle|Sodium - Lockwood|HDK_1.50.0.238.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
D6F5543E-17FD42D7-840D5F06-61FAEDA3|kName|kDesc|Doctor Who TARDIS - Private Space And Clubhouse Bundle|This Bundle Comes With The Doctor Who TARDIS Clubhouse And Doctor Who TARDIS Private Space, Including The BBC Active Camera And Active Light Items. TARDIS™ Stands For Time And Relative Dimension In Space. The TARDIS™ Looks Like A 1950s Wooden Police Phone Box On The Outside, But Its Far Bigger On The Inside. Amaze Your Friends When They Discover The Wonder Of Time Lord Technology. Doctor Who Logo © 2013 And TM BBC. Licensed By BBC WW Ltd.|Apt_Bundle|BBC Worldwide Limited|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
D8288EA4-0AFD4EF4-BAF03845-21AE1B37|kName|kDesc|Lock-a-doodle Clubhouse Pack|Lock-a-doodle Clubhouse Pack This Pack Includes The Following: • Lock-a-doodle Studio • Lock-a-doodle Studio (Clubhouse) • Lock-a-doodle • Lock-a-doodle Display Easel Lock-a-doodle Is A Fun Social Drawing Game. Create Doodles For Your Friends To Guess, Accept Random Challenges From Other Players Or Unlock Doodle Mode And Doodle To Your Heart's Content. The More Lock-a-doodle Doodle Packs You Own, The More Stickers, Colours And Shapes At Your Disposal For Creating Incredible Works Of Art! Includes Your First Doodle Pack For FREE!|Apt_Bundle|Lockwood|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
DB7A1E3D-BA73452E-A1FC291C-FAFABDD3|kName|kDesc|Castle Greywold: Apartment And Clubhouse Bundle|This Bundle Includes: Castle Greywold: Apartment Castle Greywold: Clubhouse ※ Upon Purchase, All Items Will Be Added To Their Corresponding Categories.|Apt_Bundle|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
DBB1D495-2C594A0E-BBF96ECD-E7D616B6|kName|kDesc|LOOT™'s Space Apartment (Plugged-in) Open House Bundle|This Insane Open House Bundle Comes With The Private Space And The Following Items: 1. LOOT™ Photo Telescope 2. LOOT™ Searchlight 3. LOOT™ Fog Machine 4. LOOT™ Grandfather Clock 5. LOOT™ Active Camera 6. LOOT™ Active Light 7. Alien Invasion Lava Lamp 8. Amaterasu Barstool 9. Amaterasu Côte D'Azur Cocktail 10. Amaterasu Potted Plant 11. Amaterasu Strawberry Coupe 12. Amaterasu Tall Potted Plant 13. Computer 14. Earth 15. Ghostbusters™ Books 16. Ghostbusters™ Slimer Figurine 17. Glass Coffee Table 18. LOOT™ Snowboard – Lemon 19. Lava Lamp 20. MIB™ - Adorian Particle Blaster (Ornament) 21. MIB™ - Adorian Plasma Rifle (Ornament) 22. MIB™ - HQ Chair 23. MIB™ - Noisy Cricket (Ornament) 24. Mini-Fridge 25. Office Chair 26. Office Phone 27. Orange Retro Speaker Left 28. Orange Retro Speaker Right 29. Space Cubes – Black 30. Space Tables – Orange 31. Space Tables – Red 32. Stage 2 Books 33. Stage 2 Coffee Table 34. Water Cooler|Apt_Bundle|© LOOT™|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
E4ADBB64-96B8496B-9BB3C402-C2B466ED|kName|kDesc|Cutteridge Estate – Clubhouse Bundle|Unlock The Mysteries Of Cutteridge Estate. This Elegant Victorian Estate Is Rumored To Be The Final Resting Place Of Many Dark And Depraved Souls. Do You Dare To Venture Into These Forsaken Halls In Search Of The Secrets Which Lie Within? Bundle Includes: Cutteridge Estate, Cutteridge Estate – Clubhouse, Mysterious Lantern (Inventory Item).|Apt_Bundle|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.65.0.139.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
E637721C-F77342AA-B3D07A7E-5A6799E3|kName|kDesc|Hollywood Hills House Nighttime Estate Bundle|Gaze Upon Glistening Los Angeles As Hollywood Hills Royalty, In Your Private Mansion Above The LA Skyline! Features Include: • Built-in Entertainment On Demand Theatre System; • A Swimming Feature For The Infinity Pool! THIS Is The Spot To Entertain Your Closest Friends And Clients. Purchase Of This Estate Comes Bundled With The LOOT™ Active Camera And Active Light, So You Can Film Your Parties And Upload Them To YouTube! PLEASE READ: Due To Contractual And Rights Agreements, All Content May Not Be Available In All Countries. Content Availability Is Dependent On The Geolocation Of The Device. CRACKLE Content Is Only Available In US, CA, UK, And AU. RADIOIO Is Only Available In US And CA. Only One LOOT™ TV Or LOOT™ Radio Can Be Active At A Time.|Apt_Bundle|© LOOT™|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
EA5EF982-AC174923-B990C460-AA18D0F5|kName|kDesc|Seven Winds Bundle: Caliph|Reign Over Your Own Celestial Paradise With The Palace Of The Seven Winds! Bundle Includes 2 Items At A Savings Of Over 25%! • Palace Of The Seven Winds Personal Space • Palace Of The Seven Winds Clubhouse.|Apt_Bundle|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.65.0.139.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
EB6D29F1-44234956-A91D6386-88CE43BA|kName|kDesc|VEEMEE Apartment Bundle|Four Great Apartments From VEEMEE. This Bundle Contains: (1) 50s Diner - Bundle (2) Acorn Meadows Park Apartment (3) St Patricks Day Value Pub Bundle (4) The London Pub|Apt_Bundle|VEEMEE|HDK_1.82.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
EC2EB33F-76CC4057-8A3D8422-E213FB26|kName|kDesc|Country Chic - Tour Bus Mega Bundle|Including: Tour Bus, Vehicle Seat, Kitchen - Corner Unit, Hob Unit, Oven Housing, Sink Unit And Standard Unit, Settee - Corner Piece And Straight Piece, Stool, Acoustic And Electric Guitar Wall Hangings, Gold And Platinum Disc Wall Hanging, Exclusive Tour Bus Top, Trousers, Boots And Hat For Her And Cardigan Top, Trousers, Boots And Hat For Him!|Apt_Bundle|JAM Games Ltd|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
F173BA13-4B674D64-948E720A-F3FFF5E9|kName|kDesc|The Prairie Ultimate Pack|The Prairie Ultimate Pack This Pack Includes The Following: • The Prairie Saloon (Clubhouse) • The Prairie Ranch (Apartment) • LMO - Saddled Mustang - Black • LMO - Saddled Mustang - Dapple Grey • LMO - Saddled Mustang - Steel Grey • LMO - Saddled Pinto Pony - Skewbald • LMO - Saddled Mustang - Palomino • LMO - Saddled Pretty Pony - Pink • LMO - Saddled Mustang - Grey • LMO - Mustang - Dapple Grey • LMO - Mustang - Grey The Prairie Saloon And The Prairie Ranch Both Contain The Horse Care Game Which Has 7 In-game Rewards. Each Space Also Contains 4 Unique Rewards, Including One Available To Guests!|Apt_Bundle|Lockwood|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
F4499F15-C8C24901-8DC892CC-CA19DD42|kName|kDesc|SeaClyff Night Bundle|You Save Big By Getting The Night Versions Of Both The Retreat And The Clubhouse For One Price. * SeaClyff Night Retreat * SeaClyff Night Clubhouse * Vintage Jazz Radio|Apt_Bundle|Game Mechanics|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
F58044D5-3C2C41F2-BC6F0B3A-839564F1|kName|kDesc|The Nightclub: Ultimate Bundle|The Perfect Bundle For Those Who Want To Party In The Ultimate Nightlife Spot - The Nightclub. This Bundle Includes: * The Nightclub: Apartment * The Nightclub: Clubhouse * The Nightclub: Confetti Cannon * The Nightclub: Laser Display * The Nightclub: Bubble Machine * BoxBeats: Nightclub Edition * BoxBeats Minis: Nightclub Edition * The Nightclub: Lounge Seat * GST- The Nightclub: Flow Dance Pack (Male) * GST- The Nightclub: Flow Dance Pack (Female) * GST- The Nightclub: Booty Shake Dance Pack (Male) * GST- The Nightclub: Booty Shake Dance Pack (Female) Please Note, In Order To Access This Clubhouse You Will Need To Have Purchased The Clubhouse Slot From Either The Estates Store Or The Clubs Menu (available In Options). ※Active Items Provide More Functionality Than Normal Items. You May Only Place Limited Numbers Of The Active Items In Your Apartment Or Clubhouse At Any Time. ※ Upon Purchase, All Items Will Be Added To Their Corresponding Categories.|Apt_Bundle|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
F5A54001-363C419D-84A4BFDD-659B02FE|kName|kDesc|SeaClyff Day And Night Bundle|You Save Big By Getting The Day And Night Versions Of Both The Retreat And The Clubhouse For One Price. * SeaClyff Retreat * SeaClyff Clubhouse * Pulp Music Radio * SeaClyff Night Retreat * SeaClyff Night Clubhouse * Vintage Jazz Radio|Apt_Bundle|Game Mechanics|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
F5B1BE1A-7CC94482-AE949A2A-5DFEB4AD|kName|kDesc|921 Acacia Drive Interior Decorator Bundle - Vivid|921 Acacia Drive Interior Decorator Bundle - Vivid This Pack Includes The Following: • 921 Acacia Drive • Cucumber Country Kitchen Set - Liquorice • Cucumber Modern Lines Bathroom Set - Dazzle • Bayonne Furniture Pack - Brights • Cucumber Contemporary Bedroom Set - Vivid Live The Suburban Dream At 921 Acacia Drive! With A Range Of Spacious Rooms And 22 Bundled Furniture Items, Along With 8 Daily Reward Items That Give You The Essential Furniture Items, You Can Decorate Your Home To Suit Your Style.|Apt_Bundle|Lockwood|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
F5D90D22-16B94743-A42D6C5C-261590B6|kName|kDesc|Crystal Seashores Mega Bundle|Available As A Single Purchase, The Crystal Seashores Mega Bundle Includes The Apartment, Clubhouse, And Furniture Bundle For This Space. Now You Can Enjoy Everything This Elaborate Space Has To Offer!|Apt_Bundle|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
F8164201-98D848A5-9AFE56A1-8E92A00E|kName|kDesc|Nightlife Lounge Mega Bundle|Available As A Single Purchase, The Nightlife Lounge Mega Bundle Includes The Apartment, Clubhouse, And Furniture Bundle For This Space. Now You Can Enjoy Everything This Elaborate Space Has To Offer!|Apt_Bundle|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.60.0.451.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
F9AE8A05-9DA945BA-AE5CFB15-8EAD4A6A|kName|kDesc|Infinite Oasis Ranch Mega Bundle|Available As A Single Purchase, The Infinite Oasis Ranch Mega Bundle Includes The Apartment, Clubhouse, And Furniture Bundle For This Space. Now You Can Enjoy Everything This Elaborate Space Has To Offer!|Apt_Bundle|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
F9BC788B-770A4C95-B5BA06D0-3FA11CB5|kName|kDesc|Paris Clock Tower Mega Bundle|Take A Chance And Add Some Unique European Flavor To Your Style. This One Of A Kind Bundle Includes The Paris Clock Tower Apartment, 76 Furniture Items And 35 Clothing Items!|Apt_Bundle|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.55.0.155.BETA2|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
FEAB92CF-68B64523-88520E94-56C601EC|kName|kDesc|Tuscan Villa Mega Bundle|Available As A Single Purchase, The Tuscan Villa Mega Bundle Includes The Apartment, Clubhouse, And Furniture Bundle For This Space. Now You Can Enjoy Everything This Elaborate Space Has To Offer!|Apt_Bundle|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
