0464CA03-88374946-83E00C25-122881D1|kName|kDesc|No Man's Land, Museum Expansion Map.|This Map Pack Allows You To Fight On The No Man's Land Museum Map.|Apt_Addon|VEEMEE|HDK_1.66.0.144.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
05959018-4BC040BC-AD0B4D02-CC3BBF9D|kName|kDesc|Blueprint: Home - Cruise Ship Environment|Build Your Home On The Deck Of A Gigantic Cruise Ship. Note - You Will Need To Own Blueprint: Home To Access This Content Once It Has Been Purchased.|Apt_Addon|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.65.0.139.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
072F62A3-86CE44BC-9B85BDE6-0BD646A3|kName|kDesc|Lock-a-doodle Doodle Pack - Jewel Of The Skies|Each Doodle Pack Contains New Colours, Stickers, Words And Shapes. Please Note: Doodle Packs Can Only Be Used In Conjunction With The Lock-a-doodle Mini-game Or Active Object, Or Lock-a-doodle Gift Edition.|Apt_Addon|Lockwood|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
107E5858-4DD348B2-BD0C5BD1-10230902|kName|kDesc|The Complex: Silo|Purchasing This Item Will Unlock The Silo Area Within The Complex Apartment.|Apt_Addon|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
11B1D26A-73CC4E69-8422BEDF-DFB0C45A|kName|kDesc|Lock-a-doodle Doodle Pack - Spring Time|Each Doodle Pack Contains New Colours, Stickers, Words And Shapes. Please Note: Doodle Packs Can Only Be Used In Conjunction With The Lock-a-doodle Mini-game Or Active Object, Or Lock-a-doodle Gift Edition.|Apt_Addon|Lockwood|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
1774454A-BC524698-A3C44BF0-1AE58BFC|kName|kDesc|The Complex: Bio Dome|Purchasing This Item Will Unlock The Bio Dome Area Within The Complex Apartment.|Apt_Addon|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
1B2F04E5-4583472A-A47B6CFC-523B71CB|kName|kDesc|The Complex 2: Garden|Purchasing This Item Will Unlock The Garden Area Within The Complex 2.|Apt_Addon|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
1EF255E7-215C42B1-9223A893-FE407851|kName|kDesc|EmoRay: Mission Pack 2|EmoRay: Mission Pack 2 Gives You An Extra Mission With Story To Explore. Purchasing This Mission Pack For Volume One Will Give You The Ability To Earn These Rewards: -Cuddly Bear Companion -Cuddly Bear Rug (Flooring) Purchasing This Mission Pack Adds To Your Total Volume One Leaderboard Score. Purchasing And Completing All The Mission Packs For Volume One Will Earn You An Extra Song For The EmoRay Boombox. *This Mission Pack Can Only Be Purchased If You Have Purchased EmoRay: Volume One.|Apt_Addon|Heavy Water|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
20A52609-24EF4E2C-84E0ED20-4533C177|kName|kDesc|Blueprint: Home - City Of The Future Environment|Welcome To The City Of The Future. What Better Way To Show Off Your Blueprint: Home. Note - You Must Own Blueprint: Home By NDreams To Use This Item.|Apt_Addon|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
22140963-A0E6449B-A99E25B8-09D10A83|kName|kDesc|The Complex: Dock|Purchasing This Item Will Unlock The Dock Area Within The Complex Apartment.|Apt_Addon|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
2345481C-C5334098-86ED2AEE-050285BD|kName|kDesc|The Boutique Apartment: Bathroom|Purchasing This Item Will Unlock The Bathroom Area Within The Boutique Apartment.|Apt_Addon|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
25210DC6-3613429D-B1958F06-DA389239|kName|kDesc|Avalon Keep: Dungeon|Explore The Hidden Depths Of Your Keep. This Expansion Also Adds To The Rewards In The Crystal Hunter Game, As Well As Owner Only Rewards By Feeding The Dungeon Monster! *The Dungeon Can Only Be Purchased If You Already Own Avalon Keep.|Apt_Addon|Heavy Water|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
2BEDEC3A-EAE14B31-8F6D316D-087E57FB|kName|kDesc|The Complex: Officers Lounge|Purchasing This Item Will Unlock The Officers Lounge Area Within The Complex Apartment.|Apt_Addon|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
2C1B6890-61CC45DA-9D1CEE81-3E9B3878|kName|kDesc|Blueprint: Home - City Penthouse Environment|Build Your Home Atop A Huge Skyscraper In The Middle Of A Thriving City. Your Luxury Penthouse Will Benefit From The Best View Money Can Buy. Note - You Will Need To Own Blueprint: Home To Access This Content Once It Has Been Purchased.|Apt_Addon|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.65.0.139.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
3012CD2E-109740B8-B1C853A5-94BDF83A|kName|kDesc|Bramblenook Farm Update Bundle|An Epic Update To Bramblenook Farm! Allows You To Select New Styles For Your Bramblenook Farmhouse, Craft New Items For Yourself And Your Friends And Raise Cows. Also Contains: Cow Statue, Cow Companion And Calf Companion.|Apt_Addon|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
34D1601A-C8BE43C9-8477BD5D-45F3AB1B|kName|kDesc|Lock-a-doodle Doodle Pack - Iron Fusion|Each Doodle Pack Contains New Colours, Stickers, Words And Shapes. Please Note: Doodle Packs Can Only Be Used In Conjunction With The Lock-a-doodle Mini-game Or Active Object, Or Lock-a-doodle Gift Edition.|Apt_Addon|Lockwood|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
38B027E5-73D84C3D-829092A8-C85AC762|kName|kDesc|Cutteridge Ghost Stories Bundle|Delve Deeper Into The Mysteries Of Cutteridge Estate By Purchasing The Cutteridge Ghost Stories Bundle! This Eerie Expansion To Cutteridge Estate Reveals The Story Behind The Tormented Souls That Haunt The Estate And Introduces Terrifying New Minigames With Spooky Rewards. Bundle Includes: •4 New Minigames And Rewards Added To The Cutteridge Estate Personal Space •Ghostly Skull Companion •Mysterious Lantern (male And Female) •Evil Pumpkin •Complete All Four Minigames To Unlock The Ultimate Reward. Not For The Faint Of Heart!|Apt_Addon|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
47A1BB9B-AC6C4E05-97C62C83-B7CC217D|kName|kDesc|The Complex 2: Bedroom|Purchasing This Item Will Unlock The Bedroom Area Within The Complex 2.|Apt_Addon|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
4971A179-242F458A-8833B3EF-516D17F0|kName|kDesc|The Boutique Apartment: Kitchen|Purchasing This Item Will Unlock The Kitchen Area Within The Boutique Apartment.|Apt_Addon|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
4DC32458-EAA74304-976D83ED-4C8EADCD|kName|kDesc|Lock-a-doodle Doodle Pack - Food|Each Doodle Pack Contains New Colours, Stickers, Words And Shapes. Please Note: Doodle Packs Can Only Be Used In Conjunction With The Lock-a-doodle Mini-game Or Active Object, Or Lock-a-doodle Food.|Apt_Addon|Lockwood|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|LUA-REWARD|Res:0
65729B42-6F894015-A547BAEE-C816764D|kName|kDesc|Blueprint: Home - Alien Sky|A Beautiful Sky That Can Be Used To Change The Mood In Your Blueprint: Home. You Will Need To Own Blueprint: Home To Access These Items.|Apt_Addon|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.65.0.139.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
70CA65C3-9F0F4C13-99637E02-BB05586B|kName|kDesc|Novus Prime Private Hangar|This Is A Fully Functional Hangar For Your Novus Prime Officer's Quarters. With This Hangar You Can Play Missions With Friends, Use The Workshop, And Collect Salaries.|Apt_Addon|Hellfire Games, Inc.|HDK_1.52.0.2.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
77F339D2-618047F4-8247A680-126C9040|kName|kDesc|EmoRay: Mission Pack 1|EmoRay: Mission Pack 1 Gives You An Extra Mission With Story To Explore. Purchasing This Mission Pack For Volume One Will Give You The Ability To Earn These Rewards: -Hammy Companion -Cuddly Bear Chair (Chair) Purchasing This Mission Pack Adds To Your Total Volume One Leaderboard Score. Purchasing And Completing All The Mission Packs For Volume One Will Earn You An Extra Song For The EmoRay Boombox. *This Mission Pack Can Only Be Purchased If You Have Purchased EmoRay: Volume One.|Apt_Addon|Heavy Water|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
790A77BE-989D4E55-B7AF209B-1C2A0C8C|kName|kDesc|Blueprint: Home - Night Time Sky|This Will Change The Sky In Your Blueprint: Home To A Blissful Night Time Sky. Note - You Must Own Blueprint: Home By NDreams To Use This Item.|Apt_Addon|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
7FB87048-98BE4B23-ADB553EE-308ED7C6|kName|kDesc|Lock-a-doodle Doodle Pack - Stitchkins|Each Doodle Pack Contains New Colours, Stickers, Words And Shapes. Please Note: Doodle Packs Can Only Be Used In Conjunction With The Lock-a-doodle Mini-game Or Active Object, Or Lock-a-doodle Gift Edition.|Apt_Addon|Lockwood|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
81B9C15A-F03542E7-A8246710-78287347|kName|kDesc|Lock-a-doodle Doodle Pack - Dinosaurs|Each Doodle Pack Contains New Colours, Stickers, Words And Shapes. Please Note: Doodle Packs Can Only Be Used In Conjunction With The Lock-a-doodle Mini-game Or Active Object, Or Lock-a-doodle Gift Edition.|Apt_Addon|Lockwood|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
85F74B72-09A9476D-B28162EA-39CEF087|kName|kDesc|Blueprint: Home - Desert 1995 Environment|Build Your Home In The Middle Of A Surreal Desert, What Mysteries Will You See? Note - You Will Need To Own Blueprint: Home To Access This Content Once It Has Been Purchased.|Apt_Addon|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.65.0.139.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
93BAE492-CADD48EC-A242D170-652A63A8|kName|kDesc|Blueprint: Home - Snow Capped Mountain Environment|The Perfect Environment For Those Who Do Not Wish To Be Disturbed. This Environment Comes Complete With Falling Snow. Note - You Must Own Blueprint: Home By NDreams To Use This Item.|Apt_Addon|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
A6DE6ED5-38DA416D-9ED0704F-7BEEA9FF|kName|kDesc|EmoRay: Volume Two|EmoRay: Volume Two Contents Immediately Available In Game: -Access To Chapters 5 - 8 In Story Mode Access To Earn These Rewards In Game: -Sergeant McMillen Outfit (Male) -Soldier Outfit (Male) -P-Touch Outfit (Male) -Mrs.Radd Outfit (Female) -An Additional Song For The EmoRay Boombox -Grizzly Bear Head (Male) -Grizzly Bear Head (Female) -Bare Grizzly Bear Chair (Chair) -Bare Grizzly Bear Rug (Flooring) -Raging Unicorns Poster (Wall Hanging) -Taxi Driver Outfit (Male) -P-Touch Companion -Radd&Son Garage Sign (Wall Hanging) -Mounted Cuddly Bear Head (Wall Hanging) -Mounted Grizzly Bear Head (Wall Hanging) Purchasing EmoRay: Volume Two Grants You The Ability To Post Scores To More Leaderboards And Earn More ModPoints. ModPoints Can Be Used In EmoRay To Buy Weapon And Vehicle Upgrades As Well As Virtual Items For Use In PlayStation®Home.|Apt_Addon|Heavy Water|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
ACF5EA5C-182A405E-9A2AB024-98977F13|kName|kDesc|Lock-a-doodle Doodle Pack - Medusa|Each Doodle Pack Contains New Colours, Stickers, Words And Shapes. Please Note: Doodle Packs Can Only Be Used In Conjunction With The Lock-a-doodle Mini-game Or Active Object, Or Lock-a-doodle Gift Edition.|Apt_Addon|Lockwood|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
B07F16AD-BF474F0F-82E6ED9F-C5865C90|kName|kDesc|Lock-a-doodle Doodle Pack - Delirious Squid|Each Doodle Pack Contains New Colours, Stickers, Words And Shapes. Please Note: Doodle Packs Can Only Be Used In Conjunction With The Lock-a-doodle Mini-game Or Active Object, Or Lock-a-doodle Gift Edition.|Apt_Addon|Lockwood|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
B080B774-33364399-ABB7304A-97D17B47|kName|kDesc|The Complex 2: Kitchen|Purchasing This Item Will Unlock The Kitchen Area Within The Complex 2.|Apt_Addon|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
BA918110-24624739-B096C989-6B628D65|kName|kDesc|Blueprint: Home - Golden Sunset Sky|A Beautiful Sky That Can Be Used To Change The Mood In Your Blueprint: Home. You Will Need To Own Blueprint: Home To Access These Items.|Apt_Addon|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.65.0.139.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
C10056FC-9F90420C-812E2532-4C48044B|kName|kDesc|Lock-a-doodle Doodle Pack - Drey|Each Doodle Pack Contains New Colours, Stickers, Words And Shapes. Please Note: Doodle Packs Can Only Be Used In Conjunction With The Lock-a-doodle Mini-game Or Active Object, Or Lock-a-doodle Gift Edition.|Apt_Addon|Lockwood|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
C488CFA1-CFB047EC-BA8B275C-4CE5C27D|kName|kDesc|EmoRay: Volume One|EmoRay: Volume One Contents Immediately Available In Game: -Access To Chapters 1 - 4 In Story Mode -Emo's Garage Loft -Emo Ray Outfit (Male) -Emo Ray Outfit (Female) -Emo Ray Boombox With 1 Song Access To Earn These Rewards In Game: -Porsche Outfit (Female) -Hammy Outfit (Male) -Chopper Outfit (Male) -Mr.Radd Outfit (Male) -An Additional Song For The Emo Ray Boombox -Cuddly Bear Head (Male) -Cuddly Bear Head (Female) -Health Pick Up (Ornament) -Ammo Pick Up (Ornament) -Spare Parts (Ornament) -Cuddly Bear Poster (Wall Hanging) -Heavy Water Poster (Wall Hanging) -Bare Cuddly Bear Chair (Chair) -Bare Cuddly Bear Rug (Flooring) -Porsche Companion -Business Man Outfit -Mailman Outfit Purchasing EmoRay: Volume One Grants You The Ability To Post Scores To Leaderboards, Earn ModPoints, And You Receive The Personal Apartment: Emo's Garage Loft. ModPoints Can Be Used In EmoRay To Buy Weapon And Vehicle Upgrades As Well As Virtual Items For Use In PlayStation®Home.|Apt_Addon|Heavy Water|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
C523045F-CB8E4C95-B739410B-429EBE7C|kName|kDesc|The Boutique Apartment: Lounge|Purchasing This Item Will Unlock The Lounge Area Within The Boutique Apartment.|Apt_Addon|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
C994058B-0D584CD8-84415347-D516211D|kName|kDesc|Lock-a-doodle Doodle Pack - Dream Universe|Each Doodle Pack Contains New Colours, Stickers, Words And Shapes. Please Note: Doodle Packs Can Only Be Used In Conjunction With The Lock-a-doodle Mini-game Or Active Object, Or Lock-a-doodle Gift Edition.|Apt_Addon|Lockwood|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
D10D8B46-76CA4C91-A9B9A836-1F5E1510|kName|kDesc|The Boutique Apartment: Terrace|Purchasing This Item Will Unlock The Terrace Area Within The Boutique Apartment.|Apt_Addon|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
D206F986-26FC46B3-90EE62A1-EC2BC0A4|kName|kDesc|Blueprint: Aurora|You Have Unlocked The Aurora-themed Environment For Use Within Blueprint: Home.|Apt_Addon|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.65.0.139.BETA|AUTO-REWARD|Res:0
E9495961-4B2F4D06-A0D80112-5EC74324|kName|kDesc|The Complex 2: Feature Room|Purchasing This Item Will Unlock The Feature Room Area Within The Complex 2.|Apt_Addon|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
E9641292-9B964507-913FF4F2-F79060E9|kName|kDesc|Cutteridge Ghost Stories Ultimate Bundle|Delve Deeper Into The Mysteries Of Cutteridge Estate By Purchasing The Cutteridge Ghost Stories Ultimate Bundle! This Eerie Expansion To Cutteridge Estate Reveals The Story Behind The Tormented Souls That Haunt The Estate And Introduces Terrifying New Minigames With Spooky Rewards. Bundle Includes: •4 New Minigames And Rewards Added To The Cutteridge Estate Personal Space •Ghostly Skull Companion •Mysterious Lantern (male And Female) •Evil Pumpkin •Complete All Four Minigames To Unlock The Ultimate Reward. Not For The Faint Of Heart! Also Includes: •Demonic Reading Chair •Demonic Ottoman •Demonic Antiquities Cabinet •Demonic Inscribed Cabinet •Demonic Antique Wood-Burning Stove •Demonic Chest Of Drawers •Possessed Portrait •Demonic Victorian Sofa •Demonic Inlaid Wood Table •Demonic Victorian Dining Chair •Demonic Sideboard •Demonic Candelabra •Demonic Chest •Tentacle Throne|Apt_Addon|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
EB2AD92F-A922421A-8A639F44-C145DE2D|kName|kDesc|Blueprint: Home - Space Dome Environment|Build Your Home In The Depths Of Space, Offering A Stunning View Of The Cosmos. Note - You Will Need To Own Blueprint: Home To Access This Content Once It Has Been Purchased.|Apt_Addon|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.65.0.139.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
ED2C31F6-A9F44729-B940D591-143FC27E|kName|kDesc|Blueprint: Home - Clear Morning Sky|A Beautiful Sky That Can Be Used To Change The Mood In Your Blueprint: Home. You Will Need To Own Blueprint: Home To Access These Items.|Apt_Addon|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.65.0.139.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
F122E567-AAB0436C-840F8441-A434B3A7|kName|kDesc|Blueprint: Home - Chameleo Sky|This Item Will Cause The Colour Of The Sky In Your Blueprint: Home To Constantly Change. There Is A Whole Spectrum Of Colours To Explore, So What Are You Waiting For? Note - You Must Own Blueprint: Home By NDreams To Use This Item.|Apt_Addon|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
F237114C-599E49B6-B177A316-ECB73490|kName|kDesc|The Boutique Apartment: Bedroom|Purchasing This Item Will Unlock The Bedroom Area Within The Boutique Apartment.|Apt_Addon|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
FABC84FE-2D744ADB-82765112-6B6E56B4|kName|kDesc|Avalon Keep: King's Chambers|A Grand Bed Chamber For Royalty. No Keep Is Complete Without The King's Chambers. This Update Comes With More Additions To The Crystal Hunter Mini-game For Owners And Guests.|Apt_Addon|Heavy Water|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
FF3B8FE1-E6164EA0-A56DE6D9-6D382CDD|kName|kDesc|Lock-a-doodle Doodle Pack - Sodium|Each Doodle Pack Contains New Colours, Stickers, Words And Shapes. Please Note: Doodle Packs Can Only Be Used In Conjunction With The Lock-a-doodle Mini-game Or Active Object, Or Lock-a-doodle Gift Edition.|Apt_Addon|Lockwood|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
