034CBED9-BCFE45DA-845E54F5-92C1303E|kName|kDesc|Techno Peep - Bundle Pack - Robot Red|Move To The Groove With Techno Peep! As The Hottest Gadget On The Market, It's Three For One With Extra Peep Fun! Bring Your Heavy Pet Peep Into Your Apartment And Let The Fun Begin. You Can Control Your Peep With Custom Animations And Moves. Take Him Outside Of Your Apartment As A Companion Or Place Him On Display In Your Apartment In His Peep-a-Boo Box. Collect Them All And Stack Them For All To See! This Set Includes The Following Items. ・Techno Peep - Robot Red ・Techno Peep - Static Mini - Robot Red ・Techno Peep - Heavy Pet - Robot Red ※ All Of The Above Items Will Become Available In Their Relevant Categories On Purchasing This Bundle.|Companion_Bundle|Heavy Water|HDK_1.66.0.144.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
03A7713C-32C74119-B2C4C38F-94550FE5|kName|kDesc|Codeglue Companion Special Bundle 2|It's The Codeglue Companion Special Bundle 2! This Bundle Includes The Spotted Jack, Brown Jack And Dog House. **IMPORTANT NOTICE** This Codeglue Companion Special Bundle 2may Contain The Items You Have Already Purchased. Only The Item Which Is Not Yet Purchased Is Added To Your Inventory And Same Purchased Item Will Not Appear In The Inventory Twice. Purchased Special Bundles Are Not Refundable, Transferable Or Exchangeable, And Cannot Be Redeemed For Cash Or Credit.|Companion_Bundle|Codeglue B.V.|HDK_1.55.0.155.BETA2|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
068E76B1-1DC641E8-ACE3D6CE-31F03EEB|kName|kDesc|Apartment Pets: Li'l Ninja Bundle|See Your Apartment Come To Life With These Fantastic Free-roaming Pets. For Best Results, Try Combining Them With The Other Apartment Pets Now Available From NDreams. This Bundle Includes: * Apartment Pets: Li'l Ninjas (Appliance) * Ninjutsu Warrior - Li'l Ninja (Companion) ※ Upon Purchase, All Items Will Be Added To Their Corresponding Categories.|Companion_Bundle|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
07DEAD37-4D0F4324-86B128B1-ECE08162|kName|kDesc|Up-Chuck Peep - Bundle Pack - Puke Green|Up-Chuck Is One Wild And Crazy Guy And The Life Of Every Party! It's Three For One With Extra Peep Fun! Bring Your Heavy Pet Peep Into Your Apartment And Let The Fun Begin. You Can Control Your Peep With Custom Animations And Moves. Take Him Outside Of Your Apartment As A Companion Or Place Him On Display In Your Apartment In His Peep-a-Boo Box. Collect Them All And Stack Them For All To See! This Set Includes The Following Items. ・Up-Chuck Peep - Puke Green ・Up-Chuck Peep - Static Mini - Puke Green ・Up-Chuck Peep - Heavy Pet - Puke Green ※ All Of The Above Items Will Become Available In Their Relevant Categories On Purchasing This Bundle.|Companion_Bundle|Heavy Water|HDK_1.66.0.144.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
08A8BA38-7DC74021-9FD9A06D-8126E389|kName|kDesc|Adult Tiger Companions Bundle|White Tigers, Orange Tigers, And Even Black Tigers, This Bundle Has Them All!|Companion_Bundle|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.55.0.155.BETA2|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
0988C713-0BE94765-967CDC82-0ED5CF37|kName|kDesc|HGL Creature Costume & Companion Bundle - Troops|Now You Can Look Like Your Favourite HGL Creature. Troops Are Here To Battle, To Fight And To Win! This Bundle Includes: (1) HGL Creature Costume - Troops (Male) (2) HGL Creature Costume - Troops (Female) (3) HGL Mini-Creature Companion - Troops Purchasing This Item Grants You 60 Fights In HGL.|Companion_Bundle|VEEMEE|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
0A8E6310-4CD34701-85B11B9C-82418FC7|kName|kDesc|Creepy Peep - Bundle Pack - Orphan Orange|Creepy Peep Is A Playful Little Monster Who Wants To Be Your Friend! It's Three For One With Extra Peep Fun! Bring Your Peep Into Your Apartment And Let The Fun Begin. You Can Control You Peep With Custom Animations And Moves. Take Him Outside Of Your Apartment As A Companion Or Place Him On Display In Your Apartment In His Peep-a-Boo Box. Collect Them All And Stack Them For All To See! This Set Includes The Following Items. ・Creepy Peep - Orphan Orange ・Creepy Peep - Static Mini - Orphan Orange ・Creepy Peep - Heavy Pet - Orphan Orange ※ All Of The Above Items Will Become Available In Their Relevant Categories On Purchasing This Bundle.|Companion_Bundle|Heavy Water|HDK_1.66.0.144.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
0D154434-38854E42-925F8A71-6F6C301B|kName|kDesc|Dusty - The Golden Brimstone Dancer Bundle|You Are Gonna Dig Dusty; She's Worth Her Weight In Gold. 24 Carat And Built Like Fort Knox. When She Dances, You'll Agree That Dusty's Commodities Should Be Held In The U. S. Federal Reserve. Put This Full Sized…active Object In Your Personal Space And Show Her Miniature Version Around Home As A Dancing Companion. Also Comes With Gold Dance Platform!|Companion_Bundle|Mass Media Games, Inc.|HDK_1.51.0.60.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
0E2E0D0D-3931480A-9B289129-8E8097CE|kName|kDesc|Kittens - Bundle|These Kittens Are A Little Balls Of Furry Feline Fun. This Bundle Contains: (1) Kittens - Black (2) Kittens - Black & White (3) Kittens - White (4) Kittens - Calico (5) Kittens - Ginger (6) Kittens - Tabby ※These Items Are Portable Items. ※Upon Purchase, The Items Will Be Placed Into Their Respective Categories.|Companion_Bundle|VEEMEE|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
133C17DE-C99946AF-875A6B8B-B9D4FDE2|kName|kDesc|HGL Creature Costume & Companion Bundle - Sonics|Now You Can Look Like Your Favourite HGL Creature. Sonics Hit Harder Than The Phattest Beats! This Bundle Includes: (1) HGL Creature Costume - Sonics (Male) (2) HGL Creature Costume - Sonics (Female) (3) HGL Mini-Creature Companion - Sonics Purchasing This Item Grants You 60 Fights In HGL.|Companion_Bundle|VEEMEE|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
1B1D9306-355F4E9B-A9B1D513-5339C8D6|kName|kDesc|Apartment Pets: Volume 1 Bundle|See Your Apartment Come To Life With These Fantastic Free-roaming Pets. This Bundle Includes: * Apartment Pets: Benjis (Appliance) * Benji (Companion) * Apartment Pets: Nippers (Appliance) * Nipper (Companion) * Apartment Pets: Li'l Ninjas (Appliance) * Ninjutsu Warrior - Li'l Ninja (Companion) ※ Upon Purchase, All Items Will Be Added To Their Corresponding Categories.|Companion_Bundle|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
1B2F4199-52324D27-807BADD9-FFEE0514|kName|kDesc|Three Cheerful Cats Set|This Set Includes A Tortoiseshell Cat, Black Cat, And Tiger Cat That Follow Their Owner. This Set Includes The Following Items Cheerful Tortoiseshell Cat/portable Item Cheerful Black Cat/portable Item Cheerful Tiger Cat/portable Item Each Item Will Be Added To The Corresponding Category When Purchased.|Companion_Bundle|Granzella Inc.|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
1C7E0A2B-423D4669-8E3E0746-D591E543|kName|kDesc|Codeglue Companion Special Bundle 1|It's The Codeglue Companion Special Bundle 1! This Bundle Includes The Puppy Dog, Valentine Cupid, Cute Kitten And Hamster In A Ball. **IMPORTANT NOTICE** This Codeglue Companion Special Bundle 1may Contain The Items You Have Already Purchased. Only The Item Which Is Not Yet Purchased Is Added To Your Inventory And Same Purchased Item Will Not Appear In The Inventory Twice. Purchased Special Bundles Are Not Refundable, Transferable Or Exchangeable, And Cannot Be Redeemed For Cash Or Credit.|Companion_Bundle|Codeglue B.V.|HDK_1.55.0.155.BETA2|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
215BABE6-49274526-9EC6970C-A3CF8A4E|kName|kDesc|Apartment Pets: Nippers Bundle|See Your Apartment Come To Life With These Fantastic Free-roaming Pets. For Best Results, Try Combining Them With The Other Apartment Pets Now Available From NDreams. This Bundle Includes: * Apartment Pets: Nippers (Appliance) * Nipper (Companion) ※ Upon Purchase, All Items Will Be Added To Their Corresponding Categories.|Companion_Bundle|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
260DA8F7-80FB4033-87DFC857-003A1166|kName|kDesc|Chim Peep - Bundle Pack - Red On White|More Fun Than A Barrel Of Monkeys Is Chim Peep! Dressed To The Nines In His Monkey Suit It's Three For One With Extra Peep Fun! Bring Your Heavy Pet Peep Into Your Apartment And Let The Fun Begin. You Can Control Your Peep With Custom Animations And Moves. Take Him Outside Of Your Apartment As A Companion Or Place Him On Display In Your Apartment In His Peep-a-Boo Box. Collect Them All And Stack Them For All To See! This Set Includes The Following Items. ・Chim Peep - Red On White ・Chim Peep - Static Mini - Red On White ・Chim Peep - Heavy Pet - Red On White ※ All Of The Above Items Will Become Available In Their Relevant Categories On Purchasing This Bundle.|Companion_Bundle|Heavy Water|HDK_1.66.0.144.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
27B3BB01-B4DF4145-A8156426-95931CD5|kName|kDesc|Lil' Snow Peep - Bundle Pack - Pampered Purple|Lil' Snow Peep Has Lost Her Sheep And Needs A Friend To Guide Her. It's Three For One With Extra Peep Fun! Bring Your Peep Into Your Apartment And Let The Fun Begin. You Can Control You Peep With Custom Animations And Moves. Take Him Outside Of Your Apartment As A Companion Or Place Him On Display In Your Apartment In His Peep-a-Boo Box. Collect Them All And Stack Them For All To See! This Set Includes The Following Items. ・Lil' Snow Peep - Pampered Purple ・Lil' Snow Peep - Static Mini - Pampered Purple ・Lil' Snow Peep - Heavy Pet - Pampered Purple ※ All Of The Above Items Will Become Available In Their Relevant Categories On Purchasing This Bundle.|Companion_Bundle|Heavy Water|HDK_1.66.0.144.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
2947E6C1-E1714290-BF41DAD7-D9CDA630|kName|kDesc|HGL Creature Costume & Companion Bundle - Critters|Now You Can Look Like Your Favourite HGL Creature. Critters Are Crazy In The Coconut! This Bundle Includes: (1) HGL Creature Costume - Critters (Male) (2) HGL Creature Costume - Critters (Female) (3) HGL Mini-Creature Companion - Critters Purchasing This Item Grants You 60 Fights In HGL.|Companion_Bundle|VEEMEE|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
30670D58-811C4F1A-AB825F3C-5CFC3FD9|kName|kDesc|Super Peep Bonus Bundle (30 Items In All!)|Pump Up The Peeps With This Super Peep Bonus Bundle Pack, Containing All 30 Peeps! Ten (10) Heavy Pet Peeps To Bring Into Your Apartment And Let The Fun Begin. You Can Control Your Peep With Custom Animations And Moves. Ten (10) Companion Peeps To Take Outside Of Your Apartment As A Companion And Ten (10) Mini-Peeps To Display In Your Apartment, Each In It's Own Peep-a-Boo Box. Stack Them For All To See! Colors As Shown. This Set Includes The Following Items. ・Chim Peep - Black On Black ・Chim Peep - Static Mini - Black On Black ・Chim Peep - Heavy Pet - Black On Black ・Techno Peep - Glowing Green ・Techno Peep - Static Mini - Glowing Green ・Techno Peep - Heavy Pet - Glowing Green ・Super Powered Peep - Ricochet Red ・Super Powered Peep - Static Mini - Ricochet Red ・Super Powered Peep - Heavy Pet - Ricochet Red ・Up-Chuck Peep - Puke Green ・Up-Chuck Peep - Static Mini - Puke Green ・Up-Chuck Peep - Heavy Pet - Puke Green ・What The Bleep Peep - Bone White ・What The Bleep Peep - Static Mini - Bone White ・What The Bleep Peep - Heavy Pet - Bone White ・Scary Fairy Peep - Persnickety Purple ・Scary Fairy Peep - Static Mini - Persnickety Purple ・Scary Fairy Peep - Heavy Pet - Persnickety Purple ・Sweetie Peep - Perfect Pink ・Sweetie Peep - Static Mini - Perfect Pink ・Sweetie Peep - Heavy Pet - Perfect Pink ・Lil' Snow Peep - Pampered Purple ・Lil' Snow Peep - Static Mini - Pampered Purple ・Lil' Snow Peep - Heavy Pet - Pampered Purple ・Sunshine Peep - Blue Skies ・Sunshine Peep - Static Mini - Blue Skies ・Sunshine Peep - Heavy Pet - Blue Skies ・Creepy Peep - Monster Green ・Creepy Peep - Static Mini - Monster Green ・Creepy Peep - Heavy Pet - Monster Green ※ All Of The Above Items Will Become Available In Their Relevant Categories On Purchasing This Bundle.|Companion_Bundle|Heavy Water|HDK_1.66.0.144.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
338E8212-E1D840BC-807B0CA8-25AA86EA|kName|kDesc|Apartment Pets: Kittens Bundle|See Your Apartment Come To Life With These Fantastic Free-roaming Pets. For Best Results, Try Combining Them With The Other Apartment Pets Now Available From NDreams. This Bundle Includes: * Apartment Pets: Kittens (Appliance) * Apartment Pets: Kitten (Companion) ※ Upon Purchase, All Items Will Be Added To Their Corresponding Categories.|Companion_Bundle|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
34B276E5-AB584FBE-A5AB3296-1EAE0F75|kName|kDesc|X7 Bundle Volume 78|Exclusive X7 Value Bundle! Includes: Glamourous Hair Glamourous Animated Bracelet GlamourousAnimated Hoops Earrings Glamourous Animated Heels Glamourous Peach Dress Ancient Broadsword Mermaid Companion|Companion_Bundle|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
35C78953-1CC04689-85ADC818-784BF859|kName|kDesc|Beautiful Shadows Companion Bundle|These Large Companions Show Others What You Really Look Like. This Bundle Includes: * Beautiful Shadow Companion (The Hunk) * Beautiful Shadow Companion (The Honey) These Are Portable Items. ※ Upon Purchase, All Items Will Be Added To Their Corresponding Categories.|Companion_Bundle|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
3618915B-C6D2470B-B77D80A4-E515CFED|kName|kDesc|Chim Peep - Bundle Pack - Black On Black|More Fun Than A Barrel Of Monkeys Is Chim Peep! Dressed To The Nines In His Monkey Suit It's Three For One With Extra Peep Fun! Bring Your Heavy Pet Peep Into Your Apartment And Let The Fun Begin. You Can Control Your Peep With Custom Animations And Moves. Take Him Outside Of Your Apartment As A Companion Or Place Him On Display In Your Apartment In His Peep-a-Boo Box. Collect Them All And Stack Them For All To See! This Set Includes The Following Items. ・Chim Peep - Black On Black ・Chim Peep - Static Mini - Black On Black ・Chim Peep - Heavy Pet - Black On Black ※ All Of The Above Items Will Become Available In Their Relevant Categories On Purchasing This Bundle.|Companion_Bundle|Heavy Water|HDK_1.66.0.144.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
37482A97-70004B87-B1EA58B7-D990B310|kName|kDesc|We Got The Peeps 2|We Got The Peeps Features A Bundle Of Some Cool Characters. Chim Peep, Techno Peep And Super Power Peep Come Packaged As Heavy Pets, Companions And Mini-Peeps! Nine Fantastic Treats In One Big Bundle! Colors As Shown. This Set Includes The Following Items. ・Chim Peep - Red On White ・Chim Peep - Static Mini - Red On White ・Chim Peep - Heavy Pet - Red On White ・Techno Peep - Robot Red ・Techno Peep - Static Mini - Robot Red ・Techno Peep - Heavy Pet - Robot Red ・Super Powered Peep - Bolting Blue ・Super Powered Peep - Static Mini - Bolting Blue ・Super Powered Peep - Heavy Pet - Bolting Blue ※ All Of The Above Items Will Become Available In Their Relevant Categories On Purchasing This Bundle.|Companion_Bundle|Heavy Water|HDK_1.66.0.144.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
38521F82-EF724E68-9BCE99AF-3DF51237|kName|kDesc|Lilith - Brimstone Dancer Bundle|According To Legends, Lilith Was Turned Into A Demon For Refusing To Obey So Don't Try To Tame This Wild Animal. Lilith Means belonging To The Night And That's Just When She's At Her Finest. Put This Full Sized…active Object In Your Personal Space And Show Her Miniature Version Around Home As A Dancing Companion.|Companion_Bundle|Mass Media|HDK_1.50.0.238.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
399C0D8F-2EBE49A6-9B42DE5F-9D3C615B|kName|kDesc|Avalon Dragon Companion Bundle|Love All The Avalon Dragon Companions? Why Not Grab This Bundle To Get All Four Dragon, Plus A Bonus Garden Variety Dragon! Includes Fire Dragon Companion, Ice Dragon Companion, Lightning Dragon Companion, Earth Dragon Companion And Garden Variety Dragon Companion.|Companion_Bundle|Heavy Water|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
3AE9B171-90F74888-B38A9DD4-54A54482|kName|kDesc|Swarms - Bundle|Take To The Skies And Replace Your Avatar In A Variety Of Creatures. This Bundle Contains: (1) A Swarm Of Bees (2) A Flight Of Dragonflies (3) A Swarm Of Butterflies This Locomotion Object Will Boost Your Speed: ・Standard = 5.25 M/s ※These Items Are Portable Items.|Companion_Bundle|VEEMEE|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
3C2C2FAF-A1674216-ABCC2994-D3C3CCC9|kName|kDesc|Animated Emoticon Super Bundle|Express Yourself With An Animated Emoticon Buddy - Including Angry, Cheeky, Happy, Super Happy, Oops, Sad And Cool|Companion_Bundle|Sodium - Lockwood|HDK_1.3.0.130.BETA2|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
3C41C918-3A1B4679-B91056E2-F4304231|kName|kDesc|Heavy Pets Halloween Bundle|Get All Three Spooky Heavy Pets With This Halloween Bundle! Includes The Ghostling, Flaming Skull, And Vampire Batling Pet Items. Place One Of These In Your Apartment And Set The Mood For The Season With These Roaming Pets!|Companion_Bundle|Heavy Water|HDK_1.3.6.22.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
3FAB1B79-27E74B06-B29700E9-1B1F9DF3|kName|kDesc|Freaky Peep Pack|The Freaky Peeps Are Packaged As One Sick Set. Up-Chuck Peep, What The Bleep Peep And Scary Fairy Peep Come Packaged As Heavy Pets, Companions And Mini-Peeps! Nine Fantastic Treats In One Big Bundle! Colors As Shown. This Set Includes The Following Items. ・Up-Chuck Peep - Puke Green ・Up-Chuck Peep - Static Mini - Puke Green ・Up-Chuck Peep - Heavy Pet - Puke Green ・What The Bleep Peep - Bone White ・What The Bleep Peep - Static Mini - Bone White ・What The Bleep Peep - Heavy Pet - Bone White ・Scary Fairy Peep - Persnickety Purple ・Scary Fairy Peep - Static Mini - Persnickety Purple ・Scary Fairy Peep - Heavy Pet - Persnickety Purple ※ All Of The Above Items Will Become Available In Their Relevant Categories On Purchasing This Bundle.|Companion_Bundle|Heavy Water|HDK_1.66.0.144.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
3FB6C896-C0B94BC7-9BA4A658-586D2918|kName|kDesc|Lockwood Safari Companion Pack|Lockwood Safari Companion Pack This Pack Includes The Following: • Kubwa The Silverback Gorilla • Kiboko The Baby Hippo • Tembo The Baby Elephant Go On A Safari With Lockwood!|Companion_Bundle|Lockwood|HDK_1.60.0.450.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
43E2B556-B91A4245-8C72C6D6-B7644A8C|kName|kDesc|Domestic Cat - Bundle|A Bundle Of Six Beautiful Felines This Bundle Contains: (1) Domestic Cat - Black (2) Domestic Cat - Black & White (3) Domestic Cat - White (4) Domestic Cat - Tortoiseshell (5) Domestic Cat - Ginger (6) Domestic Cat - Grey|Companion_Bundle|VEEMEE|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
464B557F-A48B46D8-A36024B1-136E57D5|kName|kDesc|What The Bleep Peep - Bundle Pack - Blazing Blue|What The Bleep Peep Is Bad To The Bone! This Naughty Little Peep Brings Three For One With Extra Peep Fun! Bring Your Peep Into Your Apartment And Let The Fun Begin. You Can Control You Peep With Custom Animations And Moves. Take Him Outside Of Your Apartment As A Companion Or Place Him On Display In Your Apartment In His Peep-a-Boo Box. Collect Them All And Stack Them For All To See! This Set Includes The Following Items. ・What The Bleep Peep - Blazing Blue ・What The Bleep Peep - Static Mini - Blazing Blue ・What The Bleep Peep - Heavy Pet - Blazing Blue ※ All Of The Above Items Will Become Available In Their Relevant Categories On Purchasing This Bundle.|Companion_Bundle|Heavy Water|HDK_1.66.0.144.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
471FD4EE-75E549BF-AF98C3B7-16B3E803|kName|kDesc|Golden Dragon Bundle|The Rarest Dragon In Avalon Is The Golden Dragon. This Bundle Will Showcase Your Skills Of Hunting Down And Taming The Rarest Of Dragons. - Receive Golden Dragon Companion - Receive Dragon Rider: Golden. This Dragon Has All 5 Element Projectile Types! - Receive The Golden Dragon Statue - When You Ride Dragons In The Village Of Hexalon You Will Be Riding A Golden, Fire-breathing Dragon For All To See|Companion_Bundle|Heavy Water|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
4A1AA0E3-38EC4564-AFA9312B-16A3429A|kName|kDesc|HGL Mini-Creature Companion - Bundle|The Massive Creatures You Know And Love Weren't The Only Experiment Run By The Home Grown Laboratory. Designed To Live In Underground Tunnel Networks; These Mini-Creatures Are Perfect For A World Where The Surface Is An Inhospitable, Irradiated Wasteland. This Bundle Includes: (1) HGL Mini-Creature Companion - Troops (2) HGL Mini-Creature Companion - Critters (3) HGL Mini-Creature Companion - Sonics (4) HGL Mini-Creature Companion - Undead Purchasing This Item Grants You 80 Fights In HGL.|Companion_Bundle|VEEMEE|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
4A90C63D-6192491D-AC390981-D3353387|kName|kDesc|Sunshine Peep - Bundle Pack - Summer Rain|Let The Sunshine In With With Warm Rays Of Sunshine Peep! It's Three For One With Extra Peep Fun! Bring Your Peep Into Your Apartment And Let The Fun Begin. You Can Control You Peep With Custom Animations And Moves. Take Her Outside Of Your Apartment As A Companion Or Place Her On Display In Your Apartment In His Peep-a-Boo Box. Collect Them All And Stack Them For All To See! This Set Includes The Following Items. ・Sunshine Peep - Summer Rain ・Sunshine Peep - Static Mini - Summer Rain ・Sunshine Peep - Heavy Pet - Summer Rain ※ All Of The Above Items Will Become Available In Their Relevant Categories On Purchasing This Bundle.|Companion_Bundle|Heavy Water|HDK_1.66.0.144.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
5137BD28-2A074715-96BAB0F0-EC696ECA|kName|kDesc|Animated Emoticon Super Bundle|Express Yourself With An Animated Emoticon Buddy - Including Angry, Cheeky, Happy, Super Happy, Oops, Sad And Cool|Companion_Bundle|Sodium - Lockwood|HDK_1.3.0.130.BETA2|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
52703CBA-BA9E45BC-B3B92438-88C3B315|kName|kDesc|Pirate Companions Bundle|Collect The Entire Crew With This Bundle Of Companions. Contains Captain Crackers, The Floating Nederlander And Mister Peels The Picaroon.|Companion_Bundle|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.60.0.450.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
572E434A-D45247B8-AAF9043F-948DCFB4|kName|kDesc|Doctor Who - Dalek Companion Bundle|All Of The Dalek Companions In One Bundle! EXTERMINATE! 1) Doctor Who - Drone Dalek (Red) Companion 2) Doctor Who - Supreme Dalek (White) Companion 3) Doctor Who - Eternal Dalek (Yellow) Companion 4) Doctor Who - Strategist Dalek (Blue) Companion 5) Doctor Who - Scientist Dalek (Orange) Companion Doctor Who Logo © 2013 And TM BBC. Dalek Image © BBC/ Terry Nation 1963. Licensed By BBC WW Ltd.|Companion_Bundle|BBC Worldwide Limited|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
5870CE14-7FA6437E-AD6C0771-A5423E41|kName|kDesc|Undead Animal Bundle|Bring Life Back To This Collection Of Undead Pets. This Bundle Contains: (1) Undead Dog (2) Undead Cat (3) Undead Raven ※Upon Purchase, The Items Will Be Placed Into Their Respective Categories. ※These Items Are Portable Items.|Companion_Bundle|VEEMEE|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
59A1403C-D36B401B-B174E78D-81C5B5F9|kName|kDesc|Techno Peep - Bundle Pack - Glowing Green|Move To The Groove With Techno Peep! As The Hottest Gadget On The Market, It's Three For One With Extra Peep Fun! Bring Your Heavy Pet Peep Into Your Apartment And Let The Fun Begin. You Can Control Your Peep With Custom Animations And Moves. Take Him Outside Of Your Apartment As A Companion Or Place Him On Display In Your Apartment In His Peep-a-Boo Box. Collect Them All And Stack Them For All To See! This Set Includes The Following Items. ・Techno Peep - Glowing Green ・Techno Peep - Static Mini - Glowing Green ・Techno Peep - Heavy Pet - Glowing Green ※ All Of The Above Items Will Become Available In Their Relevant Categories On Purchasing This Bundle.|Companion_Bundle|Heavy Water|HDK_1.66.0.144.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
5A22DE31-5B9D45A1-8099AD6E-BAE23F7C|kName|kDesc|Dull-eyed Chick 6 Color Set|Dull-eyed Chick. This 6 Color Set Includes Yellow, Orange, Green, Blue, Purple, And Pink. This Set Includes The Following Items Chick With Dull Eyes (yellow)/portable Item Chick With Dull Eyes (pink)/portable Item Chick With Dull Eyes (blue)/portable Item Chick With Dull Eyes (green)/portable Item Chick With Dull Eyes (orange)/portable Item Chick With Dull Eyes (purple)/portable Item Chick With Dull Eyes (purple)/portable Item When Purchased, Each Item Will Be Added To The Corresponding Category.|Companion_Bundle|Granzella Inc.|HDK_1.65.0.139.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
5A28C58F-E1AF496B-99DEF052-5173CFFD|title|description|Sample Set Object|This Set Contains Below Items For Customizing Your Avatar.*NARISOKONAI T-shirt (Cornet/Women) (Torso)*NARISOKONAI T-shirt (Peter/Women) (Torso)*NARISOKONAI T-shirt (Pudding/Women) (Torso)*NARISOKONAI T-shirt (Bread/Women) (Torso)*NARISOKONAI T-shirt (Panini/Women) (Torso)The Items Will Be Added Under The Category Of Wardrobe After Purchasing.|Companion_Bundle|IREM SOFTWARE ENGINEERING INC.|HDK_XX|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
5B22B663-30644746-8B7E9C98-A709E6B7|kName|kDesc|Thanksgiving - Bundle|Thanksgiving - Bundle This Bundle Contains: (1) Animal Avatars - Thanksgiving - Turkey (2) Riding Turkey (3) The Autumn Wind (4) Turkey Companion (5) Thanksgiving Dining Table - Refined - 10 Person (6) Pilgrim Costume - Dress (Women) (7) Pilgrim Costume - Hat (Women) (8) Pilgrim Costume - Shoes (Women) (9) Pilgrim Costume - Hat (Men) (10) Pilgrim Costume - Jacket (Men) (11) Pilgrim Costume - Pants (Men) (12) Pilgrim Costume - Shoes (Men)|Companion_Bundle|VEEMEE|HDK_1.82.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
5C3C0681-A8094FA8-AE044FD7-5176AE4D|kName|kDesc|Spotted Jack Pack|This Package Includes Spotted Jack, One Of Our Cute Dog Companions, And An Additional Dog House! Now You Can Keep Your Companions Nice And Dry!|Companion_Bundle|Codeglue B.V.|HDK_1.52.0.2.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
5D9FCCB7-DAE94E40-A7AEBEE7-7F06D759|kName|kDesc|Hatchlings - Baby Bundle|Recently Hatched; These Little Babies Are Looking For Attention. Bring Out The Parent In You And Raises These Little Baby Hatchlings. This Bundle Contains: (1) Hatchlings - Baby Raptors (2) Hatchlings - Baby Chickens (3) Hatchlings - Baby Penguins ※These Items Are Portable Items.|Companion_Bundle|VEEMEE|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
5E9FCD1A-450E492A-B8EA03CE-DEEE996F|kName|kDesc|Four Pointy-headed Companions Bundle|Contains Four Companions: Four Eyes, Three Eyes, Five Eyes And Cyclops.|Companion_Bundle|Atom Republic|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
6446B0BE-F6534105-B162422E-34131043|kName|kDesc|Springtime Adventure Pack|Get The Springtime Spirit With This Bundle Of Active Items And Furnishings. Bundle Includes: • Bunny Companion • Easter Bunny Companion • Jackalope Companion • Egg Hunt • Bunny Den • Cascarones • Easter Basket • Swing Set • Bird Perch • Bird's Nest • Carousel • Spring Bouquet • Flower Bed - Round • Flower Bed - Square • Flower Bed - Rectangle • Flower Rug|Companion_Bundle|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
64845070-4DA74B49-BF0F773A-009E78FA|kName|kDesc|Scribble Shooter Companion Special Bundle|It's The Scribble Shooter Companion Special Bundle! This Bundle Includes The Scribble Shooter Ship Companion And Scribble Shooter Wizard Boss Companion. **IMPORTANT NOTICE** This Scribble Shooter Companion Special Bundle May Contain The Items You Have Already Purchased. Only The Item Which Is Not Yet Purchased Is Added To Your Inventory And Same Purchased Item Will Not Appear In The Inventory Twice. Purchased Special Bundles Are Not Refundable, Transferable Or Exchangeable, And Cannot Be Redeemed For Cash Or Credit. [|Companion_Bundle|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.55.0.155.BETA2|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
64FB70C9-C6A94CD3-BEEC03DC-E57881EF|kName|kDesc|Sweetie Peep - Bundle Pack - Vavoom Violet|Sweetie Pie Will Melt Your Heart As Your Favorite New Peep! It's Three For One With Extra Peep Fun! Bring Your Heavy Pet Peep Into Your Apartment And Let The Fun Begin. You Can Control Your Peep With Custom Animations And Moves. Take Her Outside Of Your Apartment As A Companion Or Place Her On Display In Your Apartment In His Peep-a-Boo Box. Collect Them All And Stack Them For All To See! This Set Includes The Following Items. ・Sweetie Peep - Vavoom Violet ・Sweetie Peep - Static Mini - Vavoom Violet ・Sweetie Peep - Heavy Pet - Vavoom Violet ※ All Of The Above Items Will Become Available In Their Relevant Categories On Purchasing This Bundle.|Companion_Bundle|Heavy Water|HDK_1.66.0.144.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
685F69DE-057942D6-AABF6C80-14B9379E|kName|kDesc|Sugar And Spice Peep Pack 2|The Sweetest Of The Peeps Packaged Together For The Sugar And Spice Peep Pack. Sweetie Peep, Lil' Snow Peep And Sunshine Peep Come Packaged As Heavy Pets, Companions And Mini-Peeps! Nine Fantastic Treats In One Big Bundle! Colors As Shown. This Set Includes The Following Items. ・Sweetie Peep - Vavoom Violet ・Sweetie Peep - Static Mini - Vavoom Violet ・Sweetie Peep - Heavy Pet - Vavoom Violet ・Lil' Snow Peep - Powder Pink ・Lil' Snow Peep - Static Mini - Powder Pink ・Lil' Snow Peep - Heavy Pet - Powder Pink ・Sunshine Peep - Summer Rain ・Sunshine Peep - Static Mini - Summer Rain ・Sunshine Peep - Heavy Pet - Summer Rain ※ All Of The Above Items Will Become Available In Their Relevant Categories On Purchasing This Bundle.|Companion_Bundle|Heavy Water|HDK_1.66.0.144.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
69E8E892-FA92421F-8CB75EA0-3D71371C|kName|kDesc|Sunshine Peep - Bundle Pack - Blue Skies|Let The Sunshine In With Warm Rays Of Sunshine Peep! It's Three For One With Extra Peep Fun! Bring Your Peep Into Your Apartment And Let The Fun Begin. You Can Control You Peep With Custom Animations And Moves. Take Her Outside Of Your Apartment As A Companion Or Place Her On Display In Your Apartment In His Peep-a-Boo Box. Collect Them All And Stack Them For All To See! This Set Includes The Following Items. ・Sunshine Peep - Blue Skies ・Sunshine Peep - Static Mini - Blue Skies ・Sunshine Peep - Heavy Pet - Blue Skies ※ All Of The Above Items Will Become Available In Their Relevant Categories On Purchasing This Bundle.|Companion_Bundle|Heavy Water|HDK_1.66.0.144.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
6D1F4F20-20BE42EB-9A7B551D-D028BD27|kName|kDesc|Four Flying Penguin Companions Bundle|Contains Four Companions: Fez, Pengo, Snowflake And Pengy.|Companion_Bundle|MakerXX|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
7127AAB0-C7584D52-B966DC24-CAF53FF7|kName|kDesc|Super Powered Peep - Bundle Pack - Bolting Blue|Super Powered Peep Is Fueled By Heavy Water For All Of His Mad Skills! It's Three For One With Extra Peep Fun! Bring Your Peep Into Your Apartment And Let The Fun Begin. You Can Control You Peep With Custom Animations And Moves. Take Him Outside Of Your Apartment As A Companion Or Place Him On Display In Your Apartment In His Peep-a-Boo Box. Collect Them All And Stack Them For All To See! This Set Includes The Following Items. ・Super Powered Peep - Bolting Blue ・Super Powered Peep - Static Mini - Bolting Blue ・Super Powered Peep - Heavy Pet - Bolting Blue ※ All Of The Above Items Will Become Available In Their Relevant Categories On Purchasing This Bundle.|Companion_Bundle|Heavy Water|HDK_1.66.0.144.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
72F46E2B-209A4D76-B55321F3-7AD74A5D|kName|kDesc|Baby Pet Companion Bundle|Enjoy The Company Of These Pets As They Follow You Around. Bundle Includes These Loveable Companions: A Boston Terrier, Bulldog, Chihuahua, Golden Retriever, Mastiff, Doberman, And A Robotic Cat.|Companion_Bundle|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.55.0.155.BETA2|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
7963A5E0-5D2F424C-905BFD1D-E6334A83|kName|kDesc|Mega Tiger Companions Bundle|Let These Exotic Tigers Roam Around Your Own Personal Space. This Bundle Comes With Tiger Cubs And Adult Tigers, Both Of Which Are Adorable And Ferocious.|Companion_Bundle|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.55.0.155.BETA2|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
7E02C5D1-68654E5F-A2180843-3AB92298|kName|kDesc|Creepy Peep - Bundle Pack - Monster Green|Creepy Peep Is A Playful Little Monster Who Wants To Be Your Friend! It's Three For One With Extra Peep Fun! Bring Your Peep Into Your Apartment And Let The Fun Begin. You Can Control You Peep With Custom Animations And Moves. Take Him Outside Of Your Apartment As A Companion Or Place Him On Display In Your Apartment In His Peep-a-Boo Box. Collect Them All And Stack Them For All To See! This Set Includes The Following Items. ・Creepy Peep - Monster Green ・Creepy Peep - Static Mini - Monster Green ・Creepy Peep - Heavy Pet - Monster Green ※ All Of The Above Items Will Become Available In Their Relevant Categories On Purchasing This Bundle.|Companion_Bundle|Heavy Water|HDK_1.66.0.144.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
7EAB4545-FD1A49D2-95865793-F41A3F1F|kName|kDesc|Super Peep Bonus Bundle 2 (30 Items In All!)|Pump Up The Peeps With This Super Peep Bonus Bundle Pack, Containing All 30 Peeps! Ten (10) Heavy Pet Peeps To Bring Into Your Apartment And Let The Fun Begin. You Can Control Your Peep With Custom Animations And Moves. Ten (10) Companion Peeps To Take Outside Of Your Apartment As A Companion And Ten (10) Mini-Peeps To Display In Your Apartment, Each In It's Own Peep-a-Boo Box. Stack Them For All To See! Colors As Shown. This Set Includes The Following Items. ・Chim Peep - Red On White ・Chim Peep - Static Mini - Red On White ・Chim Peep - Heavy Pet - Red On White ・Techno Peep - Robot Red ・Techno Peep - Static Mini - Robot Red ・Techno Peep - Heavy Pet - Robot Red ・Super Powered Peep - Bolting Blue ・Super Powered Peep - Static Mini - Bolting Blue ・Super Powered Peep - Heavy Pet - Bolting Blue ・Up-Chuck - Pasty White ・Up-Chuck Peep - Static Mini - Pasty White ・Up-Chuck - Heavy Pet - Pasty White ・What The Bleep Peep - Blazing Blue ・What The Bleep Peep - Static Mini - Blazing Blue ・What The Bleep Peep - Heavy Pet - Blazing Blue ・Scary Fairy Peep - Rotten Redhead ・Scary Fairy Peep - Static Mini - Rotten Redhead ・Scary Fairy Peep - Heavy Pet - Rotten Redhead ・Sweetie Peep - Vavoom Violet ・Sweetie Peep - Static Mini - Vavoom Violet ・Sweetie Peep - Heavy Pet - Vavoom Violet ・Lil' Snow Peep - Powder Pink ・Lil' Snow Peep - Static Mini - Powder Pink ・Lil' Snow Peep - Heavy Pet - Powder Pink ・Sunshine Peep - Summer Rain ・Sunshine Peep - Static Mini - Summer Rain ・Sunshine Peep - Heavy Pet - Summer Rain ・Creepy Peep - Orphan Orange ・Creepy Peep - Static Mini - Orphan Orange ・Creepy Peep - Heavy Pet - Orphan Orange ※ All Of The Above Items Will Become Available In Their Relevant Categories On Purchasing This Bundle.|Companion_Bundle|Heavy Water|HDK_1.66.0.144.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
7EF5355A-510F4854-A0005B01-78BAF73F|kName|kDesc|HGL Creature Costume & Companion Bundle - Undead|Now You Can Look Like Your Favourite HGL Creature. Braaaaaains…! This Bundle Includes: (1) HGL Creature Costume - Undead (Male) (2) HGL Creature Costume - Undead (Female) (3) HGL Mini-Creature Companion - Undead Purchasing This Item Grants You 60 Fights In HGL.|Companion_Bundle|VEEMEE|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
82FF5FD7-02CD4506-92FDD5C7-1A446E3E|kName|kDesc|Baby Tiger Companions Bundle|This Bundle Includes The Original White Tiger Companion And Additional Black And Orange Tiger Cubs. Thats Three Tigers To Have Roaming Around Your Apartment!|Companion_Bundle|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.55.0.155.BETA2|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
85CF623F-1E864DB9-951CAAAA-3C0EE588|kName|kDesc|What The Bleep Peep - Bundle Pack - Bone White|What The Bleep Peep Is Bad To The Bone! This Naughty Little Peep Brings Three For One With Extra Peep Fun! Bring Your Peep Into Your Apartment And Let The Fun Begin. You Can Control You Peep With Custom Animations And Moves. Take Him Outside Of Your Apartment As A Companion Or Place Him On Display In Your Apartment In His Peep-a-Boo Box. Collect Them All And Stack Them For All To See! This Set Includes The Following Items. ・What The Bleep Peep - Bone White ・What The Bleep Peep - Static Mini - Bone White ・What The Bleep Peep - Heavy Pet - Bone White ※ All Of The Above Items Will Become Available In Their Relevant Categories On Purchasing This Bundle.|Companion_Bundle|Heavy Water|HDK_1.66.0.144.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
85EC3346-8C8D42C8-852D08CE-D0A63ADE|kName|kDesc|Forsaken Planet – Companion Bundle|Travel PlayStation®Home With Your Favorite Companions From Forsaken Planet, A LOOT™ Entertainment Videogame For Tablets And Smart Phones!  This Bundle Comes With All Five Forsaken Planet Companions: Pimento, Camel, Raccoon, Zombie And Cow! When You Purchase This Forsaken Planet – Companion Bundle, You Unlock A Character And Character Hat* For Use In The Forsaken Planet Game. This Character And Hat Can Only Be Unlocked In PlayStation®Home! To Retrieve Your Rewards, Create Or Access Your LOOT™ Entertainment Account At The Log-in Station Located At The Forsaken Planet Globe Logo In The LOOT Space Station Hub. Looking For Even Sweeter Forsaken Planet Deals And In-game Rewards? Check Out The Forsaken Planet Ultimate Bundle In The LOOT™ Store! (*Character And Character Hat Unlock Specialized Gameplay Perks Within The Forsaken Planet Videogame!)|Companion_Bundle|© LOOT™|HDK_1.66.0.144.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
87345A11-039D4D5D-85D7118C-E74A181D|kName|kDesc|B Movie Madness - Mad Scientist - Bundle - Women|Join The B Movie Madness With This Mad Scientist Costume. This Bundle Contains: (1) B Movie Madness - Mad Scientist - Feet - Women (2) B Movie Madness - Mad Scientist - Hands - Women (3) B Movie Madness - Mad Scientist - Head - Women (4) B Movie Madness - Mad Scientist - Legs - Women (5) B Movie Madness - Mad Scientist - Torso - Women (6) B Movie Madness - Mad Scientist - Companion - Igor ※Upon Purchase, The Items Will Be Placed Into Their Respective Categories.|Companion_Bundle|VEEMEE|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
878D05D5-B0EE44CD-9DEB143D-7E0E83C6|kName|kDesc|Up-Chuck - Bundle Pack - Pasty White|Up-Chuck Is One Wild And Crazy Guy And The Life Of Every Party! It's Three For One With Extra Peep Fun! Bring Your Heavy Pet Peep Into Your Apartment And Let The Fun Begin. You Can Control Your Peep With Custom Animations And Moves. Take Him Outside Of Your Apartment As A Companion Or Place Him On Display In Your Apartment In His Peep-a-Boo Box. Collect Them All And Stack Them For All To See! This Set Includes The Following Items. ・Up-Chuck - Pasty White ・Up-Chuck Peep - Static Mini - Pasty White ・Up-Chuck - Heavy Pet - Pasty White ※ All Of The Above Items Will Become Available In Their Relevant Categories On Purchasing This Bundle.|Companion_Bundle|Heavy Water|HDK_1.66.0.144.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
891CA38D-7790410F-B842B98B-D7D63528|kName|kDesc|MiniBot: Battlebox Gadget Bundle|Maximize Your MiniBots Experience! This Bundle Contains Male And Female Versions Of The Rocket Boots Clothing Item, The Pulse Field Chair, Teleport Beacon, And Stealth Sofa Furniture Items And The Turret And Sentry Companions. BONUS: Unlocks The Following Gadgets For Use In MiniBots: Battlebox And MiniBots Multiplayer: Rocket Boots, Deployable Turret, Sentry Companion, Pulse Field, Teleport Beacon, And Stealth Field.|Companion_Bundle|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.65.0.139.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
8C635D67-D4984A08-81A973B0-021B7D06|kName|kDesc|Plush Ponies: Large Companions Bundle|Get All Three Large Plush Pony Companions In One Great Value Bundle. This Bundle Includes: * Plush Ponies: Rainbow (Large Companion) * Plush Ponies: Candy Floss (Large Companion) * Plush Ponies: Liquorish (Large Companion) These Are Portable Items ※ Upon Purchase, All Items Will Be Added To Their Corresponding Categories.|Companion_Bundle|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
8ED26ED3-9F314BAA-94E9E0F3-0D3D611C|kName|kDesc|Scary Fairy Peep - Bundle Pack - Rotten Redhead|Scary Fairy Is One Twisted Sister Peep! It's Three For One With Extra Peep Fun! Bring Your Heavy Pet Peep Into Your Apartment And Let The Fun Begin. You Can Control Your Peep With Custom Animations And Moves. Take Her Outside Of Your Apartment As A Companion Or Place Her On Display In Your Apartment In A Peep-a-Boo Box. Collect Them All And Stack Them For All To See! This Set Includes The Following Items. ・Scary Fairy Peep - Rotten Redhead ・Scary Fairy Peep - Static Mini - Rotten Redhead ・Scary Fairy Peep - Heavy Pet - Rotten Redhead ※ All Of The Above Items Will Become Available In Their Relevant Categories On Purchasing This Bundle.|Companion_Bundle|Heavy Water|HDK_1.66.0.144.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
907F200A-D4E34BD5-AD284728-088F9A0B|kName|kDesc|Street Moves Vol 2 Bundle|Here You Can Find The Street Moves Characters And Musical Companion From Volume 2 In One Affordable Bundle. This Bundle Includes. * Broadway Star (Male) * Boogy Boy (Male) * Swingin' Sister (Female) * Embarrassing Dad (Male) * Companion – Headphones ※ Upon Purchase, All Items Will Be Added To Their Corresponding Categories.|Companion_Bundle|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
9093DC05-0DA14516-8573C3C1-460DF282|kName|kDesc|Bramblenook Barnyard Bundle|The Perfect Bundle For The Animal Lover! Bundle Includes: ・Pigsty ・Chicken Coop ・Sheepfold ・Chick Companion ・Piglet Companion ・Lamb Companion ・Chicken Companion ・Pig Companion ・Sheep Companion|Companion_Bundle|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
91840E0E-04D44E64-8477BD98-00D03035|kName|kDesc|Farm Animals Companion Bundle|Includes The Baby Chicken Companion, The Pig Companion, The Sheep Companion, And The Donkey Companion.|Companion_Bundle|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.65.0.139.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
94D4F4CA-29DF4439-BD391130-FE23864B|kName|kDesc|Layla - Brimstone Dancer Bundle|Meet Layla, She'll Be Making You Call Out For Your Mummy! Shes Got Moves That Havent Been Seen For Centuries. Sit And Stare While You Beg For A Wardrobe Malfunction. Put This Full Sized…active Object In Your Personal Space And Show Her Miniature Version Around Home As A Dancing Companion.|Companion_Bundle|Mass Media|HDK_1.50.0.238.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
94F0028B-867E400A-86B75812-11514018|kName|kDesc|English Setter Companion Bundle|An Excellent Country Dog With A Great Nose For Sniffing Out The Most Silent Prey. The English Setter Is A Friend For Life Making For Best Companion For Any Time Or Place. This Bundle Includes: • Molly The English Setter • Rosie The English Setter|Companion_Bundle|Lockwood|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
97F10971-F4AA43FF-87582469-C65EBCEB|kName|kDesc|Lively Cat 3-piece Set|A 3-piece Set Of Calico, Black And Tabby Cats Following After Their Master. This Set Includes The Following Items: - Lively Calico Cat (Portables) - Lively Black Cat (Portables) - Lively Tabby Cat (Portables) * Upon Purchase, Each Item Will Be Added To The Applicable Category.|Companion_Bundle|Granzella Inc.|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
990F5C4F-84754FB4-A42E589C-701049EE|kName|kDesc|Novus Prime Ultimate Value Pack|Unlock The Ultimate Sci-fi Action Collection In PlayStation®Home With Every Piece Of Novus Prime Content Ever Released By Hellfire Games! The Novus Prime Ultimate Value Pack Contains Over 80 Items: Every Fighter Ship, Weapon, Outfit, XP And Nebulon Boost, Mission Expansion, Companion, Paint Job, Game Enhancement, Clothing Item, And Personal Space Available For Novus Prime. Includes: - Officers Quarters Personal Space - Private Hangar Expansion - Power Mech-Suit With Nebulon Magnet (Bundle) - Rogue Mech-Suit (Bundle) - Discobot XT6000 Suit (Male) - Obsidian Bladewalker Suit (Male) - Obsidian Pilot Suit (Male) - Obsidian Blade Ship - Kunai Fighter Ship W/ Helmet (Male & Female) - Codebreaker Ship W/ Helmet (Male & Female) - Midas Reactive Defense System W/ 25% Nebulon Booster (Male & Female) - Nebulon Storage Backpack W/ 10% Nebulon Booster (Male & Female) - Avatar Projection System W/ 5% XP Booster (Male & Female) - Twin Pulse Cannons W/ 5% XP Booster (Male & Female) - Handheld Arc Drill W/ 5% Nebulon Booster (Male & Female) - Disruption Shot Pistols W/ 5% Nebulon Booster (Male & Female) - Ion Stream Power Armor (Male) - Nebulon-Interweave Power Suit (Female) - Tech Goggles W/ Enemy Scanner (Male & Female) - Obsidian Throwing Star (Male & Female) - Radiant Storm Ship Weapon - Electromagnetic Bomb Ship Weapon - Ion Beam Ship Weapon - Ion Blaster Cannons (Male & Female) - Escalation Mission Pack - Obsidian Rune Blades (Male & Female) - Novus Prime Stereo - Novus Prime Concept Art: Blackwing - Novus Prime Concept Art: Blade Lotus - Novus Prime Concept Art: Codebreaker - Novus Prime Concept Art: Gladius - Novus Prime Concept Art: Kunai - Novus Prime Concept Art: Witch Doctor - Novus Prime Concept Art: Adamant - Novus Prime Concept Art: The Kraken - Long-Term Memory Conditioning (300% XP Boost) - Conduit Pilot Gloves (Male & Female) - Mental Conditioning Chamber - Armored Pilots Leggings W/ Deflection Shield (Male & Female) - Bot Spider Companion - DataBot Jr. Companion - Bot Bee Swarm Companion - Mini-Mech Companion - Lil Sis Companion - Mini Gladius Companion - Mini Witch Doctor Companion - Mini Obsidian Blade Companion - Flames Paint Job W/ Helmet (Male & Female) - Tiger Stripes Paint Job W/ Helmet (Male & Female) - Tribal Skulls Paint Job W/ Helmet (Male & Female) - Spacewalk Propulsion Boots (Male & Female) - Zero-Gravity Simulator (Male & Female) - Spacewalk Blaster Pistol (Male & Female) - Turbo Matrix Ship Engines Upgrade|Companion_Bundle|Hellfire Games, Inc.|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
9BF29355-829943BD-BB42DD19-5570CD5A|kName|kDesc|Lively Cat 3-piece Set|A 3-piece Set Of Calico, Black And Tabby Cats Following After Their Master. This Set Includes The Following Items: - Lively Calico Cat (Portables) - Lively Black Cat (Portables) - Lively Tabby Cat (Portables) * Upon Purchase, Each Item Will Be Added To The Applicable Category.|Companion_Bundle|Granzella Inc.|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
A25A56F1-9B0741B1-ADE3B504-C238BEF4|kName|kDesc|3 Spirited-Cat Set|A 3-cat Set Including A Calico, A Black Cat And A Tabby That Follow The Heels Of The Owner. This Set Includes The Following Items. ・Spirited Calico (Portable Item) ・Spirited Black Cat (Portable Item) ・Spirited Tabby (Portable Item) ※Upon Purchase, The Items Will Be Placed In Their Respective Categories.|Companion_Bundle|Granzella Inc.|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
A5CACAB4-00AF44F9-BCA95287-135EEF5E|kName|kDesc|Sugar And Spice Peep Pack|The Sweetest Of The Peeps Packaged Together For The Sugar And Spice Peep Pack. Sweetie Peep, Lil' Snow Peep And Sunshine Peep Come Packaged As Heavy Pets, Companions And Mini-Peeps! Nine Fantastic Treats In One Big Bundle! Colors As Shown. This Set Includes The Following Items. ・Sweetie Peep - Perfect Pink ・Sweetie Peep - Static Mini - Perfect Pink ・Sweetie Peep - Heavy Pet - Perfect Pink ・Lil' Snow Peep - Pampered Purple ・Lil' Snow Peep - Static Mini - Pampered Purple ・Lil' Snow Peep - Heavy Pet - Pampered Purple ・Sunshine Peep - Blue Skies ・Sunshine Peep - Static Mini - Blue Skies ・Sunshine Peep - Heavy Pet - Blue Skies ※ All Of The Above Items Will Become Available In Their Relevant Categories On Purchasing This Bundle.|Companion_Bundle|Heavy Water|HDK_1.66.0.144.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
A73FF06A-D13D4D3C-8264BDDE-82BE8712|kName|kDesc|HGL Creature Costume & Companion Bundle|This Mega Bundle Gives You All The HGL Creature Costumes And All Of The HGL Mini-Creature Companions. This Bundle Includes: (1) HGL Creature Costume - Troops (Male) (2) HGL Creature Costume - Troops (Female) (3) HGL Creature Costume - Critters (Male) (4) HGL Creature Costume - Critters (Female) (5) HGL Creature Costume - Sonics (Male) (6) HGL Creature Costume - Sonics (Female) (7) HGL Creature Costume - Undead (Male) (8) HGL Creature Costume - Undead (Female) (9) HGL Mini-Creature Companion - Troops (10) HGL Mini-Creature Companion - Critters (11) HGL Mini-Creature Companion - Sonics (12) HGL Mini-Creature Companion - Undead Purchasing This Item Grants You 240 Fights In HGL.|Companion_Bundle|VEEMEE|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
B0B8C206-479C4F4A-9BB37F0D-7FBEFD53|kName|kDesc|Apartment Pets: Benjis Bundle|See Your Apartment Come To Life With These Fantastic Free-roaming Pets. For Best Results, Try Combining Them With The Other Apartment Pets Now Available From NDreams. This Bundle Includes: * Apartment Pets: Benjis (Appliance) * Benji (Companion) ※ Upon Purchase, All Items Will Be Added To Their Corresponding Categories.|Companion_Bundle|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
B4D3F614-5F26436C-814ECB21-7E6805C0|kName|kDesc|Brigitte - Brimstone Dancer Bundle|Meet Brigitte, Female Guardian Of Graves. Her Dance Moves Captivate All. Brigitte Will Put A Hex On You Because When She Dances, You Cant Take Your Eyes Off Her. Put This Full Sized…active Object In Your Personal Space And Show Her Miniature Version Around Home As A Dancing Companion.|Companion_Bundle|Mass Media|HDK_1.50.0.238.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
B4D654FE-0F4E45BC-8E71AEB2-0246637E|kName|kDesc|NSanity: Balloonies Bundle (Male)|Literally Become An Air Head With This Bundle Of Comical Balloon Style Heads. This Set Includes: *Ballooney Ash (Male) (Headdress) *Ballooney Pete (Male) (Headdress) *Ballooney Joe (Male) (Headdress) ※Upon Purchase, All Items Will Be Added To Their Corresponding Categories.|Companion_Bundle|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.52.0.2.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
B76937B4-EC794258-9A875508-905BAC07|kName|kDesc|VIP Companions Bundle|Look Like A Real VIP With Those Four Companions: The Valentine Girlfriend, The Valentine Boyfriend, The Butler And The Bodyguard.|Companion_Bundle|Atom Republic|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
BCA920CC-DBAB4A9D-8570FCB5-21810DEA|kName|kDesc|Brown Jack Pack|This Package Includes Brown Jack, One Of Our Cute Dog Companions, And An Additional Dog House! Now You Can Keep Your Companions Nice And Dry!|Companion_Bundle|Codeglue B.V.|HDK_1.52.0.2.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
BDFDC3AF-31ED4155-8804E860-9125B2A7|kName|kDesc|Brimstone Dancer Bundle|This Bundle Includes 3 Brimstone Dancers, 3 Companions And 3 Animated Dance Platforms! Brigitte, Layla And Lilith Will Tantalize You With Their Wicked Ways. These Ladies Are As Dangerous As They Are Beautiful. Put These Full Sized…active Objects In Your Personal Space And Show The Miniature Versions Around Home As Dancing Companions.|Companion_Bundle|Mass Media|HDK_1.50.0.238.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
C0BE3346-E8CD473E-BAF45D60-2840B2C4|kName|kDesc|X7 Bundle Volume 89|Exclusive X7 Value Bundle! Includes: Low Chrome Table Tribal Blade Of Honor (F) Animated Neon Glasses (Female) Animated Rainy Cloud (Male) Infernal Revolver (Male) Grey Hoodie (Male) CAS - Rocket Racks Spotted Cat Companion|Companion_Bundle|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
C40614C2-2FBC4ADE-AB2E2857-41279587|kName|kDesc|Giant Insect - Bundle|Transform Your Avatar Into A Huge Bug With These Giant Insect Locomotion Items. This Locomotion Object Will Boost Your Speed: ・Standard = 5.25 M/s This Bundle Contains: (1) Giant Lady Bird (2) Giant Locust (3) Giant Ant (4) Giant Mantis|Companion_Bundle|VEEMEE|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
C95037AA-92AC4046-9B84404A-8DA2EDB7|kName|kDesc|X7 Bundle Volume 86|Exclusive X7 Value Bundle! Includes: Soul Hunter Mask (Male) Soul Hunter Top (Male) Soul Hunter Bottom (Male) Soul Hunter Shoes (Male) Soul Hunter Gloves (Male) Animated Atomic Hoodie (Male) Helicopter Companion|Companion_Bundle|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
CAFBA347-58694E2F-901BE94D-64010528|kName|kDesc|NDreams Ultimate Horror Bundle|This Is A Must Own Bundle For Any True Horror Fan. It Is Full Of Outfits, Ornaments, Active Items And Companions. This Incredible Value For Money Bundle Contains The Following Items: * Black Party Robe (Male) (Full Body Outfit) * Black Party Robe (Female) (Full Body Outfit) * Epic Black Party Robe (Male) (Full Body Outfit) * Epic Black Party Robe (Female) (Full Body Outfit) * The Bling Reaper (Male) (Full Body Outfit) * The Bling Reaper (Female) (Full Body Outfit) * Skull Mask 1 (Male) (Head) * Skull Mask 2 (Male) (Head) * Skull Mask 3 (Male) (Head) * Skull Mask 1 (Female) (Head) * Skull Mask 2 (Female) (Head) * Skull Mask 3 (Female) (Head) * Benji (Companion) * Nipper (Companion) * Li'l Reaper (Companion) * Lil Bling Reaper (Companion) * Crypt Keeper (White) (Active Item) * Crypt Keeper (Green) (Active Item) * Crypt Keeper (Red) (Active Item) * Candle (Orange) (Ornament) * Candle (Red) (Ornament) * Candle (White) (Ornament) * Portrait Of Lord Patrick (Wall Hanging) * Portrait Of Miss Tamsin Of Hampshire (Wall Hanging) * Dusty Book Shelf (Wall Hanging) * Horror Candelabra 1 (Ornament) * Horror Candelabra 2 (Ornament) * Horror Candelabra 3 (Ornament) * Ghostly Mirror (Ornament) * Horror Headstone 1 (Ornament) * Horror Headstone 2 (Ornament) ※ All Of The Above Items Will Become Available In Their Relevant Categories On Purchasing This Bundle.|Companion_Bundle|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.65.0.139.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
CB0411CF-368545C6-9320132F-543D7309|title|title desc|Sample Set Object|This Set Contains Below Items For Customizing Your Avatar.*NARISOKONAI T-shirt (Cornet/Men) (Torso)*NARISOKONAI T-shirt (Peter/Men) (Torso)*NARISOKONAI T-shirt (Pudding/Men) (Torso)*NARISOKONAI T-shirt (Bread/Men) (Torso)*NARISOKONAI T-shirt (Panini/Men) (Torso)The Items Will Be Added Under The Category Of Wardrobe After Purchasing.|Companion_Bundle|IREM SOFTWARE ENGINEERING INC.|HDK_XX|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
CD601483-6B744627-9C9D0334-2D1EF6E5|kName|kDesc|We Got The Peeps|We Got The Peeps Features A Bundle Of Some Cool Characters. Chim Peep, Techno Peep And Super Powered Peep Come Packaged As Heavy Pets, Companions And Mini-Peeps! Nine Fantastic Treats In One Big Bundle! Colors As Shown. This Set Includes The Following Items. ・Chim Peep - Black On Black ・Chim Peep - Static Mini - Black On Black ・Chim Peep - Heavy Pet - Black On Black ・Techno Peep - Glowing Green ・Techno Peep - Static Mini - Glowing Green ・Techno Peep - Heavy Pet - Glowing Green ・Super Powered Peep - Ricochet Red ・Super Powered Peep - Static Mini - Ricochet Red ・Super Powered Peep - Heavy Pet - Ricochet Red ※ All Of The Above Items Will Become Available In Their Relevant Categories On Purchasing This Bundle.|Companion_Bundle|Heavy Water|HDK_1.66.0.144.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
CFEBBCEF-819249FE-8EC5F5DE-B3DBB654|kName|kDesc|Lil' Snow Peep - Bundle Pack - Powder Pink|Lil' Snow Peep Has Lost Her Sheep And Needs A Friend To Guide Her. It's Three For One With Extra Peep Fun! Bring Your Peep Into Your Apartment And Let The Fun Begin. You Can Control You Peep With Custom Animations And Moves. Take Him Outside Of Your Apartment As A Companion Or Place Him On Display In Your Apartment In His Peep-a-Boo Box. Collect Them All And Stack Them For All To See! This Set Includes The Following Items. ・Lil' Snow Peep - Powder Pink ・Lil' Snow Peep - Static Mini - Powder Pink ・Lil' Snow Peep - Heavy Pet - Powder Pink ※ All Of The Above Items Will Become Available In Their Relevant Categories On Purchasing This Bundle.|Companion_Bundle|Heavy Water|HDK_1.66.0.144.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
D5FADB62-50FC43E7-B34D0AB3-7DA3C574|kName|kDesc|B Movie Madness - Mad Scientist - Bundle - Men|Join The B Movie Madness With This Mad Scientist Costume. This Bundle Contains: (1) B Movie Madness - Mad Scientist - Feet - Men (2) B Movie Madness - Mad Scientist - Hands - Men (3) B Movie Madness - Mad Scientist - Head - Men (4) B Movie Madness - Mad Scientist - Legs - Men (5) B Movie Madness - Mad Scientist - Torso - Men (6) B Movie Madness - Mad Scientist - Companion - Igor ※Upon Purchase, The Items Will Be Placed Into Their Respective Categories.|Companion_Bundle|VEEMEE|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
D6E8B9E2-F873439E-A1D245AE-19DD95DC|kName|kDesc|X7 Bundle Volume 80|Exclusive X7 Value Bundle! Includes: Butterfly Dress Butterfly Girl Hair Enchanted Bow Of Mastery Frizzy Hairstyle Mini Yeti Companion Rainbow Bean Bag Chair Japanese Bonsai Tree|Companion_Bundle|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
D91167CC-71E14DE9-BEF591C6-3AC423FD|kName|kDesc|Street Moves Vol 4 Bundle|Here You Can Find The Street Moves Characters And Musical Companion From Volume 4 In One Affordable Bundle. This Bundle Includes. * 80's Icon (Female) * Dancing Diva (Female) * Rebel Raver (Female) * Clubwear Cutie (Female) * Companion - Speaker ※ Upon Purchase, All Items Will Be Added To Their Corresponding Categories.|Companion_Bundle|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
DEFC69E3-B91E4AA0-9504B7FE-61AD5CB9|kName|kDesc|American Wildlife Companions Pack|American Wildlife Companions Pack This Pack Includes The Following: • Bartholomew The Bear Cub • Wulfred The Wolf • Sammy The Skunk A Collection Of Wildlife That Will Turn Your Apartment Into An All-American Conservation Park!|Companion_Bundle|Lockwood|HDK_1.60.0.450.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
E0D68097-35A443A1-BEF1CE80-FED40C11|kName|kDesc|Ugly Animals - Bundle|The World's Ugliest Animals, Or The Cutest? You Decide. Either Way, They Want To Be Your Friend. This Bundle Contains: (1) Ugly Animals - Aye-aye (2) Ugly Animals - Blobfish (3) Ugly Animals - California Condor (4) Ugly Animals - Naked Mole Rat (5) Ugly Animals - Proboscis Monkey (6) Ugly Animals - Star-nosed Mole|Companion_Bundle|VEEMEE|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
E2F2D783-51544D59-85C6943A-F431498D|kName|kDesc|Storm Of The North - Direwolves - Bundle|Be Part Of The Pack With This Direwolves Bundle. This Bundle Contains: (1) Storm Of The North - Direwolf Companion - White (2) Storm Of The North - Direwolf Companion - Grey (3) Storm Of The North - Direwolf Companion - Copper (4) Storm Of The North - Direwolf Companion - Scarface|Companion_Bundle|VEEMEE|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
ECAAC630-323346C2-827BA88B-AF2C2615|kName|kDesc|Cinco De Mayo Adventure Pack|The Perfect Bundle For A Cinco De Mayo Fiesta! Bundle Contains: Mariachi Hat (Male), Mariachi Jacket (Male), Mariachi Trousers (Male), Mariachi Boots (Male), Maracas (Male), Mariachi Hat (Female), Mariachi Jacket (Female), Mariachi Trousers (Female), Mariachi Boots (Female), Maracas (Female), Mariachi Meercat Companion, El Mojo Companion, Cactusizer, Piñata, Chimenea, Tumbleweeds, Mariachi Meercats.|Companion_Bundle|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
EE90835C-45A3402E-86A99C27-388B0572|kName|kDesc|Street Moves Vol 1 Bundle|Here You Can Find The Street Moves Characters And Musical Companion From Volume 1 In One Affordable Bundle. This Bundle Includes. * BGirl (Female) * BBoy (Male) * HipHop Hero (Male) * HipHop Honey (Female) * Street Moves Companion Stereo ※ Upon Purchase, All Items Will Be Added To Their Corresponding Categories.|Companion_Bundle|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
F4A69755-91E84811-9C01DF8C-6B460879|kName|kDesc|Sweetie Peep - Bundle Pack - Perfect Pink|Sweetie Piewill Melt Your Heart As Your Favorite New Peep! It's Three For One With Extra Peep Fun! Bring Your Heavy Pet Peep Into Your Apartment And Let The Fun Begin. You Can Control Your Peep With Custom Animations And Moves. Take Her Outside Of Your Apartment As A Companion Or Place Her On Display In Your Apartment In His Peep-a-Boo Box. Collect Them All And Stack Them For All To See! This Set Includes The Following Items. ・Sweetie Peep - Perfect Pink ・Sweetie Peep - Static Mini - Perfect Pink ・Sweetie Peep - Heavy Pet - Perfect Pink ※ All Of The Above Items Will Become Available In Their Relevant Categories On Purchasing This Bundle.|Companion_Bundle|Heavy Water|HDK_1.66.0.144.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
FB911369-09EF4D50-A22E5EB8-949346CB|kName|kDesc|Juggernaut Nautilus Adventure Pack|Join The Adventure With This Collection Of Nautilus Inspired Clothing And Furniture. Bundle Includes: •Sea Captain Jacket (Blue) •Sea Captain Jacket (Black) •Sea Captain Pants (Tan) •Sea Captain Pants (Black) •Sea Captain Boots •Sea Captain Hat (Blue) •Sea Captain Hat (Black) •Nautilus Ring •Sea Nymph Top (Blue) •Sea Nymph Top (Violet) •Sea Nymph Skirt (Blue) •Sea Nymph Skirt (Violet) •Sea Anemone Hair Accessory •Sea Nymph Rings (Blue) •Sea Nymph Rings (Violet) •Sea Nymph Sandals (Blue) •Sea Nymph Sandals (Violet) •Nautilus Shell Table •Nautilus Shell Lamp •Porthole Wall Hanging •Aquarium Table •Nautilus Chair •Sea Captain's Chair •Bubble Fissure •Coral Reef Sofa •Lanternfish Castle •Clamshell Chair •Bioluminescent Kelp •Bubbly Submarine Companion •Fredrick Von Copperbottom Companion.|Companion_Bundle|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
FC06A1FA-6E084E68-A86B8C4F-42AB36EB|kName|kDesc|Age Of Swords - Mega Bundle|All Of The Age Of Swords Outfits. This Bundle Contains: ・17x Male Clothing Items. ・8x Female Clothing Items. ・21x Furniture Items. ・1x Companion Item. This Bundle Contains: (1) Age Of Swords - Northern King - Outfit Bundle (2) Age Of Swords - Northern Queen - Outfit Bundle (3) Age Of Swords - Northern Princess - Outfit Bundle (4) Age Of Swords - Knight - Outfit Bundle (5) Age Of Swords - Man At Arms - Outfit Bundle (6) Age Of Swords - Druid - Outfit Bundle (7) Age Of Swords - Banquet - Bundle (8) Age Of Swords - Throne - Bundle (9) Age Of Swords - Library - Lectern (10) Age Of Swords - Companion - Wolfhound|Companion_Bundle|VEEMEE|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
FCE33355-91F5442E-A0E66403-44B2E03F|kName|kDesc|X7 Bundle Volume 88|Exclusive X7 Value Bundle! Includes:Mini Hunter Companion Aqua Aura (M) Overstuffed Down Vest (M) Gatling Gun Arm (M) Forever Plaid (M) Inflatable Football Couch Sweet Treats Furniture - Cotton Candy Rug|Companion_Bundle|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
FD41FE4E-39FB4936-A4D9B8FE-3A95FD7B|kName|kDesc|Super Powered Peep - Bundle Pack - Ricochet Red|Super Powered Peep Is Fueled By Heavy Water For All Of His Mad Skills! It's Three For One With Extra Peep Fun! Bring Your Peep Into Your Apartment And Let The Fun Begin. You Can Control You Peep With Custom Animations And Moves. Take Him Outside Of Your Apartment As A Companion Or Place Him On Display In Your Apartment In His Peep-a-Boo Box. Collect Them All And Stack Them For All To See! This Set Includes The Following Items. ・Super Powered Peep - Ricochet Red ・Super Powered Peep - Static Mini - Ricochet Red ・Super Powered Peep - Heavy Pet - Ricochet Red ※ All Of The Above Items Will Become Available In Their Relevant Categories On Purchasing This Bundle.|Companion_Bundle|Heavy Water|HDK_1.66.0.144.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
FF27C8E6-A12A4AD2-81DC1DA7-CE1D61CD|kName|kDesc|Scary Fairy Peep - Bundle Pack - Persnickety Purple|Scary Fairy Is One Twisted Sister Peep! It's Three For One With Extra Peep Fun! Bring Your Heavy Pet Peep Into Your Apartment And Let The Fun Begin. You Can Control Your Peep With Custom Animations And Moves. Take Her Outside Of Your Apartment As A Companion Or Place Her On Display In Your Apartment In A Peep-a-Boo Box. Collect Them All And Stack Them For All To See! This Set Includes The Following Items. ・Scary Fairy Peep - Persnickety Purple ・Scary Fairy Peep - Static Mini - Persnickety Purple ・Scary Fairy Peep - Heavy Pet - Persnickety Purple ※ All Of The Above Items Will Become Available In Their Relevant Categories On Purchasing This Bundle.|Companion_Bundle|Heavy Water|HDK_1.66.0.144.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
