0070C3F1-C5BB48FD-8B971296-0307705E|kName|kDesc|Spunland Seeds|Whenever You Visit Spunland You Will Always Start With 3 Seeds!|Consumable|Madmunki|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|AUTO-REWARD|Res:0
00D5EB51-49014907-8A178A00-BCCB5C57|kName|kDesc|Xi: Continuum - Buff Pack (250)|Give Your Associates A Temporary Boost Of Power And Gain The Upper Hand In The Xi: Continuum Combat Game. This Pack Contains 250 Consumable Buffs. These Buffs Are Only For Use In The Xi: Continuum Combat Game. Note - This Is A Consumable Item.|Consumable|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
023F207A-BD994DEE-AA4B4D66-9E389D81|kName|kDesc|Xi: Continuum - Associate Pack 10|Add More Grunt, Guile And Guns To Your Crew With These 5 Random Associates For The Xi: Continuum Combat Game. 5 Associates That You Do Not Currently Own Will Be Chosen At Random. These Associates Are Only For Use In The Xi: Continuum Combat Game. Note - On Buying All 16 Associate Packs You Are Guaranteed To Unlock All 80 Purchasable Associates.|Consumable|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
04BFCBAA-59C0485B-8EAB9F8C-63C65832|kName|kDesc|Xi: Continuum - Associate Pack 1|Add More Grunt, Guile And Guns To Your Crew With These 5 Random Associates For The Xi: Continuum Combat Game. 5 Associates That You Do Not Currently Own Will Be Chosen At Random. These Associates Are Only For Use In The Xi: Continuum Combat Game. Note - On Buying All 16 Associate Packs You Are Guaranteed To Unlock All 80 Purchasable Associates.|Consumable|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
066E7127-21CF45FD-9010A87E-200B5E8A|kName|kDesc|GZ Tickets (240)|A Strand Of 240 Tickets That Allow For Use Of Special Services In The Various Granzella Lounges.|Consumable|Granzella Inc.|HDK_1.82.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
0689BD6B-52DD440E-84C27863-12B59112|kName|kDesc|GZ Tickets (30)|A Strand Of 30 Tickets That Allow For Use Of Special Services In The Various Granzella Lounges.|Consumable|Granzella Inc.|HDK_1.65.0.139.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
06B86A70-034E4C25-8DD78D26-D255DD38|kName|kDesc|Uproar Credits - 2,620|Uproar Credits Allow You To Purchase, Rent And Gift Weapons, Serums, Clothing Items And Taunts In Uproar - The Fast Paced, Action Packed Third-person Shooter, Exclusive To PlayStation®Home. This Pack Contains: 2221 Uproar Credits + 399 Bonus Uproar Credits Get More Bonus Credits When You Purchase Larger Packs And Take Full Advantage Of The Game's Extensive Customisation Options!|Consumable|Lockwood|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
06C8437A-1E53412A-A6ACABC0-48695707|kName|kDesc|Diamond Beach Infinity Pool|Add A Private Pool And Strech Of Beach To Your Modern Beach Mansion Complete With Rockwaterfall And Cabanas. Go Swimming In The Pool With Custom Swim Animations, Lounge In The Sun Or Wade Into The Ocean And Enjoy The Scenery. Did We Mention The Awesome Rock Waterfall?! Bring Your Friends Over To Swim And Gift Them With Exclusive Freebies: Golden Bikini, Golden Swim Trunks, Golden Beach Blanket, Golden Umbrella And Golden Ice Chest.|Consumable|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.60.0.450.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
06E23C61-887D4319-8E2E8B44-98F01804|kName|kDesc|GZ Tickets (30)|A Strand Of 30 Tickets That Allow For Use Of Special Services In The Various Granzella Lounges.|Consumable|Granzella Inc.|HDK_1.65.0.139.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
0706DB2B-B0494BA1-ADDEC48A-6D8EE292|kName|kDesc|GZ Ticket (30 Tickets)|These 30 Tickets Bring You Special Discounts In Various Granzella Lounges.|Consumable|Granzella Inc.|HDK_1.65.0.139.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
07541DAB-28924A4E-854E3606-0158C1AF|kName|kDesc|GZ Tickets (60)|A Strand Of 60 Tickets That Allow For Use Of Special Services In The Various Granzella Lounges.|Consumable|Granzella Inc.|HDK_1.65.0.139.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
07F8BA4E-9FAB4801-9ACEAB83-D4856A49|kName|kDesc|Xi: Continuum - Associate Pack 14|Add More Grunt, Guile And Guns To Your Crew With These 5 Random Associates For The Xi: Continuum Combat Game. 5 Associates That You Do Not Currently Own Will Be Chosen At Random. These Associates Are Only For Use In The Xi: Continuum Combat Game. Note - On Buying All 16 Associate Packs You Are Guaranteed To Unlock All 80 Purchasable Associates.|Consumable|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
08162686-EB694695-8B80DE93-FCC2C015|kName|kDesc|GZ Tickets (60)|A Strand Of 60 Tickets That Allow For Use Of Special Services In The Various Granzella Lounges.|Consumable|Granzella Inc.|HDK_1.65.0.139.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
087C88C2-1EAB4313-81985860-B45E28BE|kName|kDesc|GZ Ticket (60 Tickets)|These 60 Tickets Bring You Special Discounts In Various Granzella Lounges.|Consumable|Granzella Inc.|HDK_1.65.0.139.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
094C6D68-49634716-B746B65C-3BE8074D|kName|kDesc|GZ Tickets (240)|A Strand Of 240 Tickets That Allow For Use Of Special Services In The Various Granzella Lounges.|Consumable|Granzella Inc.|HDK_1.82.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
09594404-641640D1-AA848BAF-83485B18|kName|kDesc|3,600 Giftinator Bucks|Get A +44% Bonus Instantly With This Pack Of 3,600 Giftinator Bucks To Use With The Giftinator 9000 From Hellfire Games. Redeem To Gift Exclusive Items To Friends (and Yourself!) And Earn Karma Bonuses With Each Transaction!|Consumable|Hellfire Games, Inc.|HDK_1.83.0.11.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
0AEA689C-EBEF4A99-9B28DF3B-A0DA8A42|kName|kDesc|Peach|The Wonderful Living Thing Said To Live In Shangri-La Is Drawn Near. 20-piece Set.|Consumable|Will Co.,Ltd.|HDK_1.52.0.2.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
0BCDAB19-93DD4593-AF91EF95-6B887230|title|description|Dueling Red Stones X12|Set Of 12 Mysterious Gemstones That Restore Order Counts For Use With The Peakvox Monster.|Consumable|O-Two Inc.|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
0F758E3C-9C3C4D21-80991302-5125AB00|kName|kDesc|Vortex Attractor (50)|Vortex Attractors Can Be Used In The Aurora Sky Fishing Game To Dramatically Reduce The Waiting Time And Distance Between You And Your Catch, Making It Much Easier To Reel In The Rarer Catches. This Is A Pack Of 50 Vortex Attractors.|Consumable|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.52.0.2.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
106AD49C-16E640BD-B6F99A61-DE35CC27|kName|kDesc|Single Pickaxe|Single Pickaxe|Consumable|Digital Leisure|HDK_1.82.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
1095A584-B34E4612-9C0B23F8-63D5D32C|kName|kDesc|Eggplant|Food Which Draws A Rare Living Thing Near. 15-piece Set.|Consumable|Will Co.,Ltd.|HDK_1.52.0.2.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
10A396E2-19A44985-B6C294D3-FCE869DD|kName|kDesc|Xi: Continuum - Associate Pack 15|Add More Grunt, Guile And Guns To Your Crew With These 5 Random Associates For The Xi: Continuum Combat Game. 5 Associates That You Do Not Currently Own Will Be Chosen At Random. These Associates Are Only For Use In The Xi: Continuum Combat Game. Note - On Buying All 16 Associate Packs You Are Guaranteed To Unlock All 80 Purchasable Associates.|Consumable|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
11F19590-3A734B47-95298565-D29E4673|kName|kDesc|Fantail Goldfish|Fantail Goldfish|Consumable|Digital Leisure|HDK_1.66.0.144.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
1325B0E9-B3994DDF-A95BBF09-38A99F3A|kName|kDesc|GZ Tickets (60 Tickets)|This Is A Series Of 60 Tickets That Entitles You To Special Services At Various Lounges In Granzella.|Consumable|Granzella Inc.|HDK_1.60.0.450.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
142AD815-FCFF4B23-806257B7-7CACE573|kName|kDesc|Treasure: 2700 Coins|2700 Coins To Spend In Cutthroats: Battle For Black Powder Cove's Armoury.|Consumable|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.60.0.450.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
14511AA6-2BBB451D-9C54190C-7EFBC74C|kName|kDesc|Dragons Green Golden Ticket|Purchase The Golden Ticket To Unlock The Full Version Of Dragons Green Permanently.|Consumable|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.40.0.264.BETA4|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
160103FD-919A4FEB-B7D3E01E-F2B9FB91|kName|kDesc|50 Los Penguini Brothers Tickets|Each Los Penguini Brothers Ticket Entitles You To Play The Los Penguini Brothers Aerial Challenge. Jump For Fame And Reward.|Consumable|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.52.0.2.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
163B865E-980D4FF2-BA2373A0-1E0B3478|kName|kDesc|SodiumOne Full Game Rental Ticket - 1 Day|Blast Your Way Through All 50 Levels Of SodiumOne! Youll Receive Full Access To The Most Explosive Shooter In PlayStation®Home For 1 Day From The Time Of Purchase With This Game Rental Ticket.|Consumable|Sodium - Lockwood|HDK_1.41.0.37.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
17A05DC3-DFF343E9-AD5E07CA-47676219|kName|kDesc|OrbRunner: Orb Attractor + 750XP|This Great Piece Of Technology Will Draw All Useful Energy Orbs Towards You, Making It Easier To Collect Orbs In The OrbRunner Mini Game Within Aurora. Note - This Is A Mini Game Upgrade Not An Apartment Item.|Consumable|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
1A4C324D-3D564E7E-91667C14-15A6C95F|title|description|Angel Elixir X30|Set Of 30 Elixirs To Restore Combat Loss For Use With Peakvox Monster.|Consumable|O-Two Inc.|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
1A6153BD-90DE454B-8C53E7B2-31EE58CC|kName|kDesc|2500 ModPoints|Purchase ModPoints For The EmoRay Store. This Particular Consumable Will Give You 2500 ModPoints. When You Enter The EmoRay Store Your ModPoints Will Be Deducted From This Consumable Before Using ModPoints Already Earned Through Gameplay.|Consumable|Heavy Water|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
1A78CEA2-2E8A4283-9540C0F3-F5C9A4EA|kName|kDesc|160 Home Tycoon Gold Coins|Includes 160 Gold Coins To Spend In Home Tycoon. Unlock Premium Buildings And Expansion Packs Containing New Missions, Fun Activities, Stylish Clothing, And More Rewards!|Consumable|Hellfire Games, Inc.|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
1AA4E391-EB9A4560-979E8A79-6F3C761F|kName|kDesc|Charcoal Champ Special Sauce|Season Your Meat To Perfection-- This Special Sauce Will Add All Possible Seasonings To Any Piece Of Meat In Charcoal Champ For Big Bonus Points. 10 Uses In Each Pack.|Consumable|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
1FD4952A-7C454A8A-B9D69794-D76BAAA3|kName|kDesc|F.U.B.A.R. War Bucks (50)|These Are A Special Kind Of Currency For Use In F.U.B.A.R. (Fight Until Blood And Ruin). Use War Bucks To Speed Up Your Progress Through The Game, Purchase Unique Items For Your Base And To Enhance Your Gameplay Experience.|Consumable|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.65.0.139.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
20DFBA47-7F414005-B8532CA0-8DFED8E7|kName|kDesc|Xi: Continuum - Personal Teleport Module|Teleport Easily Around The Continuum From Your Current Location With This Handy Addition To Your Aeropal. This Is A Minigame Upgrade And Will Not Appear In Your Inventory. For Use In Xi: Continuum Only.|Consumable|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
24A3B619-922F435F-88D05844-52A5A279|kName|kDesc|1,600 Home Tycoon Gold Coins With VIP Bonus Items|Includes 1,600 Gold Coins, Exclusive VIP Gold Helicopter, VIP Mayor's Podium With 7 Custom Animations, Gold Car Companion, And Permanently Increases Your Maximum Workers To 60!|Consumable|Hellfire Games, Inc.|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
2603B3BC-BE9543B5-98D99473-1721B46A|title|description|Golden Pocket Watch X3|Points For A Certain Amount Of Time Quest Available On Peakvox Monster A Set Of 3 Pocket Watches That Increase Your Acquisition Friendliness.|Consumable|O-Two Inc.|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
293BDCA4-CEC94CC0-AF0AB94A-2D7D6ABF|kName|kDesc|Cabin Boy In Trout Trouble!|Life On The Open Seas Is Grand! Well, Maybe Not For Our Cabin Boy. Help Our Hero In This Adventure Get Through The Day! Catch The Fish Lil Dickie Throws To Him, Keep Lil Missus From Burning Under The Hot Sun And Whatever You Do, Watch Out For Chairman Meow!! Get To Level 30 And Win A Free Cabin Boy Shirt: Lil Dickie For The Boys, Lil Missus For The Girls! For You Hardcore Gamers Out There, Accumulate 12,000 Points Over Time To Win The Golden Trout Trophy!|Consumable|© 2010 LOOT™|HDK_1.3.6.22.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
2C95440E-1C704360-989E1D5B-6337E1F8|kName|kDesc|500 Acorn Vouchers|A Pack Of 500 Acorn Vouchers For Use In Acorn Meadow Park. Enjoy Any Activity In The Park In Exchange For Acorn Vouchers. The Larger The Pack Of Vouchers, The Better The Value.|Consumable|VEEMEE|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
2DAA4874-5F224636-AC033B9D-9239A765|kName|kDesc|F.U.B.A.R. War Bucks (250)|These Are A Special Kind Of Currency For Use In F.U.B.A.R. (Fight Until Blood And Ruin). Use War Bucks To Speed Up Your Progress Through The Game, Purchase Unique Items For Your Base And To Enhance Your Gameplay Experience.|Consumable|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.65.0.139.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
2EBBEABE-455B4866-A96E8FB4-F0EBBC98|kName|kDesc|Arcade GAME Tokens - 50 Plays|Each Of These 50 GAME Tokens Gives You One Play On Any Of Our Public Space Arcade Cabinets. Battle The Alien Hordes In Savage Cosmos Or Become Electrokid And Use Your Special Powers To Defeat The Evil Company. Will You Be Able To Fight Your Way Through The SuperHero Madhouse - Or Will You Lose Your Mind Trying? Our Arcade Games Include High Score Leaderboards, Many Unlockable Medals And Rewards To Show Off To Your Friends. When Your Tokens Are Used Up, You Can Buy As Many More As You Like. You Can Also Purchase The Personal Space Version Of Any Of Our Arcade Games For Use In Any Of Your Apartments!|Consumable|VEEMEE|HDK_1.60.0.450.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
33295A86-C300441B-A4E83EE8-68B07AF8|kName|kDesc|Uproar Credits - 350|Uproar Credits Allow You To Purchase, Rent And Gift Weapons, Serums, Clothing Items And Taunts In Uproar - The Fast Paced, Action Packed Third-person Shooter, Exclusive To PlayStation®Home. This Pack Contains: 332 Uproar Credits + 18 Bonus Uproar Credits Get More Bonus Credits When You Purchase Larger Packs And Take Full Advantage Of The Game's Extensive Customisation Options!|Consumable|Lockwood|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
3462361F-04E34715-844BE31C-0FB4D6D2|kName|kDesc|Xi: Continuum - Associate Pack 3|Add More Grunt, Guile And Guns To Your Crew With These 5 Random Associates For The Xi: Continuum Combat Game. 5 Associates That You Do Not Currently Own Will Be Chosen At Random. These Associates Are Only For Use In The Xi: Continuum Combat Game. Note - On Buying All 16 Associate Packs You Are Guaranteed To Unlock All 80 Purchasable Associates.|Consumable|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
3B3B2CC8-BA394F20-92878500-EB915A8D|kName|kDesc|2000 Aurora XP|Congratulations - You've Just Won A Reward That Gives You A Massive 2000 FREE Aurora XP! This Means You May Already Have Won Some Rewards And Levelled Up! Don't Forget To Visit Aurora!|Consumable|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|AUTO-REWARD|Res:0
3CC77530-CF8243A1-A731E2C7-8E954221|kName|kDesc|1000 VEEMEE 3D Printer Vouchers|A Pack Of 1000 Vouchers For Use With The VEEMEE 3D Printer. Choose From A Varied Selection Of Reward Items To Print In The Comfort Of Your (virtual) Home, Or Use The Vouchers To Send An Item To A Friend's 3D Printer. The Larger The Pack Of Vouchers, The Better The Value.|Consumable|VEEMEE|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
3CE5F061-126E455D-81BE66A9-A5FFE0DD|kName|kDesc|Lockwood Token Pack - 61|Use Lockwood Tokens With The Lockwood Gift Machine To Give Gifts To Your Friends - Pack Of 61.|Consumable|Lockwood|HDK_1.52.0.2.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
3D45C776-5D674C77-AA050D7B-0A2DF449|kName|kDesc|OrbRunner: Time Vortex (20) + 250XP|This Consumable Item Will Make The Clock In OrbRunner Run Down A Lot Slower Than Normal. Note - This Is A Mini Game Upgrade Not An Apartment Item.|Consumable|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
41572A7D-7472434F-A9CC5E74-1C46EC72|kName|kDesc|Lockwood Token Pack - 6240|Use Lockwood Tokens With The Lockwood Gift Machine To Give Gifts To Your Friends - Pack Of 6240.|Consumable|Lockwood|HDK_1.52.0.2.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
41FBFF75-289F4BB3-B6BFFFA1-7B674E5F|kName|kDesc|OrbRunner: Time Vortex (50) + 375XP|This Consumable Item Will Make The Clock In OrbRunner Run Down A Lot Slower Than Normal. Note - This Is A Mini Game Upgrade Not An Apartment Item.|Consumable|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
42C5CB6C-D6D74F47-A214E7ED-34A32A50|kName|kDesc|GZ Ticket (10 Tickets)|These 10 Tickets Bring You Special Discounts In Various Granzella Lounges.|Consumable|Granzella Inc.|HDK_1.65.0.139.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
42D12669-6C0A4135-954D5108-7D95658F|kName|kDesc|1,650 Giftinator Bucks|Get A +32% Bonus Instantly With This Pack Of 1,650 Giftinator Bucks To Use With The Giftinator 9000 From Hellfire Games. Redeem To Gift Exclusive Items To Friends (and Yourself!) And Earn Karma Bonuses With Each Transaction!|Consumable|Hellfire Games, Inc.|HDK_1.83.0.11.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
43A1AEB5-D2314F7B-B6BD3225-7BED188B|kName|kDesc|30-Day Pass|This Pass Allows You Access To X7 For 30 Days From The Date You Purchased It. Enjoy The Most Popular Club In Town!|Consumable|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.60.0.450.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
43F03BA0-E05A4197-8E704671-D1F64C4C|kName|kDesc|Dragons Green Thirty Day Ticket|Purchase The Thirty Day Ticket To Unlock The Full Version Of Dragons Green For 30 Days.|Consumable|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.3.6.22.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
44FB632B-60B4478D-86CB8B38-41481E77|kName|kDesc|Espionage 9 Tickets (35)|Use These Tickets To Play Espionage 9 And Lead Your Intelligence Agents To Global Domination!|Consumable|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.52.0.2.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
451777B6-C52F45A9-800AF658-7217FB4C|kName|kDesc|600 Aquabux|You Will Be Purchasing A Token For 600 AquaBux Which You May Consume To Purchase Or Gift Fish And/or Decorations.|Consumable|Digital Leisure|HDK_1.66.0.144.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
456024D8-5CB34C55-AD82BB55-854C7777|kName|kDesc|Golden-striped Grouper|Golden-striped Grouper|Consumable|Digital Leisure|HDK_1.66.0.144.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
4756E86C-008C44CB-AAD9B236-DA3ACF78|kName|kDesc|Espionage 9 Tickets (15)|Use These Tickets To Play Espionage 9 And Lead Your Intelligence Agents To Global Domination!|Consumable|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.52.0.2.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
488443B1-804C4523-89D63BD6-52EEBFE1|kName|kDesc|F.U.B.A.R. War Bucks (1000)|These Are A Special Kind Of Currency For Use In F.U.B.A.R. (Fight Until Blood And Ruin). Use War Bucks To Speed Up Your Progress Through The Game, Purchase Unique Items For Your Base And To Enhance Your Gameplay Experience.|Consumable|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.65.0.139.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
48C29131-935443AB-90CB35AA-93DE6B64|kName|kDesc|100 VEEMEE 3D Printer Vouchers|A Pack Of 100 Vouchers For Use With The VEEMEE 3D Printer. Choose From A Varied Selection Of Reward Items To Print In The Comfort Of Your (virtual) Home, Or Use The Vouchers To Send An Item To A Friend's 3D Printer. The Larger The Pack Of Vouchers, The Better The Value.|Consumable|VEEMEE|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
4901A493-A0214834-A711F524-28C93EE9|kName|kDesc|Xi: Continuum - Buff Pack (10)|Give Your Associates A Temporary Boost Of Power And Gain The Upper Hand In The Xi: Continuum Combat Game. This Pack Contains 10 Consumable Buffs. These Buffs Are Only For Use In The Xi: Continuum Combat Game. Note - This Is A Consumable Item.|Consumable|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
499509A4-24A94552-929A268F-602C76B1|kName|kDesc|720 Giftinator Bucks|Get A +20% Bonus Instantly With This Pack Of 720 Giftinator Bucks To Use With The Giftinator 9000 From Hellfire Games. Redeem To Gift Exclusive Items To Friends (and Yourself!) And Earn Karma Bonuses With Each Transaction!|Consumable|Hellfire Games, Inc.|HDK_1.83.0.11.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
4B24B65F-17C54594-A602C7BA-2980C040|kName|kDesc|10,000 Gold|10,000 Gold|Consumable|Digital Leisure|HDK_1.82.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
4B2B989E-CC0B4AA8-858B1FE3-859FA45B|kName|kDesc|Vortex Attractor (100)|Vortex Attractors Can Be Used In The Aurora Sky Fishing Game To Dramatically Reduce The Waiting Time And Distance Between You And Your Catch, Making It Much Easier To Reel In The Rarer Catches. This Is A Pack Of 100 Vortex Attractors.|Consumable|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.52.0.2.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
4E652422-31164E99-B2E5FE99-D71F028B|kName|kDesc|Supa-Fun Robo-Goalie Time!! 50 Ball Pack|Gives Up To 50 Plays Of Supa-Fun Robo-Goalie Time!!|Consumable|VEEMEE|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
5071A24E-086A4EBE-892CA1E2-0D406A86|kName|kDesc|Yetis Vs Hunters - Improved Kill Streak|Increases The Time Frame, From 5 Seconds To 10 Seconds, For A Kill To Count Towards The Current Kill Streak. The Effect Lasts For An Entire Round Of Play. (10 Pack)|Consumable|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.55.0.155.BETA2|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
51A43A42-5C694AC6-9DBBE4BF-D94C4BB3|kName|kDesc|Yetis Vs Hunters - Slower Game Clock|Slows The Game Timer For 15 Seconds. (10 Pack)|Consumable|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.55.0.155.BETA2|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
53F13EBF-8BA74D61-BF5DC991-3D1D34EE|kName|kDesc|Xi: Continuum - Associate Pack 2|Add More Grunt, Guile And Guns To Your Crew With These 5 Random Associates For The Xi: Continuum Combat Game. 5 Associates That You Do Not Currently Own Will Be Chosen At Random. These Associates Are Only For Use In The Xi: Continuum Combat Game. Note - On Buying All 16 Associate Packs You Are Guaranteed To Unlock All 80 Purchasable Associates.|Consumable|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
558EDF38-5064415B-9D523BB1-E4826C88|kName|kDesc|Lockwood Token Pack - 480|Use Lockwood Tokens With The Lockwood Gift Machine To Give Gifts To Your Friends - Pack Of 480.|Consumable|Lockwood|HDK_1.52.0.2.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
5647EE6F-72F341B1-93D0D4B3-05EE4BCA|kName|kDesc|5000 VEEMEE 3D Printer Vouchers|A Pack Of 5000 Vouchers For Use With The VEEMEE 3D Printer. Choose From A Varied Selection Of Reward Items To Print In The Comfort Of Your (virtual) Home, Or Use The Vouchers To Send An Item To A Friend's 3D Printer. The Larger The Pack Of Vouchers, The Better The Value.|Consumable|VEEMEE|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
57421054-BED04C84-AA1DAF30-497CF607|kName|kDesc|Vortex Attractor (10)|Vortex Attractors Can Be Used In The Aurora Sky Fishing Game To Dramatically Reduce The Waiting Time And Distance Between You And Your Catch, Making It Much Easier To Reel In The Rarer Catches. This Is A Pack Of 10 Vortex Attractors.|Consumable|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.52.0.2.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
5A72D2DC-FF73460F-B819B3B8-1C99049F|kName|kDesc|OrbRunner: Double Vision (20) + 500XP|This Consumable Item Will Make Twice As Many Orbs Appear As Normal In OrbRunner. Note - This Is A Mini Game Upgrade Not An Apartment Item.|Consumable|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
5B9BCC58-E794496A-B10A027C-DAFB1C19|kName|kDesc|Lockwood Token Pack - 80|Use Lockwood Tokens With The Lockwood Gift Machine To Give Gifts To Your Friends - Pack Of 80.|Consumable|Lockwood|HDK_1.52.0.2.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
5D85906C-C5D34492-B5ADE07C-0A1DC58C|kName|kDesc|LOOT™ Premium RadioIO Rental Pass -- Two Days|Want To Enjoy RadioIO Without Commercial Interruptions? With This Rental Pass In Your Inventory, You Can Activate Any Portable LOOT™ Radio Or Baked-in EOD In A LOOT™ Estate/clubhouse And Enjoy Commercial-free Streams For Two Full Days From Point Of Purchase! Plus, You Get Access To 21 ADDITIONAL Music Channels, AND Higher Audio Quality For All Of The RadioIO Streams! Best Of All, As Long As Your Rental Pass Is Active And Yours Is The Account Controlling The Device, Your Friends Wont Hear Any Commercials, Either! Absolutely Perfect For Parties! Includes: 1.) 81 Commercial Free Channels For You And Your Guests 2.) Higher Audio Quality On All Stations 3.) Exclusive RadioIO Blue Hoodie (male) 4.) Exclusive RadioIO Red Hoodie (female) PLEASE READ: Due To Contractual And Rights Agreements, All Content May Not Be Available In All Countries. Content Availability Is Dependent On The Geolocation Of The Device. RADIOIO Is Only Available In US And CA. Only One LOOT™ TV Or LOOT™ Radio Can Be Active At A Time.|Consumable|© LOOT™|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
5DBE4CA0-B49A48FE-9ABEE2DF-DAF40500|kName|kDesc|Flower Cucumber|The Game Which Likes An Elegant Cucumber Is Drawn Near. 40-piece Set.|Consumable|Will Co.,Ltd.|HDK_1.52.0.2.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
60D1BA67-114A4038-8F2F9B57-7A16C204|kName|kDesc|Game Mechanics 2000 Coin Pack|These Are Coins That Can Be Used In Any Game Mechanics Game That Uses Coins.|Consumable|Game Mechanics|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
61439307-016E49B1-9801ECC9-767DD2BF|kName|kDesc|Xi: Continuum - Associate Pack 6|Add More Grunt, Guile And Guns To Your Crew With These 5 Random Associates For The Xi: Continuum Combat Game. 5 Associates That You Do Not Currently Own Will Be Chosen At Random. These Associates Are Only For Use In The Xi: Continuum Combat Game. Note - On Buying All 16 Associate Packs You Are Guaranteed To Unlock All 80 Purchasable Associates.|Consumable|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
649AB341-1DF24FD9-9963A430-33B2BC9D|kName|kDesc|Charcoal Champ Cookout Pack|Load Up On 10 Magic Rubs, 10 Sodas, And 10 Lighter Fluids For Charcoal Champ.|Consumable|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
6523DDE1-B884465D-B076A8D3-2B3E7344|kName|kDesc|1000 MyGymTokens|1000 MyGym Tokens For You To Spend On Any Items From The Range Of MyGym Clothing And Objects.|Consumable|VEEMEE|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
66BD67C1-D12C4C13-97C3CABB-5EBBE5CA|kName|kDesc|330 Home Tycoon Gold Coins|Includes 330 Gold Coins To Spend In Home Tycoon. Unlock Premium Buildings And Expansion Packs Containing New Missions, Fun Activities, Stylish Clothing, And More Rewards!|Consumable|Hellfire Games, Inc.|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
6AB43A15-E0F54C63-91D6D0F5-A958702F|kName|kDesc|The Green Ticket|This Is Good For 50 Plays In The Midway. Play Games, Win Fabulous Prizes, Impress Your Friends And Enemies! This Item Can Be Purchased Multiple Times, So Come Back Again When You Run Out!|Consumable|Mass Media Games, Inc.|HDK_1.41.0.37.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
6ACF0885-21B44FB2-9BE50613-35824A8A|kName|kDesc|100000 ModPoints|Purchase ModPoints For The EmoRay Store. This Particular Consumable Will Give You 100000 ModPoints. When You Enter The EmoRay Store Your ModPoints Will Be Deducted From This Consumable Before Using ModPoints Already Earned Through Gameplay.|Consumable|Heavy Water|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
6C1AB140-FB184B15-937116CC-4196BA5E|kName|kDesc|The Ticket Of Hayabusa|The Ticket Which Can Try The Function Of The Fishing Rod Of Hayabusa On Number-of-times Limitation.|Consumable|Will Co.,Ltd.|HDK_1.66.0.144.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
6D2DEE74-4D2C45FB-B1DE7DBC-FFB2A08E|kName|kDesc|Yetis Vs Hunters - Infinite Ammo|Unlimited Ammo For 15 Seconds. (10 Pack)|Consumable|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.55.0.155.BETA2|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
6F26586F-D2674CAB-A548D08C-F1D1C4FF|title|description|Dueling Red Stones X7|Set Of 7 Mysterious Gemstones That Restore Order Count For Use With Peakvox Monster.|Consumable|O-Two Inc.|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
6F70D035-4BB74FE7-BC6D74A8-5C3D3502|kName|kDesc|4000 Aquabux|You Will Be Purchasing A Token For 4000 AquaBux Which You May Consume To Purchase Or Gift Fish And/or Decorations.|Consumable|Digital Leisure|HDK_1.66.0.144.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
719DE010-E5854323-A85EB48E-B7DB8200|kName|kDesc|150 Giftinator Bucks|Includes 150 Giftinator Bucks To Use With The Giftinator 9000 From Hellfire Games. Redeem To Gift Exclusive Items To Friends (and Yourself!) And Earn Karma Bonuses With Each Transaction!|Consumable|Hellfire Games, Inc.|HDK_1.83.0.11.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
73E9C591-2A60426E-AFB1FF81-751EB89E|kName|kDesc|Xi: Continuum - Associate Pack 9|Add More Grunt, Guile And Guns To Your Crew With These 5 Random Associates For The Xi: Continuum Combat Game. 5 Associates That You Do Not Currently Own Will Be Chosen At Random. These Associates Are Only For Use In The Xi: Continuum Combat Game. Note - On Buying All 16 Associate Packs You Are Guaranteed To Unlock All 80 Purchasable Associates.|Consumable|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
7A2F07EC-D4844621-BCCADDF4-CD1D1E92|kName|kDesc|Treasure: 21600 Coins|21600 Coins To Spend In Cutthroats: Battle For Black Powder Cove's Armoury.|Consumable|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.60.0.450.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
7AC1C1AE-8DF14A23-BFA3392D-9FE8C9A8|kName|kDesc|325 Giftinator Bucks|Get A +8% Bonus Instantly With This Pack Of 325 Giftinator Bucks To Use With The Giftinator 9000 From Hellfire Games. Redeem To Gift Exclusive Items To Friends (and Yourself!) And Earn Karma Bonuses With Each Transaction!|Consumable|Hellfire Games, Inc.|HDK_1.83.0.11.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
7B664B18-3E2D43F7-AB7B2DB4-FA0626A4|kName|kDesc|100 MyGym Tokens|100 MyGym Tokens For You To Spend On Any Items From The Range Of MyGym Clothing And Objects.|Consumable|VEEMEE|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
7BDC421C-A9254314-B3B2678F-62FDFB50|kName|kDesc|OrbRunner: Time Vortex (100) + 625XP|This Consumable Item Will Make The Clock In OrbRunner Run Down A Lot Slower Than Normal. Note - This Is A Mini Game Upgrade Not An Apartment Item.|Consumable|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
7CB7A73B-404C4A59-A427F348-6602A9D8|kName|kDesc|Uproar Credits - 730|Uproar Credits Allow You To Purchase, Rent And Gift Weapons, Serums, Clothing Items And Taunts In Uproar - The Fast Paced, Action Packed Third-person Shooter, Exclusive To PlayStation®Home. This Pack Contains: 666 Uproar Credits + 64 Bonus Uproar Credits Get More Bonus Credits When You Purchase Larger Packs And Take Full Advantage Of The Game's Extensive Customisation Options!|Consumable|Lockwood|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
7D8E7EF0-E41A499B-BC88345C-58A6868C|kName|kDesc|GZ Tickets (30 Tickets)|This Is A Series Of 30 Tickets That Entitles You To Special Services At Various Lounges In Granzella.|Consumable|Granzella Inc.|HDK_1.60.0.450.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
7DF6CC19-A7564C85-8C21D6F7-3E210C00|title|description|Gold Pocket Watch X7|Points Of Availability In Quests For A Certain Time That Can Be Used With Peakvox Monster A Set Of 7 Pocket Watches That Increase Your Acquisition Friendliness.|Consumable|O-Two Inc.|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
7FAEFE51-29274DE7-9FBBCCF7-2958378F|kName|kDesc|Uproar Credits - 225|Uproar Credits Allow You To Purchase, Rent And Gift Weapons, Serums, Clothing Items And Taunts In Uproar - The Fast Paced, Action Packed Third-person Shooter, Exclusive To PlayStation®Home. This Pack Contains: 221 Uproar Credits + 4 Bonus Uproar Credits Get More Bonus Credits When You Purchase Larger Packs And Take Full Advantage Of The Game's Extensive Customisation Options!|Consumable|Lockwood|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
8344FF1A-E98D4467-97C25759-9F6DA847|kName|kDesc|Xi: Continuum - Associate Pack 11|Add More Grunt, Guile And Guns To Your Crew With These 5 Random Associates For The Xi: Continuum Combat Game. 5 Associates That You Do Not Currently Own Will Be Chosen At Random. These Associates Are Only For Use In The Xi: Continuum Combat Game. Note - On Buying All 16 Associate Packs You Are Guaranteed To Unlock All 80 Purchasable Associates.|Consumable|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
852158AA-B6D64E41-B3687407-A8ED1BC3|kName|kDesc|40,000 Chips|Best Value! - 40,000 Casino Chips Will Be Added To Your Holdings When You Play Your First Game. Chips May Be Used At Any Available Casino Game Throughout The Space. Included With This Purchase Is Exclusive Access To The VIP Section, Where The Most Serious Gamers Come To Play. Simply Wear The VIP Top Hat To Be Let In. As An Added Bonus, You'll Also Be The First To Receive Early Access To Your Own Private Hotel Space Compliments Of The Casino Manager.|Consumable|Digital Leisure|HDK_1.55.0.155.BETA2|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
8643C7F5-912F4F31-8C9632BF-A819EC28|kName|kDesc|2000 VEEMEE 3D Printer Vouchers|A Pack Of 2000 Vouchers For Use With The VEEMEE 3D Printer. Choose From A Varied Selection Of Reward Items To Print In The Comfort Of Your (virtual) Home, Or Use The Vouchers To Send An Item To A Friend's 3D Printer. The Larger The Pack Of Vouchers, The Better The Value.|Consumable|VEEMEE|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
87616D21-5ED3470F-9714B470-B9A7193A|kName|kDesc|Uproar Credits - 6,850|Uproar Credits Allow You To Purchase, Rent And Gift Weapons, Serums, Clothing Items And Taunts In Uproar - The Fast Paced, Action Packed Third-person Shooter, Exclusive To PlayStation®Home. This Pack Contains: 5554 Uproar Credits + 1296 Bonus Uproar Credits Get More Bonus Credits When You Purchase Larger Packs And Take Full Advantage Of The Game's Extensive Customisation Options!|Consumable|Lockwood|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
876AAF6A-542B4461-B33D2909-AED647C6|kName|kDesc|Thander Rice Cake|Monster Japon Attract Sweet-loving Creatures With Bait That Can Be Used Within A Single Fishing fishing Game. You Will Never Get The Wrong One, So You Can Accumulate Points Efficiently. Purchasing It Adds 20 Pieces. Also, Each Use Consumes 1 Piece. After Purchase, It Takes A Little Time To Reflect The Quantity To The Mini-game.|Consumable|Will Co.,Ltd.|HDK_1.60.0.450.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
878CDD93-A9B44598-858C7A6E-733CBCD8|kName|kDesc|Trial Cucumber|The Free Trial Copy Of a Cucumber With A Flower.|Consumable|Will Co.,Ltd.|HDK_1.52.0.2.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
87EE7792-30B94450-B98B282C-21E10E1B|kName|kDesc|Xi: Continuum - Associate Pack 4|Add More Grunt, Guile And Guns To Your Crew With These 5 Random Associates For The Xi: Continuum Combat Game. 5 Associates That You Do Not Currently Own Will Be Chosen At Random. These Associates Are Only For Use In The Xi: Continuum Combat Game. Note - On Buying All 16 Associate Packs You Are Guaranteed To Unlock All 80 Purchasable Associates.|Consumable|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
8846E8C2-09BA40DE-A90BB3D7-0A7A0F8D|kName|kDesc|10 Juggernaut Coins|Redeem Juggernaut Coins For Exclusive Juggernaut Games Content For Yourself Or Your Friends!|Consumable|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.65.0.139.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
89B7C21F-D9BC4687-841C03D7-8464B9E7|kName|kDesc|Game Mechanics 100 Coin Pack|These Are Coins That Can Be Used In Any Game Mechanics Game That Uses Coins.|Consumable|Game Mechanics|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
89EABF8E-22E042A7-8D13AF61-3379EF9B|kName|kDesc|Treasure: 172800 Coins|172800 Coins To Spend In Cutthroats: Battle For Black Powder Cove's Armoury.|Consumable|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.60.0.450.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
8A04F6A8-3B774682-882B55EE-FBAE1D26|kName|kDesc|The Ticket Of Steel|The Ticket Which Can Try The Function Of The Fishing Rod Of Steel On Number-of-times Limitation.|Consumable|Will Co.,Ltd.|HDK_1.66.0.144.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
8B2E5BE7-27BB49AB-B54FBFEE-A453E94A|kName|kDesc|GZ Tickets (10)|A Strand Of 10 Tickets That Allow For Use Of Special Services In The Various Granzella Lounges.|Consumable|Granzella Inc.|HDK_1.65.0.139.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
8D52BB2C-6A2A4410-B5067452-2DE48A60|kName|kDesc|Heal Bug Pack|This Pack Gives You 15 Heal Bug Abilities, Allowing You To Repair And Mend Your Creatures In The Thick Of Battle.|Consumable|FluffyLogic Development Ltd.|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
8FD1D0BE-B8EF4C77-80DA9325-D84D0F98|kName|kDesc|Xi: Continuum - Buff Pack (50)|Give Your Associates A Temporary Boost Of Power And Gain The Upper Hand In The Xi: Continuum Combat Game. This Pack Contains 50 Consumable Buffs. These Buffs Are Only For Use In The Xi: Continuum Combat Game. Note - This Is A Consumable Item.|Consumable|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
90AD937B-E89D4704-85B07C6A-952CECF3|kName|kDesc|1500 Aquabux|You Will Be Purchasing A Token For 1500 AquaBux Which You May Consume To Purchase Or Gift Fish And/or Decorations.|Consumable|Digital Leisure|HDK_1.66.0.144.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
90C1BA45-3A2C4093-B2949A7B-47CD65C3|kName|kDesc|The Ticket Of Sacred Flame|Monster Japon Ippon FishingThis Ticket Allows You To Try Out The Haja No Rod Feature In The fishing Game A Limited Number Of Times. You Can Get This Ticket By Exchanging Points At The Monster Japon Ippon Fishing Reception Desk.|Consumable|Will Co.,Ltd.|HDK_1.66.0.144.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
94D8D17F-3DA44DA1-A62415A1-A1A03F48|kName|kDesc|100 Acorn Vouchers|A Pack Of 100 Acorn Vouchers For Use In Acorn Meadow Park. Enjoy Any Activity In The Park In Exchange For Acorn Vouchers. The Larger The Pack Of Vouchers, The Better The Value.|Consumable|VEEMEE|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
979766DC-D66A4B84-BAACEA74-5E942FA2|kName|kDesc|Yetis Vs Hunters - Explosive Darts|Hunter Power-Up! Double Points For Each Kill And Adds Splash Damage To Kill Several Enemies With One Hit. The Effect Lasts For An Entire Round Of Play.|Consumable|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.55.0.155.BETA2|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
982B2607-9D384E64-87CDE0B7-EB76412E|kName|kDesc|Charcoal Champ Ultimate Magic Rub|Get 60 Magic Rubs To Make Perfect Meat Every Time In Charcoal Champ.|Consumable|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
9A18F263-913D4C9B-9C14662E-8D4BFF1B|kName|kDesc|Treasure: 86400 Coins|86400 Coins To Spend In Cutthroats: Battle For Black Powder Cove's Armoury.|Consumable|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.60.0.450.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
9C291241-92184016-858000A3-151BC969|kName|kDesc|Charcoal Champ Soda|Get 10 Sodas To Slow Down The Clock In Charcoal Champ.|Consumable|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
9CEDC3A2-9E844C95-81E87268-98D44607|kName|kDesc|Oni Rice Cake|Kaiju Japon One Fishing Bait Available Within The fishing Game Attracts Cracker-loving Creatures. You Will Never Get A Hazing, So You Can Accumulate Points Efficiently. Purchasing It Adds 25 Pieces. Also, Each Use Consumes 1 Piece. It Takes A Little Time To Reflect The Quantity To The Mini-game After Purchase.|Consumable|Will Co.,Ltd.|HDK_1.60.0.450.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
9E96CEFA-D1D74A88-8CE8A33A-029D8391|kName|kDesc|2000 Aurora XP|Congratulations - You've Just Won A Reward That Gives You A Massive 2000 FREE Aurora XP! This Means You May Already Have Won Some Rewards And Levelled Up! Don't Forget To Visit Aurora!|Consumable|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|AUTO-REWARD|Res:0
9EF0FF41-9EEE4E62-96FF23B2-BFC6B439|kName|kDesc|5,000 Chips|5,000 Casino Chips Will Be Added To Your Holdings When You Play Your First Game. Chips May Be Used At Any Available Casino Game Throughout The Space. You'll Also Be Rewarded With Unique Items Just For Playing! Good Luck!|Consumable|Digital Leisure|HDK_1.55.0.155.BETA2|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
9F52F453-F37B4241-9C9685BC-BA5085C7|kName|kDesc|Uproar Credits - 110|Uproar Credits Allow You To Purchase, Rent And Gift Weapons, Serums, Clothing Items And Taunts In Uproar - The Fast Paced, Action Packed Third-person Shooter, Exclusive To PlayStation®Home. This Pack Contains: 110 Uproar Credits Get More Bonus Credits When You Purchase Larger Packs And Take Full Advantage Of The Game's Extensive Customisation Options!|Consumable|Lockwood|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
A37C9A91-D1DB4F7B-8F5E9257-A4CF6D60|kName|kDesc|Charcoal Champ Magic Rub|Get 10 Magic Rubs To Make Perfect Meat Every Time In Charcoal Champ.|Consumable|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
A6462FC7-C9304F9B-A72EF806-147C4B14|kName|kDesc|F.U.B.A.R. War Bucks (10)|These Are A Special Kind Of Currency For Use In F.U.B.A.R. (Fight Until Blood And Ruin). Use War Bucks To Speed Up Your Progress Through The Game, Purchase Unique Items For Your Base And To Enhance Your Gameplay Experience.|Consumable|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
A8CE41C8-0C6A4C9C-AE868998-6475B2FC|kName|kDesc|2000 Acorn Vouchers|A Pack Of 2000 Acorn Vouchers For Use In Acorn Meadow Park. Enjoy Any Activity In The Park In Exchange For Acorn Vouchers. The Larger The Pack Of Vouchers, The Better The Value.|Consumable|VEEMEE|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
AB09D35C-38AD4614-9A40676D-7384D0F1|kName|kDesc|Xi: Continuum - Associate Pack 7|Add More Grunt, Guile And Guns To Your Crew With These 5 Random Associates For The Xi: Continuum Combat Game. 5 Associates That You Do Not Currently Own Will Be Chosen At Random. These Associates Are Only For Use In The Xi: Continuum Combat Game. Note - On Buying All 16 Associate Packs You Are Guaranteed To Unlock All 80 Purchasable Associates.|Consumable|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
AB28900E-6F034B3A-BFA2FDB4-E4DFAD32|kName|kDesc|500 Chips|500 Casino Chips Will Be Added To Your Holdings When You Play Your First Game. Chips May Be Used At Any Available Casino Game Throughout The Space. You'll Also Be Rewarded With Unique Items Just For Playing! Good Luck!|Consumable|Digital Leisure|HDK_1.55.0.155.BETA2|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
AB624964-8D2C4798-962D77BF-C3E5737F|kName|kDesc|75 Home Tycoon Gold Coins|Includes 75 Gold Coins To Spend In Home Tycoon. Unlock Premium Buildings And Expansion Packs Containing New Missions, Fun Activities, Stylish Clothing, And More Rewards!|Consumable|Hellfire Games, Inc.|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
AB722D79-A5BE40B6-8789E49A-C21D2A67|kName|kDesc|Balsam Pear|The Living Thing Said To Live In A South Direction Is Drawn Near. 30-piece Set.|Consumable|Will Co.,Ltd.|HDK_1.52.0.2.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
AB820CB2-684B407A-A0F089A4-2F23701F|kName|kDesc|Treasure: 5400 Coins|5400 Coins To Spend In Cutthroats: Battle For Black Powder Cove's Armoury.|Consumable|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.60.0.450.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
ABC04D9A-D33C40E6-B9AACF85-69A0FE45|kName|kDesc|150 Juggernaut Coins|Redeem Juggernaut Coins For Exclusive Juggernaut Games Content For Yourself Or Your Friends!|Consumable|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.65.0.139.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
ADB40B0E-7982453F-979062A0-072F10BD|kName|kDesc|500 VEEMEE 3D Printer Vouchers|A Pack Of 500 Vouchers For Use With The VEEMEE 3D Printer. Choose From A Varied Selection Of Reward Items To Print In The Comfort Of Your (virtual) Home, Or Use The Vouchers To Send An Item To A Friend's 3D Printer. The Larger The Pack Of Vouchers, The Better The Value.|Consumable|VEEMEE|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
AFE58A31-22994815-B9AE8C95-BC494862|kName|kDesc|1,000 Gold|1,000 Gold|Consumable|Digital Leisure|HDK_1.82.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
B0D95A26-C88141A7-A6CC6C1D-F87DBB80|kName|kDesc|Game Mechanics 5000 Coin Pack|These Are Coins That Can Be Used In Any Game Mechanics Game That Uses Coins.|Consumable|Game Mechanics|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
B6A6A14D-8DCD4A90-881C8411-14A0EEF7|kName|kDesc|OrbRunner: Double Vision (100) + 875XP|This Consumable Item Will Make Twice As Many Orbs Appear As Normal In OrbRunner. Note - This Is A Mini Game Upgrade Not An Apartment Item.|Consumable|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
B73BCE6C-2E594445-912F50A3-D4D42AD8|kName|kDesc|OrbRunner: Double Vision (50) + 625XP|This Consumable Item Will Make Twice As Many Orbs Appear As Normal In OrbRunner. Note - This Is A Mini Game Upgrade Not An Apartment Item.|Consumable|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
B76B6456-B30E4A14-925B38A2-7CB355E5|kName|kDesc|10 Los Penguini Brothers Tickets|Each Los Penguini Brothers Ticket Entitles You To Play The Los Penguini Brothers Aerial Challenge. Jump For Fame And Reward.|Consumable|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.52.0.2.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
B8A6C1BD-4D0D45BD-AB5C793E-CC0CC574|kName|kDesc|SodiumOne Full Game Rental Ticket - 2 Days|Blast Your Way Through All 50 Levels Of SodiumOne! Youll Receive Full Access To the Most Explosive Shooter In PlayStation®Home For 2 Days From The Time Of Purchase With This Game Rental Ticket.|Consumable|Sodium - Lockwood|HDK_1.41.0.37.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
B8AA0A12-301342C6-9D356C15-BB6D62C4|kName|kDesc|80,000 Gold|80,000 Gold|Consumable|Digital Leisure|HDK_1.82.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
B963AB7C-47FC43E3-B369EAFA-50FE9AF3|kName|kDesc|5000 Acorn Vouchers|A Pack Of 5000 Acorn Vouchers For Use In Acorn Meadow Park. Enjoy Any Activity In The Park In Exchange For Acorn Vouchers. The Larger The Pack Of Vouchers, The Better The Value.|Consumable|VEEMEE|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
BA4FCBB1-DF2A4F7C-8388CC7A-504B7899|kName|kDesc|Xi: Continuum - Associate Pack 5|Add More Grunt, Guile And Guns To Your Crew With These 5 Random Associates For The Xi: Continuum Combat Game. 5 Associates That You Do Not Currently Own Will Be Chosen At Random. These Associates Are Only For Use In The Xi: Continuum Combat Game. Note - On Buying All 16 Associate Packs You Are Guaranteed To Unlock All 80 Purchasable Associates.|Consumable|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
BAE00D28-2D7F45BD-8254A0DE-E0CE6408|Name|Desc|Home Hold 'Em Poker Token Pack 50|Pack Of 50 Tokens Used To Purchase Or Gift In-game Items.|Consumable|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.65.0.139.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
BDEB86D2-CE934CFA-AC883242-46922AC9|kName|kDesc|Upgrade Bug Speed Pack|This Pack Gives You 15 Bug Speed Upgrades, Allowing You To Create Faster Creatures.|Consumable|FluffyLogic Development Ltd.|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
C30EEC98-2982445D-98362584-834B7D53|kName|kDesc|Xi: Continuum - Associate Pack 8|Add More Grunt, Guile And Guns To Your Crew With These 5 Random Associates For The Xi: Continuum Combat Game. 5 Associates That You Do Not Currently Own Will Be Chosen At Random. These Associates Are Only For Use In The Xi: Continuum Combat Game. Note - On Buying All 16 Associate Packs You Are Guaranteed To Unlock All 80 Purchasable Associates.|Consumable|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
C447B831-F1AB40D1-BA762871-42B73483|kName|kDesc|100 Los Penguini Brothers Tickets|Each Los Penguini Brothers Ticket Entitles You To Play The Los Penguini Brothers Aerial Challenge. Jump For Fame And Reward.|Consumable|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.52.0.2.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
C5198D13-10F94179-9CAF03D1-14F0497E|kName|kDesc|25000 ModPoints|Purchase ModPoints For The EmoRay Store. This Particular Consumable Will Give You 25000 ModPoints. When You Enter The EmoRay Store Your ModPoints Will Be Deducted From This Consumable Before Using ModPoints Already Earned Through Gameplay.|Consumable|Heavy Water|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
C7A0DCF5-1D5E4F8E-B1EB4D3A-A88490EF|kName|kDesc|OrbRunner: Elite XP Booster|Equip This Item For The Latest In Orb-collection Technology! Once Activated, This Item Will Allow You To Collect 4x XP In OrbRunner, Resulting In You Leveling Up And Reaching Those Rewards FOUR TIMES FASTER!|Consumable|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
CA02D341-8E4D46CC-B5CD7E41-6E424964|kName|kDesc|Electromagnetic Bomb|Shut Down Enemy Ships With The Electromagnetic Bomb! You Control When This Bomb Detonates, Unleashing A Disruptive Electromagnetic Pulse That Shuts Down Enemy Weapons Systems.|Consumable|Hellfire Games, Inc.|HDK_1.52.0.2.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
CC88E3D0-0B194C75-99233928-ACCE9547|kName|kDesc|Xi: Continuum - Axiom Agent Pack|This Awesome Bundle Provides You With Complete Access To The Greatest Adventure In PlayStation®Home. Xi: Continuum, The Sequel To Xi, Is An Adventure Game Featuring Over 30 Missions With Hidden Rewards, An Evolving Story, As Well As Exclusive Videos And Websites. This Bundle Comes With The Evolving 'Vertigo' Apartment (with Additional Areas That Unlock As You Play Through The Game), The Flying Robotic Aeropal Companion, The Xoff Cola Machine Teleporter, 10 Combat Associates To Fight With In Single And Multiplayer Battles, And 5 Buffs To Temporarily Boost The Power Of Your Combat Associates. This Bundle Includes: * Access To The Xi: Continuum Adventure Game, Including The Xi: Continuum Public Space. * Xi: Continuum - Vertigo Apartment * Xi: Continuum - Aeropal Companion * Xi: Continuum - Xoff Cola Machine * 10 Random Associates And 5 Consumable Buffs For Use Within The Xi: Continuum Combat Game. ※Upon Purchase, All Items Will Be Added To Their Corresponding Categories.|Consumable|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
CC9463F1-9FC94E2E-B936B994-46AF1747|kName|kDesc|Xi: Continuum - Associate Pack 12|Add More Grunt, Guile And Guns To Your Crew With These 5 Random Associates For The Xi: Continuum Combat Game. 5 Associates That You Do Not Currently Own Will Be Chosen At Random. These Associates Are Only For Use In The Xi: Continuum Combat Game. Note - On Buying All 16 Associate Packs You Are Guaranteed To Unlock All 80 Purchasable Associates.|Consumable|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
CE9782C1-CBDD4742-A8DFA323-00350C90|kName|kDesc|Game Mechanics 500 Coin Pack|These Are Coins That Can Be Used In Any Game Mechanics Game That Uses Coins.|Consumable|Game Mechanics|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
D06FEACD-1C3842C2-B09E259D-7FD6DEF0|kName|kDesc|Experience Booster (Mental Reception Conditioning)|This Lightning-quick Conditioning Session Puts Eager Pilots In A Mental State Ideal For Learning. All Experience Point Gains From Defeating Enemies Are Increased To 150% For The Next Twenty-four Hours!|Consumable|Hellfire Games, Inc.|HDK_1.52.0.2.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
D41B124E-5F024FBC-A3159EBB-466A3962|kName|kDesc|Uproar Credits - 1,270|Uproar Credits Allow You To Purchase, Rent And Gift Weapons, Serums, Clothing Items And Taunts In Uproar - The Fast Paced, Action Packed Third-person Shooter, Exclusive To PlayStation®Home. This Pack Contains: 1110 Uproar Credits + 160 Bonus Uproar Credits Get More Bonus Credits When You Purchase Larger Packs And Take Full Advantage Of The Game's Extensive Customisation Options!|Consumable|Lockwood|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
D487057F-3AD54E16-BEB4EFDE-BA652EAB|kName|kDesc|Charcoal Champ Extra Soda|Get 25 Sodas To Slow Down The Clock In Charcoal Champ.|Consumable|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
D6FFC332-C05C45CC-9689A746-1A76C09D|kName|kDesc|Xi: Continuum - Associate Pack 16|Add More Grunt, Guile And Guns To Your Crew With These 5 Random Associates For The Xi: Continuum Combat Game. 5 Associates That You Do Not Currently Own Will Be Chosen At Random. These Associates Are Only For Use In The Xi: Continuum Combat Game. Note - On Buying All 16 Associate Packs You Are Guaranteed To Unlock All 80 Purchasable Associates.|Consumable|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
D7C3B576-586548FB-8BF02DC0-DFEA4876|kName|kDesc|7-Day Pass|This Pass Allows You Access To X7 For 7 Days From The Date You Purchased It. Enjoy The Most Popular Club In Town!|Consumable|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.60.0.450.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
D956A000-586744E1-ABABBE41-6623977E|kName|kDesc|Bumble Bee - Sodium2 Racer Paint Scheme|A Dazzling Yellow Skin For Your Sodium2 Racer. Pass Over The Finish Line As No More Than A Blinding, Golden Streak!|Consumable|Sodium - Lockwood|HDK_1.50.0.238.BETA|AUTO-REWARD|Res:0
D9CEDE89-DA4D4C7D-AE3DCCE5-EE8EE11C|kName|kDesc|Teleport Plant Pack|This Pack Gives You 10 Teleport Plant Power-ups, Allowing You To Teleport Troublesome Plants Away From The Route Your Creatures Are Taking.|Consumable|FluffyLogic Development Ltd.|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
DA1418BE-3B5B4493-BF2A2FDC-FF4E7EBD|kName|kDesc|Lockwood Token Pack - 2780|Use Lockwood Tokens With The Lockwood Gift Machine To Give Gifts To Your Friends - Pack Of 2780.|Consumable|Lockwood|HDK_1.52.0.2.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
DB905982-34364A9F-B21400B9-A1D51707|kName|kDesc|Reconfigure Bug Pack|This Pack Gives You 10 Reconfigure Bug Power-ups, Allowing You To Change One Creature Into Another Whenever You Please. Used Wisely This Power-up Can Turn A Dire Situation Around In Seconds.|Consumable|FluffyLogic Development Ltd.|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
DD7A400A-6887411D-BD0CBC7A-8A152413|kName|kDesc|Charcoal Champ Ultimate Soda|Get 60 Sodas To Slow Down The Clock In Charcoal Champ.|Consumable|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
DD7E347F-4A034A1C-BCA9FD12-B73A40A4|kName|kDesc|Multiple Pickaxes|Seven Pickaxes Are Included In This Bundle.|Consumable|Digital Leisure|HDK_1.82.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
DE470753-D99148A6-8FA0FD9E-D2E2DE63|kName|kDesc|SodiumOne Full Game Rental Ticket - 7 Days|Blast Your Way Through All 50 Levels Of SodiumOne! Youll Receive Full Access To The Most Explosive Shooter In PlayStation®Home For 7 Days From The Time Of Purchase With This Game Rental Ticket.|Consumable|Sodium - Lockwood|HDK_1.41.0.37.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
DEAED36C-95AF48E7-9EA86DE9-9F0BD532|YECK Ticket (50P)|Use it in the games of YECK Land. Each has 50 points.|YECK Ticket (50P)|Use It In The Games Of YECK Land. Each Has 50 Points.|Consumable|YECK Entertainment|HDK_1.66.0.144.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
DF72DEA1-9E0B42B3-9BC0389D-72444197|kName|kDesc|750 Home Tycoon Gold Coins|Includes 750 Gold Coins To Spend In Home Tycoon. Unlock Premium Buildings And Expansion Packs Containing New Missions, Fun Activities, Stylish Clothing, And More Rewards!|Consumable|Hellfire Games, Inc.|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
DFBEF417-3B7A4CC9-B25FE855-6DD19AC6|title|description|Gold Pocket Watch X12|Points Available For A Certain Amount Of Time In Quests For Use With Peakvox Monster Set Of 12 Pocket Watches To Increase Acquisition Friendliness.|Consumable|O-Two Inc.|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
E19B8460-DFBE478D-92DC2C03-A39AC416|kName|kDesc|Charcoal Champ Extra Magic Rub|Get 25 Magic Rubs To Make Perfect Meat Every Time In Charcoal Champ.|Consumable|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
E206BBDE-94E3437F-B299C978-D1BBC7FA|kName|kDesc|Supa-Fun Robo-Goalie Time!! 20 Ball Pack|Gives Up To 20 Plays Of Supa-Fun Robo-Goalie Time!!|Consumable|VEEMEE|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
E2F0C65A-49494C96-A74305BA-D42EBACF|kName|kDesc|OrbRunner: Harmful Orb Anti-Attractor + 750XP|This Great Piece Of Technology Will Stop Harmful Orbs From Being Attracted To You, Making It Easier To Get A Higher Score In The OrbRunner Mini Game Within Aurora. Note - This Is A Mini Game Upgrade Not An Apartment Item.|Consumable|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
E58F8615-19C44B64-BF25B724-2D8A2117|kName|kDesc|Beacon Pack|This Pack Gives You 15 Activate Beacon Power-ups, Allowing You To Direct Your Creatures As You Please.|Consumable|FluffyLogic Development Ltd.|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
E59050C2-B8EE426D-99F03E97-2CF2000D|kName|kDesc|15,000 Chips|15,000 Casino Chips Will Be Added To Your Holdings When You Play Your First Game. Chips May Be Used At Any Available Casino Game Throughout The Space. You'll Also Be Rewarded With Unique Items Just For Playing! Good Luck!|Consumable|Digital Leisure|HDK_1.55.0.155.BETA2|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
E5E02472-987543D7-91BC3E88-60F5CC67|kName|kDesc|GZ Tickets (10 Tickets)|Ten Tickets That Entitle You To Special Services In Various Granzella Lounges.|Consumable|Granzella Inc.|HDK_1.60.0.450.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
E6DF37F6-2B634E74-BB0E8D95-CCA5C43A|kName|kDesc|100 Aquabux|You Will Be Purchasing A Token For 100 AquaBux Which You May Consume To Purchase Or Gift Fish And/or Decorations.|Consumable|Digital Leisure|HDK_1.66.0.144.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
E6E96FEA-6AC9432D-89FE07C0-39DE5F95|kName|kDesc|Upgrade Bug Ability Pack|This Pack Gives You 10 Bug Ability Upgrades, Allowing You To Create More Effective Creatures With Special Abilities That Can Make A Huge Difference.|Consumable|FluffyLogic Development Ltd.|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
E80FA884-757F4296-B4E287FD-266EBCBA|kName|kDesc|Xi: Continuum - Complete Associate Bundle|This Great Value For Money Bundle Provides You With All 16 Associate Packs, Which Unlocks All 80 Purchasable Associates. This Bundle Includes: * Xi: Continuum - Associate Pack 1 * Xi: Continuum - Associate Pack 2 * Xi: Continuum - Associate Pack 3 * Xi: Continuum - Associate Pack 4 * Xi: Continuum - Associate Pack 5 * Xi: Continuum - Associate Pack 6 * Xi: Continuum - Associate Pack 7 * Xi: Continuum - Associate Pack 8 * Xi: Continuum - Associate Pack 9 * Xi: Continuum - Associate Pack 10 * Xi: Continuum - Associate Pack 11 * Xi: Continuum - Associate Pack 12 * Xi: Continuum - Associate Pack 13 * Xi: Continuum - Associate Pack 14 * Xi: Continuum - Associate Pack 15 * Xi: Continuum - Associate Pack 16 ※ These Associates Are Only For Use In The Xi: Continuum Combat Game.|Consumable|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
E811B53C-AEFE4E92-95D425DA-9E7A713F|kName|kDesc|Charcoal Champ Extra Lighter Fluid|Toss On The Lighter Fluid To Instantly Cook All Meat On The Grill To Perfect In Charcoal Champ. 25 Uses In Each Pack.|Consumable|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
EB2F3652-08F94C6C-A2A2585F-580E852E|kName|kDesc|LOOT™ Premium RadioIO Rental Pass -- Thirty Days|Want To Enjoy RadioIO Without Commercial Interruptions? With This Rental Pass In Your Inventory, You Can Activate Any Portable LOOT™ Radio Or Baked-in EOD In A LOOT™ Estate/clubhouse And Enjoy Commercial-free Streams For 30 Days From Point Of Purchase! Plus, You Get Access To 21 ADDITIONAL Music Channels, AND Higher Audio Quality For All Of The RadioIO Streams! Best Of All, As Long As Your Rental Pass Is Active And Yours Is The Account Controlling The Device, Your Friends Wont Hear Any Commercials, Either! Includes: 1.) 81 Commercial Free Channels For You And Your Guests 2). Higher Audio Quality On All Stations 3.) Exclusive RadioIO Blue Hoodie (male) 4.) Exclusive RadioIO Red Hoodie (female) 5.) Exclusive RadioIO Black Hoodie (male) 6.) Exclusive RadioIO Black Hoodie (female) PLEASE READ: Due To Contractual And Rights Agreements, All Content May Not Be Available In All Countries. Content Availability Is Dependent On The Geolocation Of The Device. RADIOIO Is Only Available In US And CA. Only One LOOT™ TV Or LOOT™ Radio Can Be Active At A Time.|Consumable|© LOOT™|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
EF845C96-B71343CB-9C2D1082-8C3B5326|kName|kDesc|1000 Acorn Vouchers|A Pack Of 1000 Acorn Vouchers For Use In Acorn Meadow Park. Enjoy Any Activity In The Park In Exchange For Acorn Vouchers. The Larger The Pack Of Vouchers, The Better The Value.|Consumable|VEEMEE|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
EFDFCB0F-B57A4616-A2FF0550-C196DC91|kName|kDesc|8 Hex Tokens|Use Hex Tokens To Buy Tiles For Hexx. Once Purchased This Will Add 8 Hex Tokens To Your Hexx Account. These Tokens Are For Use Within The Hexx Game Only.|Consumable|Heavy Water|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
F050BCF9-52574110-B1329CB8-FDA287B4|kName|kDesc|Arcade GAME Tokens - 100 Plays|Each Of These 100 GAME Tokens Gives You One Play On Any Of Our Public Space Arcade Cabinets. Battle The Alien Hordes In Savage Cosmos Or Become Electrokid And Use Your Special Powers To Defeat The Evil Company. Will You Be Able To Fight Your Way Through The SuperHero Madhouse - Or Will You Lose Your Mind Trying? Our Arcade Games Include Hi Score Leaderboards, Many Unlockable Medals And Rewards To Show Off To Your Friends. When Your Tokens Are Used Up, You Can Buy As Many More As You Like. You Can Also Purchase The Personal Space Version Of Any Of Our Arcade Games For Use In Any Of Your Apartments!|Consumable|VEEMEE|HDK_1.60.0.450.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
F1DB57AA-8A2F4B09-847573ED-A284ACCA|kName|kDesc|30,000 Gold|30,000 Gold|Consumable|Digital Leisure|HDK_1.82.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
F2719759-37754C70-9A8EF0E8-69EC6409|kName|kDesc|10000 ModPoints|Purchase ModPoints For The EmoRay Store. This Particular Consumable Will Give You 10000 ModPoints. When You Enter The EmoRay Store Your ModPoints Will Be Deducted From This Consumable Before Using ModPoints Already Earned Through Gameplay.|Consumable|Heavy Water|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
F2CF5CF6-E50C4C25-A5E77DFE-DA2A9C37|kName|kDesc|Charcoal Champ Lighter Fluid|Toss On The Lighter Fluid To Instantly Cook All Meat On The Grill To Perfect In Charcoal Champ. 10 Uses In Each Pack.|Consumable|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
F40FAAB0-D1864C40-A81C09F8-FBEB00B9|kName|kDesc|Treasure: 10800 Coins|10800 Coins To Spend In Cutthroats: Battle For Black Powder Cove's Armoury.|Consumable|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.60.0.450.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
F4155C3D-E61047BE-BAD25BBF-529F59D9|kName|kDesc|The Ticket Of Destruction|Kaiju Japon Ippon FishingThe Ticket To Try The hakai No Rod Functionality Available Within The fishing Game For A Limited Number Of Times. You Can Get It By Exchanging Points At The Monster Japon Ippon Fishing Reception Desk.|Consumable|Will Co.,Ltd.|HDK_1.66.0.144.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
F5683679-42F943E3-BE76B9F7-B11C02BA|kName|kDesc|60 Juggernaut Coins|Redeem Juggernaut Coins For Exclusive Juggernaut Games Content For Yourself Or Your Friends!|Consumable|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.65.0.139.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
F5E0F5BD-8A23402E-97D25E07-23375055|kName|kDesc|Espionage 9 Tickets|Use These Tickets To Play Espionage 9 And Lead Your Intelligence Agents To Global Domination!|Consumable|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.52.0.2.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
F736DFCC-9DD8471C-B95F8BA0-8BE99FC3|kName|kDesc|Xi: Continuum - Associate Pack 13|Add More Grunt, Guile And Guns To Your Crew With These 5 Random Associates For The Xi: Continuum Combat Game. 5 Associates That You Do Not Currently Own Will Be Chosen At Random. These Associates Are Only For Use In The Xi: Continuum Combat Game. Note - On Buying All 16 Associate Packs You Are Guaranteed To Unlock All 80 Purchasable Associates.|Consumable|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
F7CCF365-225F4CC8-BF7D3D33-CF15778F|kName|kDesc|Nebulon Booster (Portable Nebulon Purifier)|This Portable Device Processes Gathered Nebulon-charged Material, Increasing The Amount Of Pure Nebulon Extracted From It. All Nebulon Gains From Defeating Enemies Are Increased To 150% For The Next Twenty-four Hours!|Consumable|Hellfire Games, Inc.|HDK_1.52.0.2.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
F9407F03-018E4098-BEAF6D6F-568864F6|Name|Desc|Home Hold 'Em Poker Token Pack 10|Pack Of 10 Tokens Used To Purchase Or Gift In-game Items.|Consumable|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.65.0.139.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
F95F9367-0F3F4E3B-A669C575-55A9BCEF|kName|kDesc|500 MyGymTokens|500 MyGym Tokens For You To Spend On Any Items From The Range Of MyGym Clothing And Objects.|Consumable|VEEMEE|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
FAD0A888-67F54095-8E4922BF-401DEEB5|kName|kDesc|2000 MyGymTokens|2000 MyGym Tokens For You To Spend On Any Items From The Range Of MyGym Clothing And Objects.|Consumable|VEEMEE|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
FAE204D3-40CA42AA-8055A1D3-8721EE08|kName|kDesc|Lockwood Token Pack - 1180|Use Lockwood Tokens With The Lockwood Gift Machine To Give Gifts To Your Friends - Pack Of 1180.|Consumable|Lockwood|HDK_1.52.0.2.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
FBDB6247-958A4E5E-90A7D5E0-4E712CA6|kName|kDesc|GZ Tickets (10)|A Strand Of 10 Tickets That Allow For Use Of Special Services In The Various Granzella Lounges.|Consumable|Granzella Inc.|HDK_1.65.0.139.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
FBE3358A-8DFC4748-A75BF8A4-C812F691|kName|kDesc|350 Juggernaut Coins|Redeem Juggernaut Coins For Exclusive Juggernaut Games Content For Yourself Or Your Friends!|Consumable|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.65.0.139.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
FC770FD0-26C34625-9ACC4C65-0C6EC041|kName|kDesc|Radiant Storm|Engulf Your Enemies In Lightning With The Radiant Storm Bomb!  You Control When This Bomb Detonates, Causing It To Explode Into A Devastating Field Of Crackling Energy.|Consumable|Hellfire Games, Inc.|HDK_1.52.0.2.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
FD7CB9B6-B30E42B2-855E29EF-89B5C576|title|description|Dueling Red Stones X3|Set Of 3 Mysterious Gemstones To Restore Order Counts For Use With Peakvox Monster.|Consumable|O-Two Inc.|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
FEFF4034-19434C50-887221BD-E88DCB1D|kName|kDesc|Treasure: 43200 Coins|43200 Coins To Spend In Cutthroats: Battle For Black Powder Cove's Armoury.|Consumable|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.60.0.450.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
