00000000-00000000-00000000-0000000F|kName|kDesc|Ice Breaker|Keep The Ball Bouncing And Smash All Of The Ice Blocks!|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_XX|NOT-RWRD|Res:3
001A2BC2-EABB4D0C-8B278FB5-5743F8DE|kName|kDesc|Active Item - Cat|Mai-Mai The Cat Enjoys Jumping Up And Down The Levels Of Her Cat Post.|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.41.0.37.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:32
005756D8-5C3E4160-B2AE82B2-F8D1FF9A|kName|kDesc|MyBedroom - Birch Wood - Bed|An Interactive MyBedroom Bed With Sleeping Animation.|Furniture/Appliance|VEEMEE|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:18
006383B0-0A884F32-BC7FE411-BFFA7C48|kName|kDesc|Arabian Canopy Bed (Active Object)|Elegant Furnishings Fit For A King. Or Queen.|Furniture/Appliance|Lockwood|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|LUA-REWARD|Res:32
013937B8-772948C9-911A0E1C-0A6B6948|kName|kDesc|Active Object - Wooden Orrery|Keep Track Of Your Favourite Planet With Your Very Own Wooden Orrery.|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.41.0.37.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:21
01505C2E-2D3C469C-AC284081-AD250021|kName|kDesc|Crypt Keeper (White)|This Crypt Keeper Ensures Your Safety From The Evil Creatures That Lurk Within. However, This Does Not Stop Your Apartment From Filling With An Eerie White Fog And The Sound Of The Horrific Creatures Imprisoned Within The Crypt Below.|Furniture/Appliance|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.52.0.2.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:6
01CD95B2-9ECC4A27-B30B47D4-1B4448D6|kName|kDesc|BoxBeats: Dance|This Stylish Sound System Comes Jam Packed With Over 10 Amazing Dance Tracks For You And Your Friends To Listen To While You Bust Some Moves. This Active Item Also Allows You To Select Specific Tracks To Play, Set The Volume And Even Randomise The Track List. This Is An Essential Item For Your Apartment.|Furniture/Appliance|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.65.0.139.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:28
02EF7EF3-AAC24A21-8EDD04B9-5D3753AB|kName|kDesc|Telescope|This Active Item Lets You Move Freely About Your Space In First Person View, Activate A Spotlight, Take Videos And Pictures And Even Customize Your Shots With Photographic Filters!|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:35
03379C94-8BB84280-85934FA2-CA78FB97|kName|kDesc|Doctor Who - Scientist Dalek (Orange) Furniture|The Orange Daleks Are The Caretakers Of Dalek Science. Dont Worry If Youre Not Good At Mathematics, Your First Lesson Will Only Hurt For A Moment. EXTERMINATE! Doctor Who Logo © 2013 And TM BBC. Dalek Image © BBC/ Terry Nation 1963. Licensed By BBC WW Ltd.|Furniture/Appliance|BBC Worldwide Limited|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:9
0356813E-3FD045C5-90F7CA20-64CBC6AC|kName|kDesc|Cobalt Blue Toaster|Get Cooking With This Interactive Toaster!|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:15
038B266A-BC364C0C-94897C5F-E24F7143|kName|kDesc|Active Object - Star Dome|Just Sit Back And Enjoy A Close-up View Of The Stars.|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.41.0.37.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:11
04434F45-5B3E4173-9BD50B52-2FE8E7B3|kName|kDesc|Black Retro Speaker Left|The Left Black Retro Speaker From The LOOT™ Home Entertainment Collection.|Furniture/Appliance|© LOOT™|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:2
0457EB0D-AEE04966-A0D97FCC-5FFA46ED|kName|kDesc|Paranormal Hotspot Generator|This Active Item Allows The User To Place Paranormal hotspots Around Their Apartment And Choose The Type Of Paranormal Even That Will Be Generated For Each Hotspot! Prepare To Terrify Your Friends With All Sorts Of Ghostly Happenings.|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:45
04676D5C-3A5B48B9-8F6852CB-F123C94B|kName|kDesc|80'' LOOT™ Platinum EOD TV - Flatscreen|Discover The Benefits Of Owning Your Very Own Platinum EOD TV That Let's You Watch Full Length Movies, TV Episodes, Live Shows And More With Your Friends In PlayStation®Home! The LOOT™ Entertainment On Demand TV Will Work In Any Private Space Unless The Space Comes With A Video Screen You Cant Turn Off, It Does Not Include Streaming Radio Or Audio-only Content. Now All You Need To Do Is Invite Your Friends Over, Pull Out The Popcorn And Make The Most Important Decision Of All: What Will You Watch First!? PLEASE READ BEFORE YOU PURCHASE: Due To Contractual And Rights Agreements, Some EOD Channels Are Nation Specific. Crackle Content Is ONLY Available In United States, Canada, United Kingdom, And Australia. RadioIO Is ONLY Available In The United States And Canada. In Addition, Due To Rights Issues, Countries May Not Receive The Same Content Selections Within The Channels. Only One TV Can Be Active At A Time. The LOOT™ EOD Will Work In Any Private Space, UNLESS The Space Comes With A Video Screen You Cannot Turn Off.|Furniture/Appliance|© LOOT™|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:42
047A8CB0-44394FC7-A869E54B-6E09747A|kName|kDesc|Bioluminescent Kelp|Adds An Aquatic Accent To Any Space. This Active Item Adorns Your Personal Space With Gently Animated Glowing Kelp. Glows In The Dark!|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:6
069F6CDB-9B85405F-AE510D01-0501CC03|kName|kDesc|Mahogany Retro Speaker Left|The Left Mahogany Retro Speaker From The Loot™ Home Entertainment Collection.|Furniture/Appliance|© 2009 Loot™|HDK_1.3.2.16.BETA1|NOT-RWRD|Res:2
06B9F020-A2ED4804-B7DD7766-E670B969|kName|kDesc|Superhero Madhouse - Arcade Cabinet|The SuperHero Madhouse Arcade Cabinet, Complete With Exclusive Mad Hero Themed Clothing For Anyone Who Purchases The Cabinet. To Get The Clothing, Place The Cabinet In Your Apartment And Play The Game. Any Visitors To Your Personal Space Can Play The Full Game, Post High-scores, And Gain Trophies In The In-game Trophy Cabinet. Can You Escape From The Madhouse...or Just Your Mind? After Placing Your Cabinet And Playing It For The First Time You Will Receive The Follow Items: 1. Superhero Madhouse - T-Shirt - Male 2. Superhero Madhouse - T-Shirt - Female 3. Superhero Madhouse - Fleece - Male 4. Superhero Madhouse - Fleece - Female 5. Superhero Madhouse - Hat - Male 6. Superhero Madhouse - Hat - Female|Furniture/Appliance|VEEMEE|HDK_1.60.0.450.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:3
06EC8A76-E4494459-8E4BF8F5-2FDA6518|kName|kDesc|Weekly ToroStation TV-San|This TV Can Run Weekly ToroStation|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.3.5.120.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:3
072B3E7E-44C34795-AC05A2B5-F3D027D5|kName|kDesc|Jessamine's Doll|This Active Item Will Release Jessamine.|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.65.0.139.BETA|LUA-REWARD|Res:6
078369D6-C0074A3E-A88119E5-6A152E48|name|description|Ghostbusters™ Coffee Maker|A Decorative Ghostbusters™ Ornament For PlayStation®Home Personal Spaces.|Furniture/Appliance|© 2009 Columbia Pictures Industries, Inc.|HDK_1.3.6.22.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:2
07EC34C7-67984277-916874A1-E24A9A98|kName|kDesc|Scribble Shooter|Do You Have What It Takes To Be The Savior Of The PlayStation®Home Universe? Take Down The Evil Alien Hordes In This Frenzied Shoot 'em Up Arcade Game. (Comes With 10 FREE PlayStation®Home Rewards That Are Unlocked During Gameplay)|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.52.0.2.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:3
0854B4A0-5F984F6F-8E57B990-48D1E306|kName|kDesc|LOOT™ Reel-to-reel|Fill The Air With Music! A Must Have For Any Private Or Clubhouse Space - Invite Your Friends Over And Get The Party Started! Enjoy Endless Streams Featuring Pop, Rock, Dance, And Talk. The LOOT™ Radio Delivers Real Music To The Comfort Of Your PlayStation®Home Personal Space! PLEASE READ BEFORE YOU PURCHASE Due To Contractual And Rights Agreements, Some Channels Are Nation Specific. RadioIO Is Only Available In The United States And Canada. In Addition, Due To Rights Issues, Countries May Not Receive The Same Content Selections Within The Channels. Only One Radio Or Television Can Be Active At A Time. The LOOT Radio Will Work In Any Private Space, UNLESS The Space Comes With A Tv Or Radio You Cannot Turn Off.|Furniture/Appliance|© LOOT™|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:48
085BD9FF-46DF4E15-A21F18FD-4CA2AA7F|kName|kDesc|Sega Renegade Ops: Preboot - Explosion!|KABOOM! An Exploding Visual Effect For Your Apartment.|Furniture/Appliance|VEEMEE|HDK_1.66.0.144.PUB|AUTO-REWARD|Res:9
087F1CA5-A88E43EF-B324493F-CEEF45DD|kName|kDesc|Apartment Pets: Li'l Ninjas|See Your Apartment Come To Life With These Fantastic Free-roaming Pets. For Best Results, Try Combining Them With The Other Apartment Pets Now Available From NDreams. This Is An Active Item.|Furniture/Appliance|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:17
08A8B58C-4B5340B9-8E742D4F-9878EDF0|kName|kDesc|Doctor Who TARDIS|TARDIS™ Stands For Time And Relative Dimension In Space. The TARDIS™ Looks Like A 1950s Wooden Police Phone Box On The Outside, But Its Far Bigger On The Inside. Amaze Your Friends When They Discover The Wonder Of Time Lord Technology. Doctor Who Logo © 2013 And TM BBC ©. Licensed By © BBC Worldwide Ltd.|Furniture/Appliance|BBC Worldwide Limited|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|AUTO-REWARD|Res:9
08C21A20-0E0243AA-A4A6FE9D-2DAD710E|kName|kDesc|Forsaken Planet – Cow (Animated)|LOOT Wants You To Have A Cow. Mooooooo! Looking For Even Sweeter Forsaken Planet Deals And In-game Rewards? Check Out The Forsaken Planet Bundles In The LOOT™ Store!|Furniture/Appliance|©LOOT™|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|AUTO-REWARD|Res:6
08DACB22-7BAE47DA-AA7DD3E4-824DCF02|kName|kDesc|MyBedroom - Black Marble - Bed|An Interactive MyBedroom Bed With Sleeping Animation.|Furniture/Appliance|VEEMEE|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:18
0916D2FB-8BBE4CB6-AC3C4EE1-8904C81F|AmericanPoolName|AmericanPoolDesc|Judge Dredd Pool Table|A Judge Dredd Pool Table, Ideal For Any Apartment. This Table Comes With Both Eight Ball And Nine Ball Versions Of Pool. The Game Can Be Played With Two Players, Or In A Single Player Practice Mode.|Furniture/Appliance|VEEMEE|HDK_1.60.0.450.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:55
093226CC-80FB40AE-848E59D1-22860DBD|kName|kDesc|50s Diner - Mini Table Jukebox|Select Your Favourite Songs From The Comfort Of Your Booth.|Furniture/Appliance|VEEMEE|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:27
09FBC4A4-DBD94A19-80B1A44B-22311AD2|kName|kDesc|Ghost-O-Vision|When Activated, This Active Item Gives You The Power Of Night Vision – Revealing The Hidden Spirits Lurking Within Your Space.|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:20
0A0286E5-21AA489D-A2819CCE-A7799C10|kName|kDesc|Drop Science Orange Soda Boom Box (Active Item)|Fresh Beats With Some Drop Science Style.|Furniture/Appliance|Lockwood|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:10
0A644657-F92E4FD2-A8013551-D917BF93|kName|kDesc|3D Printer|Experience The Latest In Virtual-to-real Technology With The VEEMEE 3D Printer. Place In Your Personal Space And Choose From A Wide Selection Of Exclusive Virtual Items To Print Out For You And Your Friends. VEEMEE 3D Printer Vouchers Can Be Purchased From The Printer Or From The VEEMEE Store.|Furniture/Appliance|VEEMEE|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:75
0A710F6B-8C104AD9-9F0B4765-B031ADB7|kName|kDesc|Harem Pillows - Mystic (Active Object)|Elegant Furnishings Fit For A King. Or Queen.|Furniture/Appliance|Lockwood|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|LUA-REWARD|Res:28
0A997BAE-594C4E89-B1E71A35-E0A27561|kName|kDesc|Xi: Continuum - Snowcrash Stereo|Bring The Continuum's Nightlife Into Your Apartment With This Thumping Stereo.|Furniture/Appliance|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:4
0AD31631-1D3D45EB-8BF9AF6D-456C7B4A|kName|kDesc|22'' LOOT™ Gold EOD TV - Flatscreen|For Gamers Who Have It All, Here Is A Special Edition Gold EOD TV That Let's You Watch Full Length Movies, TV Episodes, Live Shows And More With Your Friends In PlayStation®Home! The LOOT™ Entertainment On Demand TV Will Work In Any Private Space Unless The Space Comes With A Video Screen You Cant Turn Off, It Does Not Include Streaming Radio Or Audio-only Content. Now All You Need To Do Is Invite Your Friends Over, Pull Out The Popcorn And Make The Most Important Decision Of All: What Will You Watch First!? PLEASE READ BEFORE YOU PURCHASE: Due To Contractual And Rights Agreements, Some EOD Channels Are Nation Specific. Crackle Content Is ONLY Available In United States, Canada, United Kingdom, And Australia. RadioIO Is ONLY Available In The United States And Canada. In Addition, Due To Rights Issues, Countries May Not Receive The Same Content Selections Within The Channels. Only One TV Can Be Active At A Time. The LOOT™ EOD Will Work In Any Private Space, UNLESS The Space Comes With A Video Screen You Cannot Turn Off.|Furniture/Appliance|© LOOT™|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:42
0ADDEF74-A732487E-9DE97221-AAC9625A|kName|kDesc|Lunar Lander Cocktail Cabinet|Atari's Lunar Lander Arcade Game In Table Top Form. Lunar Lander® ©2012 Atari Interactive Inc. All Rights Reserved. Lunar Lander® Is A Trademark Owned By Atari Interactive Inc. FOCAL Emulation Technology ©2009-2012 Code Mystics Inc.|Furniture/Appliance|Atari Interactive Inc.|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:3
0B12CD48-51304DAF-B8785DC6-31F5DDE4|name|description|80s Television Green Screen|A Decorative Non-funtional Ghostbusters™ Prop For PlayStation®Home Personal Spaces.|Furniture/Appliance|© 2009 Columbia Pictures Industries, Inc.|HDK_1.3.6.22.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:2
0B25F05D-B12B4356-891DB76F-B7FC0316|Darts Item Name|Darts Item Desc|Darts Game|This Fantastic Dartboard Comes With 4 Different Game Types. Play 301, 501, Round The Clock And Killer With Up To 3 Friends. Previously Only Available In The London Pub Apartment, This Dartboard Can Now Be Placed In Any Personal Space - Bullseye!|Furniture/Appliance|VEEMEE|HDK_1.60.0.450.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:38
0B3FA2A3-5F3E4530-8B79E24E-F945EA1F|kName|kDesc|Water Bed|A Water Bed That Turns Dreams Into Reality, Whether You Sleep Alone Or With Someone Else. *A Gift From GZ Gift|Furniture/Appliance|Granzella Inc.|HDK_1.82.0.17.PUB|LUA-REWARD|Res:183
0B43F46B-EDB84DC6-A464FE08-22E2F8B1|kName|kDesc|Easter Basket|This Active Item Contains A Special Gift For You And Your Friends.|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:3
0B951751-EA194FFD-87980D6E-6D001D7C|kName|kDesc|Sweetie Peep - Heavy Pet - Vavoom Violet|Sweetie Pie Will Melt Your Heart As Your Favorite New Peep! Bring Sweetie Pie With You Into Your Apartment And Let The Fun Begin. Control Her With Custom Animations And Special Peep Moves!|Furniture/Appliance|Heavy Water|HDK_1.66.0.144.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:25
0C3B6092-33BA4CE3-B35897CA-7B59021D|kName|kDesc|NDreams Clocks: Victorian|A Beautiful Clock Designed To Place In Your Personal Apartment. Time Is Set According To Your PlayStation®3 Settings. Note - This Is An Appliance.|Furniture/Appliance|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:9
0C6759B9-13534767-85BFCF7D-2F7D0CB7|kName|kDesc|LOOT™ Minibox|Fill The Air With Music! A Must Have For Any Private Or Clubhouse Space - Invite Your Friends Over And Get The Party Started! Enjoy Endless Streams Featuring Pop, Rock, Dance, And Talk. The LOOT™ Radio Delivers Real Music To The Comfort Of Your PlayStation®Home Personal Space! PLEASE READ BEFORE YOU PURCHASE Due To Contractual And Rights Agreements, Some Channels Are Nation Specific. RadioIO Is Only Available In The United States And Canada. In Addition, Due To Rights Issues, Countries May Not Receive The Same Content Selections Within The Channels. Only One Radio Or Television Can Be Active At A Time. The LOOT Radio Will Work In Any Private Space, UNLESS The Space Comes With A Tv Or Radio You Cannot Turn Off.|Furniture/Appliance|© LOOT™|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:44
0C7057C4-1F9740F2-A721D0D6-4BED221C|kName|kDesc|DIY Racer (incl. Blue Car)|DIY Racer Is A Fun Mini-game That Turns Your Apartment Into An Exciting Race Track! Use Your Existing Furniture Or Our Specially Designed Furniture To Create Jumps, Bridges, And Tunnels To Create The Coolest Track You Can Imagine. Invite Your Friends And Race Against Them On The Track That You Designed! Do Tricks To Unlock Some Cool Stuff! This Mini-game Includes The Flaming Blue RC Car!|Furniture/Appliance|Codeglue B.V.|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:85
0CA0BFF6-04094837-AD6D9E91-45A20FF5|kName|kDesc|French Chateau Bed|This Royal Looking Bed Is A Great Choice For Anyone. This Is An Active Item.|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:19
0CF1F556-A3C645BC-82A29E68-31C8DD32|kName|kDesc|8 Bit Weapon|Play Songs By The Band 8 Bit Weapon. Inspired By Classic Video Game Soundtracks And Electronic Music From The 70s And 80s, 8 Bit Weapon Delivers A Sound That Is As Unique As It Is Original. Clever Melodies, Nostalgic Atmosphere, And Energetic Beats Create A Decidedly Modern Sound While Maintaining A Fun, Lo-tech Aesthetic.|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.40.0.265.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:13
0DB076F0-04E2469C-BB855924-C078870E|kName|kDesc|3D Printer|Experience The Latest In Virtual-to-real Technology With The VEEMEE 3D Printer. Place In Your Personal Space And Choose From A Wide Selection Of Exclusive Virtual Items To Print Out For You And Your Friends. VEEMEE 3D Printer Vouchers Can Be Purchased From The Printer Or From The VEEMEE Store.|Furniture/Appliance|VEEMEE|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:75
0DBAAF80-F1FE473E-B31CB735-CBB1F8A7|kName|kDesc|Light Rig|Light Rig|Furniture/Appliance|EA SPORTS|HDK_1.3.0.130.BETA2|AUTO-REWARD|Res:2
0DE4872F-D6024A69-8EBC4912-862C42B5|kName|kDesc|GROW HOME : Blue Delphinium|Grow Your Own Plantlife And Show Off Your Green Fingered Skills!|Furniture/Appliance|VEEMEE|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:55
0E6D3E3C-E93642EF-A55522B6-95E2E5B9|kName|kDesc|NDreams Luxury Hot Tub (Prestige)|This Luxurious, Beautifully Sculpted Hot Tub Is Perfect For Your Apartment. Hang Out With Up To Five People And Choose From A Variety Of Coloured Lights To Set The Mood. This Appliance Uses 6 Furniture Slots.|Furniture/Appliance|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:6
0EA31107-DA1F47B2-AB8C7BB8-3C683615|kName|kDesc|The Love Tub|This Heart Shaped Jacuzzi Active Item Has Room For 4 Avatars. You Can Also Customize The Bubbles!|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:19
0EB9222F-0F4A410A-89271D55-4882BA47|kName|kDesc|Bird Perch|This Active Item Livens Up Your Apartment With Animated Birds.|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:13
0EBE7CDB-FF6B4C4A-A98C17BB-00876CAB|kName|kDesc|40'' LOOT™ EOD TV - Wall Mounted|PLEASE READ BEFORE YOU PURCHASE: Due To Contractual And Rights Agreements, Some EOD Channels Are Nation Specific. Crackle Content Is ONLY Available In United States, Canada, United Kingdom, And Australia. RadioIO Is ONLY Available In The United States And Canada. In Addition, Due To Rights Issues, Countries May Not Receive The Same Content Selections Within The Channels. Only One TV Can Be Active At A Time. The LOOT EOD Will Work In Any Private Space, UNLESS The Space Comes With A Video Screen You Cannot Turn Off. Watch Full Length Movies, TV Episodes, Live Shows And More With Your Friends In PlayStation®Home! The LOOT™ Entertainment On Demand TV Will Work In Any Private Space Unless The Space Comes With A Video Screen You Cant Turn Off, It Does Not Include Streaming Radio Or Audio-only Content. This Bundle-exclusive Wall Mounted TV Works With The FREE LOOT™ TV Wall Mount (found In The LOOT™ Store.) Simply Hang The Mount On The Wall Like A Picture Frame Then Hook Your Wall Mounted EOD TV On It. Decorating Has Never Been So Easy!|Furniture/Appliance|© LOOT™|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:42
0EDA3044-871E4196-879B295E-6FC74717|kName|kDesc|Escape Earth Mode: Horde|Escape Virus Mode: Horde Is An Arcade Cabinet Where You Can Play. You Can Get Home Reward If You Fulfill Certain Conditions.|Furniture/Appliance|O-Two Inc.|HDK_1.60.0.450.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:3
0F284B1F-6ECB4785-A8500D2C-C8FBC6D2|kName|kDesc|Centipede Arcade Cabinet|Atari's Centipede Arcade Game In A Full-sized Classic Arcade Cabinet. Centipede® ©2012 Atari Interactive Inc. All Rights Reserved. Centipede® Is A Trademark Owned By Atari Interactive Inc. FOCAL Emulation Technology ©2009-2012 Code Mystics Inc.|Furniture/Appliance|Atari Interactive Inc.|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:3
0F42B5B4-F6894C28-B65B4995-F62B55BF|kName|kDesc|Tumble Weed Cannon|The Greatest Item In A Cowboy's Arsenal: Perfect For When Your Friend Makes A Terrible Joke! This Fantastic Appliance Will Fire Tumble Weed Across Your Apartment And Help Create A Wild West Atmosphere With Its Great Ambient Sound Effects.|Furniture/Appliance|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.52.0.2.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:6
1016B4BC-A0C44558-90E24029-8190457D|kName|kDesc|Lock-a-doodle|Lock-a-doodle Is A Fun Social Drawing Game. Create Doodles For Your Friends To Guess, Accept Random Challenges From Other Players, Or Unlock Doodle Mode And Doodle To Your Heart's Content. The More Lock-a-doodle Doodle Packs You Own, The More Stickers, Colours And Shapes At Your Disposal For Creating Incredible Works Of Art! Includes Your First Doodle Pack For FREE!|Furniture/Appliance|Lockwood|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:108
101D4E13-153F4C56-B4A1A1D2-371B2B7A|kName|kDesc|Clusterpuck|Clusterpuck Is An Old-school Arcade Game Designed For The Next Generation. This Arcade Cabinet Comes With The Clusterpuck Game, Two Awesome chip-step Tracks By Bankai, And Several Rad Prizes You Can Earn.|Furniture/Appliance|Codename: Ihobo|HDK_1.60.0.450.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:3
1038B1F1-D9F3480B-91125EB4-882567C7|kName|kDesc|Sneak Attack|This Secret Audio Trigger System Gives You The Power To Place 5 Hidden Triggers Around Your Personal Space To Surprise Your Friends When They Get Near One! This Free Item Comes With An Elephant Trumpeting Track. Purchase More Sound Banks To Add To Your Sneaky Repertoire.|Furniture/Appliance|Mass Media|HDK_1.3.6.22.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:29
10AB3974-03674ECC-8A501243-177F3E64|ToroKotatsu Name|ToroKotatsu Desc|TORO Woodgrain Heated Table|Don't Flip It Over, Now!|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.3.6.22.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:2
10FC0E07-A660468D-A4DA91DB-0DC8EF0E|kName|kDesc|Werewolf Gravestone|Awarded To The Community For Recruiting 1,000,000 Werewolves In Serenity Plaza.|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|LUA-REWARD|Res:20
1120A908-A27742FD-9DC57C0E-D5838C5E|kName|kDesc|The FREE LOOT™ Radio|This FREE Version Of The LOOT™ Radio Only Plays The LOOT™ Channel, Use It In Order To Double Check If This Kind Of Active Item Is Compatible With Your Favorite Private Space Or Club House. Then Visit The Store For The LOOT Radio Bundle, Packed With Nine Different Radio Styles, Including The Exclusive LOOT Jukebox Version. Due To Contractual And Rights Agreements, Some Channels Are Nation Specific. RadioIO Is Only Available In The United States And Canada. In Addition, Due To Rights Issues, Countries May Not Receive The Same Content Selections Within The Channels. Only One Radio Or Television Can Be Active At A Time. The LOOT™ Radio Will Work In Any Private Space Unless The Space Comes With A Video Or Audio Screen You Cant Turn Off.|Furniture/Appliance|© LOOT™|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:46
1145B316-B2084297-B313485F-EADDD188|kName|kDesc|Personal Blackjack Table|Take The Casino's Blackjack Experience Home With You With This Personal Table. All You Have To Do Is Place This Active Item In Any Space And You And Your Friends Can See Who Can Beat The Dealer At His Own Game. Taken Directly From The Floors Of Paradise Springs, This Five Player Table Will Have Your Friends Constantly Knocking At Your Door. Each Player Starts Out With A Set Amount Of Chips. If You Run Out Then Just Sit Back Down And You'll Get A Whole New Set Of Holdings. Treat Your Friends To This Endless Blackjack Experience. This Is An Animated Active Item.|Furniture/Appliance|Digital Leisure|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:201
11837619-BBE14BA4-9511F580-379727E3|kName|kDesc|Playground Boombox|Plays The Music You Find In The Playground Space.|Furniture/Appliance|MakerXX|HDK_1.3.6.22.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:10
1185F35D-DF3E40CA-AC738EE4-488533E3|kName|kDesc|Asteroids Cocktail Cabinet|Atari's Asteroids Arcade Game In Table Top Form. Asteroids® ©2012 Atari Interactive Inc. All Rights Reserved. Asteroids® Is A Trademark Owned By Atari Interactive Inc. FOCAL Emulation Technology ©2009-2012 Code Mystics Inc.|Furniture/Appliance|Atari Interactive Inc.|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:3
11985565-99E146EC-9503F44F-F779784E|kName|kDesc|Sodium Fuselage Active Object Bed|Who Says Reclaimed Heavy Metal Can't Be Luxurious And Blissfully Comfortable? Rewarded For Your Impressive Triangulation Skills In The Sodium Blimp Personal Space.|Furniture/Appliance|Lockwood|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|LUA-REWARD|Res:32
11A5346E-71BE11E1-97EB0022-19291EC2|kName|kDesc|Modernist Double Bed - Organic (Active Object)|Clean Modern Lines With A Touch Of Romance! Lockwood Beds Are Active Objects With A Realistic 'lie Down' Animation, So Lie Back And Relax On This Dreamy, Comfortable Bed. Owners Of The Cucumber Modernist Double Bed - Organic Can Purchase The Modernist Double Bed - Organic (Active Object) At A Discounted Price.|Furniture/Appliance|Lockwood|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:32
11A8AF10-579A40CF-883AD921-7C6AE366|kName|kDesc|Apartment Pets: Kittens|See Your Apartment Come To Life With These Fantastic Free-roaming Pets. For Best Results, Try Combining Them With The Other Apartment Pets Now Available From NDreams. This Is An Active Item.|Furniture/Appliance|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:16
12D36591-9E2E44D2-A22CB500-780AC0DB|kName|kDesc|Projector|A Projector From The Loot™ Home Entertainment Collection.|Furniture/Appliance|© 2009 Loot™|HDK_1.3.2.16.BETA1|NOT-RWRD|Res:2
12F9791B-CF3744C5-999B30F5-7D917C19|kName|kDesc|TV|Exclusive High-definition TV Taken From The Assassin's Hideout.|Furniture/Appliance|Ubisoft|HDK_1.3.2.27.PUB|LUA-REWARD|Res:2
1306D5AE-EC514074-ACF5562D-310EE603|kName|kDesc|Simple Picnic Table|This Active Item Seats 6 Avatars For A Delightful Picnic.|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:10
13125B7C-35F64B34-8717D44E-1A73E16D|kName|kDesc|Up-Chuck Peep - Heavy Pet - Pasty White|Up-Chuck Is One Wild And Crazy Guy And The Life Of Every Party! Bring Up-Chuck With You Into Your Apartment And Get The Party Started! You Can Control Him With Custom Animations And Special Peep Moves!|Furniture/Appliance|Heavy Water|HDK_1.66.0.144.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:25
144D13F7-EB574A85-8526A0C7-D1913709|kName|kDesc|LOOT™ Tiki Torch - Double|Light Up The Party With This Tiki Double-torch From LOOT™ Entertainment!|Furniture/Appliance|© LOOT™|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:9
145130DB-C1A744C2-ADB31C89-FC6A2CFA|kName|kDesc|Reclining Deck Armchair|Deck Armchair Advanced Furniture For Laying Down In Various Positions.|Furniture/Appliance|Granzella Inc.|HDK_1.82.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:107
1453FE23-DFF5483F-A07BEFC4-122AC7C8|kName|kDesc|Magic Cauldron|The Magic Cauldron Can Give You Advice Or Even Tell The Future. You Ask It Yes Or No Questions About What You Should Do Or What Is Going To Happen. Then The Cauldron Will Give You Your Answer.|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.41.0.37.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:12
14564B3F-0BA444C1-B5BC1539-4F793E37|kName|kDesc|Stainless Steel Stand Mixer|Get Cooking With This Interactive Stand Mixer!|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:13
1544E54F-4A124BFC-BC340525-5770C40E|kName|kDesc|Animated Snake In Terrarium|Sam The Snake Might Not Be The Most Popular Pet, But That's Only Because He Doesn't Play Well With Other Pets. Especially Rodents.|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.41.0.37.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:8
161972EC-CA4441F1-96CD04DA-1270A899|kName|kDesc|Timepieces - Torsion Clock|Always Know What The Time Is With This Working Clock. Exclusive To The VEEMEE 3D Printer. The Time Is Automatically Set Using The Time On Your PlayStation®3. ※ Active Items Provide More Functionality Than Normal Items. You May Only Place Limited Numbers Of The Active Items In Your Apartment Or Clubhouse At Any Time.|Furniture/Appliance|VEEMEE|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|LUA-REWARD|Res:10
166DEA16-6573473C-ABE94453-A58EEF19|kName|kDesc|Lamp Of The Deluge|This Active Item Will Unleash An Epic Storm Within Your Apartment.|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.65.0.139.BETA|LUA-REWARD|Res:16
167B79B9-A4044E6F-9DEE1E07-641B28D6|kName|kDesc|Ooblag|Played In Casinos Across The Galaxy, The Exciting Dice Game Is Now Here For You To Try. When You Light Up All The Letters, Don't Forget To Shout OOBLAG!|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.50.0.238.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:103
168E48CE-2C194B6B-BE15B739-2D1E68C6|kName|kDesc|Blueprint: Punch Ball|Watch Your Avatar Become A Boxing Pro With This Fantastic Active Item. Watch As Your Avatar Punches And Weaves Their Way Through A Hard Workout. This Item Is Recommended For Use With Blueprint: Home But Can Be Used In Any Personal Space.|Furniture/Appliance|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:11
16A6DDCF-A49F4239-A4B08532-88CB2998|kName|kDesc|Mariachi Meercats|This Active Item Creates A Trio Of Mariachi Meercats To Entertain You.|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:23
16B85CF5-A31E4248-B2FDBE6C-A92E7DE9|kName|kDesc|Chim Peep - Heavy Pet - Red On White|More Fun Than A Barrel Of Monkeys Is Chim Peep! Dressed To The Nines In His Monkey Suit, Bring Him Into Your Apartment And Get Down To Business! You Can Control Him With Custom Animations And Special Peep Moves!|Furniture/Appliance|Heavy Water|HDK_1.66.0.144.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:25
16C721B2-6F7040D6-B3436C12-3C6FB486|kName|kDesc|Prosthetic Records Boombox|Check Out Tracks From One Of The World's Preeminent Heavy Metal Labels, Prosthetic Records. Featured Are The Classic Thrash Metal Sounds Of HOLY GRAIL, From Los Angeles, California. This Is The Boombox For All You MetalHeads Out There!|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.52.0.2.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:15
17A5E34E-CB9F47FB-85F5D294-02DB77B7|kName|kDesc|Timepieces - Ebony Grandfather Clock|Always Know What The Time Is With This Working Clock. Exclusive To The VEEMEE 3D Printer. The Time Is Automatically Set Using The Time On Your PlayStation®3. ※ Active Items Provide More Functionality Than Normal Items. You May Only Place Limited Numbers Of The Active Items In Your Apartment Or Clubhouse At Any Time.|Furniture/Appliance|VEEMEE|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|LUA-REWARD|Res:10
17E7C0FC-095F48F0-973FDD10-484F103A|kName|kDesc|Bunny Den|This Active Item Releases Bunnies That Wander Around Your Apartment.|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:13
18068613-29CD4761-A4286CF1-86B67FC0|kName|kDesc|Thanksgiving Dining Table - Rustic - 10 Person|What's Thanksgiving Without The Dinner? Entertain Your Friends And Family In The Privacy Of Your Own Personal Space With The VEEMEE Thanksgiving Personal Dining Experience. Guests Can Receive Up To 3 Reward Items. This Table Has 10 Seats. Owning This Table Grants Access To The Big Thanksgiving Dinner Table In Acorn Meadows Park. ※ Active Items Provide More Functionality Than Normal Items. You May Only Place Limited Numbers Of The Active Items In Your Apartment Or Clubhouse At Any Time.|Furniture/Appliance|VEEMEE|HDK_1.82.0.17.PUB|LUA-REWARD|Res:60
1844E49F-109E4AF8-A655288B-D1F94797|kName|kDesc|Romantic Mood Vase|This Active Item Allows You To Place Tea Lights, Roses And Sprinkle Rose Petals To Create The Perfect Romantic Setting.|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:22
184B1B07-D2F74DE2-BFCAEAAB-2D6E0131|kName|kDesc|EmoRay BoomBox|Experience The Original Music From Emo Ray Outside Of The Game With This Boombox. This BoomBox Comes Preloaded With Six Feet Down. You Can Earn The Rest Of The Songs In The Game By Completeing The Following Tasks: • Complete Chapters 1-4 In Story Mode To Receive Wallflowers In Bloom • Complete Mission Pack 1 And Mission Pack 2 To Receive Love Hurts • Complete Chapters 5-8 In Story Mode To Receive Change The World • Complete Mission Pack 3 And Mission Pack 4 To Receive Making Out Every Track Comes With Vocals Or The Instrumental Track From The Game. Don't Forget To Check Out The Band Who Made These Songs: So Long Davey!|Furniture/Appliance|Heavy Water|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|LUA-REWARD|Res:41
1865E768-EBD54172-920F987F-509C4377|kName|kDesc|Baron's Eggcellent Plan (Active Object)|Lucy Goose Just Wants To Sit On Her Nest In Peace, But That Naughty Rabbit Baron Von Eggenschtealer Keeps Running Off With Her Eggs. Worse Still, He's Not Even Careful With Them - He Drops Them Everywhere! Will You Collect Them For Her? She's Known To Reward Her Helpers Generously...|Furniture/Appliance|Lockwood|HDK_1.50.0.238.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:79
189D33F1-79B246F2-B401BD50-1470D3B0|kName|kDesc|Asteroids Arcade Cabinet|Atari's Asteroids Arcade Game In A Full-sized Classic Arcade Cabinet. Asteroids® ©2012 Atari Interactive Inc. All Rights Reserved. Asteroids® Is A Trademark Owned By Atari Interactive Inc. FOCAL Emulation Technology ©2009-2012 Code Mystics Inc.|Furniture/Appliance|Atari Interactive Inc.|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:3
191D3DC5-2A554B9C-96B46068-5A030EA1|kName|kDesc|80'' LOOT™ Gold EOD TV - Flatscreen|For Gamers Who Have It All, Here Is A Special Edition Gold EOD TV That Let's You Watch Full Length Movies, TV Episodes, Live Shows And More With Your Friends In PlayStation®Home! The LOOT™ Entertainment On Demand TV Will Work In Any Private Space Unless The Space Comes With A Video Screen You Cant Turn Off, It Does Not Include Streaming Radio Or Audio-only Content. Now All You Need To Do Is Invite Your Friends Over, Pull Out The Popcorn And Make The Most Important Decision Of All: What Will You Watch First!? PLEASE READ BEFORE YOU PURCHASE: Due To Contractual And Rights Agreements, Some EOD Channels Are Nation Specific. Crackle Content Is ONLY Available In United States, Canada, United Kingdom, And Australia. RadioIO Is ONLY Available In The United States And Canada. In Addition, Due To Rights Issues, Countries May Not Receive The Same Content Selections Within The Channels. Only One TV Can Be Active At A Time. The LOOT™ EOD Will Work In Any Private Space, UNLESS The Space Comes With A Video Screen You Cannot Turn Off.|Furniture/Appliance|© LOOT™|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:42
1973D908-EC7146C7-86CEDBF2-B0C4F633|kName|kDesc|White Tower Speaker|The White Tower Speaker From The Loot™ Home Entertainment Collection.|Furniture/Appliance|© 2009 Loot™|HDK_1.3.2.16.BETA1|NOT-RWRD|Res:2
1A8100DE-702B4E50-AB0F898F-5765BF16|kName|kDesc|Techno Peep - Heavy Pet - Robot Red|Move To The Groove With Techno Peep! As The Hottest Gadget On The Market, You Can Bring Him Into Your Apartment For Hours Of Fun! You Can Control Him With Custom Animations And Special Peep Moves!|Furniture/Appliance|Heavy Water|HDK_1.66.0.144.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:25
1B0567CF-DFBE4BDA-BBFA203F-A4513470|kName|kDesc|Animated Rabbit|This Tiny Little Fur Ball's Name Is Baxter, Quiet And Attentive, He Hops Around His Small Cage Rummaging For Food.|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.41.0.37.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:9
1B15ACB5-D956469D-811820F4-5A5E2DEA|kName|kDesc|Beach Mat (Yellow)|Yellow Mat For Laying Down In Various Poses. This Is An Advanced Furniture Item With Added Features And Animations. The Amount Of Items Of This Type That Can Be Placed Is Limited.|Furniture/Appliance|Granzella Inc.|HDK_1.65.0.139.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:107
1B6E65E5-8390492E-B5536444-054BC609|kName|kDesc|Beach Chair (Wooden)|Wooden Chair For Laying Down In Various Poses. This Is An Advanced Furniture Item With Added Features And Animations. The Amount Of Items Of This Type That Can Be Placed Is Limited.|Furniture/Appliance|Granzella Inc.|HDK_1.65.0.139.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:107
1B755292-4AF74467-95CA7C09-ED8C0CB2|kName|kDesc|Hammer Virus|This Arcade Cabinet Can Play Hammer Virus. You Can Get Home Reward If You Fulfill Certain Conditions.|Furniture/Appliance|O-Two Inc.|HDK_1.60.0.450.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:3
1B7B6ABF-517340F7-BB2820BE-20ABEC84|kName|kDesc|MyKitchen - Toaster - Gloss Black|An Interactive Toaster For Your Kitchen. Exclusive To The VEEMEE 3D Printer. ※ Active Items Provide More Functionality Than Normal Items. You May Only Place Limited Numbers Of The Active Items In Your Apartment Or Clubhouse At Any Time.|Furniture/Appliance|VEEMEE|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|LUA-REWARD|Res:5
1C4B7D20-05FC416E-8AE3B39D-C0370F8C|kName|kDesc|Holiday Decoration Kit|Get Your Space Ready For The Holidays With This Decoration Kit. Place Up To 35 Ornaments In Any Personal Space For Only 8 Furniture Slots!|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:54
1CB1A0FB-9CA94077-AE025DCC-8C83AABA|kName|kDesc|DIY Racer (incl. Silver Car)|DIY Racer Is A Fun Mini-game That Turns Your Apartment Into An Exciting Race Track! Use Your Existing Furniture Or Our Specially Designed Furniture To Create Jumps, Bridges, And Tunnels To Create The Coolest Track You Can Imagine. Invite Your Friends And Race Against Them On The Track That You Designed! Do Tricks To Unlock Some Cool Stuff! This Mini-game Includes The Hot Silver RC Car!|Furniture/Appliance|Codeglue B.V.|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:85
1CF4F279-61A64AA9-AA94AA77-6C18160D|kName|kDesc|Beach Chair (Blue)|Blue Chair For Laying Down In Various Poses. This Is An Advanced Furniture Item With Added Features And Animations. The Amount Of Items Of This Type That Can Be Placed Is Limited.|Furniture/Appliance|Granzella Inc.|HDK_1.65.0.139.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:107
1DCF4485-ABED49D7-A51742AD-5B0ED08D|kName|kDesc|Sample: Arcade Cabinet|An Arcade Cabinet To Be Used When Testing Arcade Game Furniture.|Furniture/Appliance|Granzella Inc.|HDK_1.55.0.155.BETA2|NOT-RWRD|Res:3
1E9342C5-65D840C0-BE65EF30-22F28F0A|kName|kDesc|22'' LOOT™ EOD TV - Wall Mounted|PLEASE READ BEFORE YOU PURCHASE: Due To Contractual And Rights Agreements, Some EOD Channels Are Nation Specific. Crackle Content Is ONLY Available In United States, Canada, United Kingdom, And Australia. RadioIO Is ONLY Available In The United States And Canada. In Addition, Due To Rights Issues, Countries May Not Receive The Same Content Selections Within The Channels. Only One TV Can Be Active At A Time. The LOOT EOD Will Work In Any Private Space, UNLESS The Space Comes With A Video Screen You Cannot Turn Off. Watch Full Length Movies, TV Episodes, Live Shows And More With Your Friends In PlayStation®Home! The LOOT™ Entertainment On Demand TV Will Work In Any Private Space Unless The Space Comes With A Video Screen You Cant Turn Off, It Does Not Include Streaming Radio Or Audio-only Content. This Bundle-exclusive Wall Mounted TV Works With The FREE LOOT™ TV Wall Mount (found In The LOOT™ Store.) Simply Hang The Mount On The Wall Like A Picture Frame Then Hook Your Wall Mounted EOD TV On It. Decorating Has Never Been So Easy!|Furniture/Appliance|© LOOT™|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:42
1EA9B126-1AE648A6-A6776F91-A6228701|kName|kDesc|Apartment Android: Amber (Premium)|This Flirty Female Android Will Ensure You're Never Alone In Your Apartment! She'll Roam Around, Chat, And Even React To Some Of Your Actions. Amber Has Additional Sexy Animations And Some Seductive Small Talk. This Is An Active Item. ※Active Items Provide More Functionality Than Normal Items. You May Only Place Limited Numbers Of The Active Items In Your Apartment Or Clubhouse At Any Time.|Furniture/Appliance|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:22
1EADEE01-24134103-AE659364-7BAD4605|kName|kDesc|Medium Aquarium|A Perfect Fit For Every Room! This Tank Comes With A Collection Of 5 Fish And 6 Decorations. It Holds Up To 15 Small Or Medium Fish And 10 Small Or Medium Decorations. To Get Your Tank Started, Included With This Purchase Is The Medium Fish Pack And The Decoration Plant Pack. The Fish Included Are: Saddleback Clownfish, Cave Tetra, Green Swordtail, Bubble Eye Goldfish And Flowerhorn Cichlid. Plant Life Included: Flaming Myriophyllum, Torch Coral, Blue Ludwigia, Crimson Hygrophila, Green Ludwigia And Seaweed. That's Over Ten Items Included With Your Purchase! This Is An Animated Active Item.|Furniture/Appliance|Digital Leisure|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:584
1EF8B929-FCA940E7-8F7C6114-96CBF49B|kName|kDesc|Popcorn Popper|No Home Is Complete Without The Popcorn Popper From LOOT™.|Furniture/Appliance|© LOOT™|HDK_1.66.0.144.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:2
1F82449F-70A4419F-924F6415-801FBD9E|kName|kDesc|Flaming Skull Pets|Set Down Your Flaming Skull's Brazier To Let Your Pets Roam Around. They Look A Little Lost...|Furniture/Appliance|Heavy Water|HDK_1.66.0.144.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:9
1FC43FB9-22E5479D-895C657C-46C112B8|kName|kDesc|Active Item - Sleeping Doberman|Always Let Sleeping Dogs Lie.|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.41.0.37.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:8
2091272E-084248E1-901EA65B-C8C8874E|kName|kDesc|Dusty - The Golden Brimstone Dancer|You Are Gonna Dig Dusty; She's Worth Her Weight In Gold. 24 Carat And Built Like Fort Knox. When She Dances, You'll Agree That Dusty's Commodities Should Be Held In The U. S. Federal Reserve.|Furniture/Appliance|Mass Media Games, Inc.|HDK_1.51.0.60.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:18
213F16F9-EB914B44-B45DD14D-D7DB5D70|kName|kDesc|60'' LOOT™ Diamond EOD TV - Flatscreen|The Height Of Luxury: Own Your Very Own Blinged Out Diamond EOD TV That Let's You Watch Full Length Movies, TV Episodes, Live Shows And More With Your Friends In PlayStation®Home! The LOOT™ Entertainment On Demand TV Will Work In Any Private Space Unless The Space Comes With A Video Screen You Cant Turn Off, It Does Not Include Streaming Radio Or Audio-only Content. Now All You Need To Do Is Invite Your Friends Over, Pull Out The Popcorn And Make The Most Important Decision Of All: What Will You Watch First!? PLEASE READ BEFORE YOU PURCHASE: Due To Contractual And Rights Agreements, Some EOD Channels Are Nation Specific. Crackle Content Is ONLY Available In United States, Canada, United Kingdom, And Australia. RadioIO Is ONLY Available In The United States And Canada. In Addition, Due To Rights Issues, Countries May Not Receive The Same Content Selections Within The Channels. Only One TV Can Be Active At A Time. The LOOT™ EOD Will Work In Any Private Space, UNLESS The Space Comes With A Video Screen You Cannot Turn Off.|Furniture/Appliance|© LOOT™|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:42
21422CA4-B45744AA-98D7EF44-321EAD29|kName|kDesc|Echochrome|Collect The Echoes And Avoid Enemies In The Optical Illusion Stages.|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.83.0.11.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:3
219FEE18-94EB4364-8D359C45-CB396876|kName|kDesc|(x7) F.U.B.A.R. Helipad Game Launcher Model|Use This To Relocate To F.U.B.A.R.|Furniture/Appliance|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:3
21E5AA8F-71BE11E1-89A30022-19291EC2|kName|kDesc|Contemporary Double Bed - Rustic (Active Object)|Add Warmth And Charm To Your Apartment With The Contemporary Range From Cucumber. Lockwood Beds Are Active Objects With A Realistic 'lie Down' Animation, So Lie Back And Relax On This Dreamy, Comfortable Bed. Owners Of The Cucumber Contemporary Double Bed - Rustic Can Purchase The Contemporary Double Bed - Rustic (Active Object) At A Discounted Price.|Furniture/Appliance|Lockwood|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:32
21E6BCF9-F50D4C2B-9D2ABA19-70CC974D|kName|kDesc|NDreams Luxury Hot Tub (Nature)|This Luxurious, Beautifully Sculpted Hot Tub Is Perfect For Your Apartment. Hang Out With Up To Five People And Choose From A Variety Of Coloured Lights To Set The Mood. This Appliance Uses 6 Furniture Slots.|Furniture/Appliance|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:6
222050D1-99F7402E-B858A012-FAA8855B|kName|kDesc|Sodium Teleportal: Destination Classified|Place This Mysterious Teleportal In Your Personal Space To Gain Access To A Classified Sodium Location. Warning; Destination Contains Experimental Technology. Users Are Advised To Proceed With Caution.|Furniture/Appliance|Sodium - Lockwood|HDK_1.50.0.238.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:92
224F288D-2C12466C-BD518400-CE7CA1A6|kName|kDesc|FREE LOOT™ EOD TV|Experience The Amazing Technology That Allows You To Enjoy The LOOT EOD In Your Private Space. The LOOT™ Entertainment On Demand TV Will Work In Any Private Space Unless The Space Comes With A Video Screen You Cant Turn Off. This FREE Version Of The LOOT™ TV Only Plays The LOOT™ Channel. For The Full EOD TVs Check Out The LOOT Store For The Portable TV Bundle (packed With Exclusive Television Models And More) Or Choose From Six Different Television Options.|Furniture/Appliance|© LOOT™|HDK_1.66.0.144.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:40
22762D45-042D4E84-8502302A-940ECD90|kName|kDesc|MyKitchen - Refrigerator - Gloss Black|An Interactive Refrigerator For Your Kitchen. Exclusive To The VEEMEE 3D Printer. ※ Active Items Provide More Functionality Than Normal Items. You May Only Place Limited Numbers Of The Active Items In Your Apartment Or Clubhouse At Any Time.|Furniture/Appliance|VEEMEE|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|LUA-REWARD|Res:6
2304A296-420F4982-A197FF45-E8E715B2|ObjectName|ObjectDescription|Dig Dug™|TM & Ⓒ 1982-2009 NAMCO BANDAI Games Inc.|Furniture/Appliance|NBGI|HDK_XX|AUTO-REWARD|Res:3
23052E0D-D9C54F4E-9FA63EF4-52952F41|kName|kDesc|Two Player Chess Game #3|A Black And White Chess Board Placed On A Polished Wooden Table. This Game Is Available For Two Players.|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.40.0.265.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:71
235D6F2B-67A04998-84640318-4F6F305F|kName|kDesc|Active Object - DJ Light Set|Start A Party Of Lights With You Very Own Light Set.|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.41.0.37.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:15
251D57E6-B104479D-9A6AB0D1-402408CA|kName|kDesc|A Game About Bouncing|A Game About Bouncing Is, Well, A Game About Bouncing. You Are A Ball Who Must Bounce Off Of Bumpers And Avoid The Missiles Those Bumpers Will Throw At You. Level Up And Earn Points To Get Great Prizes!|Furniture/Appliance|Codename: Shawn McGrath|HDK_1.66.0.144.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:3
253178CF-3A2843EB-ABD47A58-39AD7679|ObjectName|ObjectDiscription|Dragon Spirit™|TM & Ⓒ1987-2009 NAMCO BANDAI Games Inc.|Furniture/Appliance|NBGI|HDK_1.40.0.265.PUB|AUTO-REWARD|Res:3
25320F59-0D304D59-B889F3B1-C4BAE835|kName|kDesc|Spinning Light Projector|Bring Colour And Life To Your Apartment With The Light Projector. Customise The Position And Colour Of Ten Different Patterns. ※Active Items Provide More Functionality Than Normal Items. You May Only Place Limited Numbers Of The Active Items In Your Apartment Or Clubhouse At Any Time.|Furniture/Appliance|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:19
25E3BB8C-D10A4734-BC929739-84B4E3BD|kName|kDesc|GROW HOME : White Jasmine|Grow Your Own Plantlife And Show Off Your Green Fingered Skills!|Furniture/Appliance|VEEMEE|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:55
25EEF42C-FC144655-85625CB9-48EFEBD0|kName|kDesc|LOOT™ Photo Telescope|This Exclusive Active Item From Your Pals At LOOT Has A Powerful Zoom Lens That Lets You Peer Far And Wide Across Any Personal Space Or Clubhouse… And Take Pictures Of Everything You See! All Pictures Are Saved To The XMB, So You Can Embarrass Your Friends On Your Favorite Social Network!|Furniture/Appliance|© 2011 LOOT™|HDK_1.51.0.60.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:47
25F7E44F-38E04FA7-B3A98396-74FF3658|Rusted Workbench|Rusted Workbench|Rusted Workbench|Rusted Workbench|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_XX|NOT-RWRD|Res:2
2615B3FB-75D84920-892053DC-8E3BEFBC|kName|kDesc|Vampire Batling Pets|Set Down Your Vampire Batling's Belfry To Let Your Pets Roam Around. Protect Your Neck!|Furniture/Appliance|Heavy Water|HDK_1.66.0.144.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:7
26F5DE92-F9084072-9A0DA107-15BA3CC9|kName|kDesc|Coffin|Rest In Eternal Peace With Custom Animations For Male And Female Avatars.|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:24
27296B06-D32648D6-A8DD4233-3E8C51CD|kName|kDesc|Spring Bouquet|This Active Item Allows You To Place 20 Floral Bouquets To Bring A Springtime Ambiance To Any Space.|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:39
27A3888C-843F44F2-804E3671-B88066C8|kName|kDesc|Samurai Bot Builder (Active Object)|With Love From Iron Fusion!|Furniture/Appliance|Lockwood|HDK_1.60.0.450.BETA|AUTO-REWARD|Res:28
27BE26F0-FB154965-8E561BCE-8B3A93CB|AmericanPoolName|AmericanPoolDesc|American Pool - Blue Table|An American Pool Table, Ideal For Any Apartment. This Table Comes With Both Eight Ball And Nine Ball Versions Of Pool. The Game Can Be Played With Two Players, Or In A Single Player Practice Mode.|Furniture/Appliance|VEEMEE|HDK_1.60.0.450.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:55
2831242A-B026450C-A6C0ADED-337CC413|kName|kDesc|80'' LOOT™ EOD TV - Wall Mounted|PLEASE READ BEFORE YOU PURCHASE: Due To Contractual And Rights Agreements, Some EOD Channels Are Nation Specific. Crackle Content Is ONLY Available In United States, Canada, United Kingdom, And Australia. RadioIO Is ONLY Available In The United States And Canada. In Addition, Due To Rights Issues, Countries May Not Receive The Same Content Selections Within The Channels. Only One TV Can Be Active At A Time. The LOOT EOD Will Work In Any Private Space, UNLESS The Space Comes With A Video Screen You Cannot Turn Off. Watch Full Length Movies, TV Episodes, Live Shows And More With Your Friends In PlayStation®Home! The LOOT™ Entertainment On Demand TV Will Work In Any Private Space Unless The Space Comes With A Video Screen You Cant Turn Off, It Does Not Include Streaming Radio Or Audio-only Content. This Bundle-exclusive Wall Mounted TV Works With The FREE LOOT™ TV Wall Mount (found In The LOOT™ Store.) Simply Hang The Mount On The Wall Like A Picture Frame Then Hook Your Wall Mounted EOD TV On It. Decorating Has Never Been So Easy!|Furniture/Appliance|© LOOT™|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:42
284EA759-C1D34448-B892B2CC-4B0C9CC7|kName|kDesc|BoxBeats Mini: Dance 2|This Stylish Sound System Comes Jam Packed With Over 10 Amazing Dance Tracks For You And Your Friends To Listen To While You Bust Some Moves. This Active Item Also Allows You To Select Specific Tracks To Play, Set The Volume And Even Randomise The Track List. This Is An Essential Item For Your Apartment. This Item Has The Same Music Tracks As The Original, But The Object Representing This Item Is 75% Smaller In Physical Size. NB - There May Be A Delay When You Place The Item Whilst The Music Tracks Download.|Furniture/Appliance|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:28
28F76382-D26D4912-A902B070-7B7E0218|kName|kDesc|Timepieces - Metronome Clock|An Interesting Clock Designed To Act Much Like A Metronome. Exclusive To The VEEMEE 3D Printer. The Time Is Automatically Set Using The Time On Your PlayStation®3. ※ Active Items Provide More Functionality Than Normal Items. You May Only Place Limited Numbers Of The Active Items In Your Apartment Or Clubhouse At Any Time.|Furniture/Appliance|VEEMEE|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|LUA-REWARD|Res:10
29A63BB7-8EA0442E-9DAF7966-EEA43980|kName|kDesc|Thanksgiving Dining Table - Refined - 10 Person|What's Thanksgiving Without The Dinner? Entertain Your Friends And Family In The Privacy Of Your Own Personal Space With The VEEMEE Thanksgiving Personal Dining Experience. Guests Can Receive Up To 3 Reward Items. This Table Has 10 Seats. Owning This Table Grants Access To The Big Thanksgiving Dinner Table In Acorn Meadows Park. ※ Active Items Provide More Functionality Than Normal Items. You May Only Place Limited Numbers Of The Active Items In Your Apartment Or Clubhouse At Any Time.|Furniture/Appliance|VEEMEE|HDK_1.82.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:60
29F952A9-DE074A6B-9B4BDE23-BE898FE4|ObjectName|ObjectDescription|Vending Machine|Place This Together With Arcade Cabinets, For An Authentic Arcade Ensemble!|Furniture/Appliance|NAMCO BANDAI Games Inc.|HDK_XX|NOT-RWRD|Res:2
2A1107C0-CC204442-A013193E-25988D3A|kName|kDesc|Flying Doomnut Of Sprinkles|The Flying Doomnut Of Sprinkles Will Whiz Around Your Apartment Spreading Fear To Onlookers. This Was Won From Playing The OMG Trap-O-Matic In Aurora. You Can Win Another Version Of This Item By Playing Collect-O-Rama In Aurora.|Furniture/Appliance|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.60.0.450.BETA|AUTO-REWARD|Res:7
2A4D03A4-58FA4C3A-8F4FBA51-FA517D92|kName|kDesc|Cobalt Blue Stand Mixer|Get Cooking With This Interactive Stand Mixer!|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:13
2AF9BFD3-42144FAD-A44E4159-0F12EB98|kName|kDesc|Decorative Lounger|Relax And Get Comfortable! This Active Item Lets You Pose And Take Snapshots In 5 Unique Positions.|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.65.0.139.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:29
2B006C69-4C89473A-9CC8A937-60E509AD|kName|kDesc|Tennis Umpire|Have Something To Say? Talk To The Ump In Your Personal Space.|Furniture/Appliance|2K Sports|HDK_1.41.0.37.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:20
2B572369-97AA4BB7-BA0543B3-A7FBC820|kName|kDesc|Old-fashioned Telephone|An Old-fashioned Telephone.|Furniture/Appliance|© 2009 LOOT™|HDK_1.3.6.22.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:2
2B6FFFF6-458B4D57-BB9EC9B5-BEEC0C10|Electric Mole Hunter Cabinet|kDesc|Electric Mole Hunter Cabinet|Electric Mole Hunter|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.60.0.450.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:3
2B8EF0AB-687C414E-BD4D5047-B694A96D|kName|kDesc|Peakvox Tweet|Item Essential For Gathering Information! High-tech Furniture That Displays/searches For Twitter Tweets. This Item Is An Advanced Piece Of Equipment Including Animation Features. This Type Of Item Can Only Be Placed In Limited Areas.|Furniture/Appliance|O-Two Inc.|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|AUTO-REWARD|Res:15
2BB190ED-BD564DF4-94E58E70-2CCF3568|kName|kDesc|BoxBeats: Horror|This BoxBeats System Houses A Collection Of Spooky Sounds That Are Perfect For Scaring Your Guests. NB - There May Be A Delay When You Place The Item Whilst The Music Tracks Download. ※Active Items Provide More Functionality Than Normal Items. You May Only Place Limited Numbers Of The Active Items In Your Apartment Or Clubhouse At Any Time.|Furniture/Appliance|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:28
2BC6DF57-4F8741E4-93FEC19E-52885791|kName|kDesc|Static Light Projector|Bring Colour And Life To Your Apartment With The Light Projector. Customise The Position And Colour Of Four Different Patterns. ※Active Items Provide More Functionality Than Normal Items. You May Only Place Limited Numbers Of The Active Items In Your Apartment Or Clubhouse At Any Time.|Furniture/Appliance|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:13
2C032DF7-E464428B-AC902AD3-A61F7F77|kName|kDesc|Space Ace Arcade Machine|In Space Ace You Play The Heroic Ace Who Must Stop The Evil Commander Borf From Taking Over The Earth!|Furniture/Appliance|Digital Leisure|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|AUTO-REWARD|Res:4
2C361509-FCAB49AC-8AC8A5F5-ECDAA063|kName|kDesc|HGL Combat - Trophy Cabinet|Impress Your Friends With Your HGL Combat Trophy Collection.|Furniture/Appliance|VEEMEE|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|AUTO-REWARD|Res:23
2CE85CB3-19E3410A-B4C03872-F6F93A51|kName|kDesc|1950s Record Player|This Record Player Is Of A Retro Design, And As Well As Looking Great In Your Apartment, Plays Music From The Sound Track Of Killer Plants From Outer Space.|Furniture/Appliance|FluffyLogic Development Ltd.|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:5
2D058945-F78D4466-A0263485-CE175513|kName|kDesc|Flying Doomnut|This Flying Doomnut Of Doom Will Whiz Around Your Apartment Spreading Fear To Onlookers. Won From The Aurora Collect-O-Rama.|Furniture/Appliance|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.50.0.238.BETA|AUTO-REWARD|Res:7
2D7A04EF-A8434BA4-9D51C143-EA563F71|kName|kDesc|Creek Falls - Bed|Give Your Bedroom The Contemporary Look It Longs For With This Low-rise Bed. As An Added Bonus, Now Two Avatars May Lay In The Bed At The Same Time. This Is An Active Item.|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:19
2D80DA49-BCB8491D-81FB1E2D-C4AE9480|kName|kDesc|KnittingMachine|KnittingMachine|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.60.0.450.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:54
2DA1CBC7-790E4468-85DB036A-760B8E35|kName|kDesc|MyGym Apartment - Equipment - Running Machine|Train On Your Running Machine To Reach A New Level Of Fitness. Each New Level You Reach Will Earn You Tokens. You Can Spend The Tokens To Get The Rewards In The MyGym Token Store. Each Piece Of MyGym Equipment Trains A Different Sets Of Muscles. Increasing Your Fitness Level On One Machine Will Not Raise It For The Others. Finished Your Training Session For Today? Why Not Practice Your Technique?|Furniture/Appliance|VEEMEE|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:99
2DB3EB7C-893F4EBC-B08475B2-449C346A|kName|kDesc|Echochrome|Collect The Echoes And Avoid Enemies In The Optical Illusion Stages.|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment Asia|HDK_1.52.0.2.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:3
2DEF4FBA-9F2046CA-887E0061-A2D731C3|kName|kDesc|Enchanted Caudron|Ask It Anything, From Your Deepest Darkest Secrets To Whether Or Not You Should Wear That Outfit Tomorrow. But Beware, You Might Be Surprised What Answers Await You.|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.41.0.37.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:12
2DF19F38-0E3C4A58-A6CF6963-B733B5C1|kName|kDesc|Smoke Machine (Red)|Add A Little Atmosphere With This Great Red Smoke Machine.|Furniture/Appliance|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.52.0.2.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:5
2E6C483F-CF0F42D3-B9F0A9B7-0E43329A|kName|kDesc|22'' LOOT™ Diamond EOD TV - Flatscreen|The Height Of Luxury: Own Your Very Own Blinged Out Diamond EOD TV That Let's You Watch Full Length Movies, TV Episodes, Live Shows And More With Your Friends In PlayStation®Home! The LOOT™ Entertainment On Demand TV Will Work In Any Private Space Unless The Space Comes With A Video Screen You Cant Turn Off, It Does Not Include Streaming Radio Or Audio-only Content. Now All You Need To Do Is Invite Your Friends Over, Pull Out The Popcorn And Make The Most Important Decision Of All: What Will You Watch First!? PLEASE READ BEFORE YOU PURCHASE: Due To Contractual And Rights Agreements, Some EOD Channels Are Nation Specific. Crackle Content Is ONLY Available In United States, Canada, United Kingdom, And Australia. RadioIO Is ONLY Available In The United States And Canada. In Addition, Due To Rights Issues, Countries May Not Receive The Same Content Selections Within The Channels. Only One TV Can Be Active At A Time. The LOOT™ EOD Will Work In Any Private Space, UNLESS The Space Comes With A Video Screen You Cannot Turn Off.|Furniture/Appliance|© LOOT™|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:42
2F1DDA81-AD6A4098-9CFFFC7E-19A727C8|kName|kDesc|Mood Light|A Fantastic Reward Won From Playing OrbRunner.|Furniture/Appliance|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|AUTO-REWARD|Res:6
2F2AAF4B-CEA54370-8E3E5B0A-961A60F3|kName|kDesc|Geometric Garden|This Active Item Allows You To Place Up To 40 Topiaries In Your Personal Space. Awarded For Reaching Level 34 In MiniBots In Serenity Plaza.|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|LUA-REWARD|Res:43
2F4D257B-F1D64B54-BD29B75E-36E6465E|kName|kDesc|GROW HOME : Cherry Blossom|Grow Your Own Plantlife And Show Off Your Green Fingered Skills!|Furniture/Appliance|VEEMEE|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:55
2FDCE747-EA004FE2-AC98F299-45D437BF|kName|kDesc|Cabin Boy In Trout Trouble – Classic|LOOT™s Cabin Boy In Trout Trouble! Is Now Available In This Classic Arcade Style. This Appliance Lets You Play The Cabin Boy Game Right In Your Very Own PlayStation®Home Personal Spaces! Catch The Fish Lil Dickie Throws Your Way, Keep Lil Missus From Burning Under The Hot Sun And Watch Out For Chairman Meow!! This Awesome Arcade Is Equipped With Leaderboards, Capers And Unlockable Items For Your Avatar! Start Playing, LOOTers!|Furniture/Appliance|© 2010 LOOT™|HDK_1.3.6.22.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:3
30D13DA1-BEE24F99-AD613D02-87C00654|kName|kDesc|Doctor Who - Strategist Dalek (Blue) Furniture|Do You Really Think You Are Smart Enough To Control A Strategist Dalek? EXTERMINATE! Doctor Who Logo © 2013 And TM BBC. Dalek Image © BBC/ Terry Nation 1963. Licensed By BBC WW Ltd.|Furniture/Appliance|BBC Worldwide Limited|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:9
30E3244F-E30B4B4E-8EBE277D-3039C748|kName|kDesc|F.U.B.A.R. Helipad Game Launcher Model|Get Direct Access To F.U.B.A.R. (Fight Until Blood And Ruin) Via This Attractive Helipad Reward Model.|Furniture/Appliance|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|AUTO-REWARD|Res:3
31D7EE34-9A554DC5-817E1EF1-17564672|kName|kDesc|Xi: Continuum - Xoff Cola Machine|This Personal Xoff Cola Machine Allows You To Teleport From Your Apartment Straight Into The Continuum. Xoff Cola - Refreshing And Functional!|Furniture/Appliance|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:6
32B4262A-35634291-A93B47B5-FB9D25DE|kName|kDesc|Active Item - Pot Of Gold|And They Said These Weren't Real.|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.51.0.60.PUB|LUA-REWARD|Res:5
3300E831-36CE4EBA-AD47531F-843E087B|kName|kDesc|Fiber Optic Plant|No, This Plant Won't Make Light Shine From Your Stomach If You Eat It. Just Enjoy The Lights.|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.50.0.238.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:7
33093670-BBD14ABD-9E7E26E6-6FC25FBC|kName|kDesc|Large Alien Plant|Part Of The MiniBot Alien Terrain Pack.|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|LUA-REWARD|Res:6
33124CB8-B06248CC-8A9895E5-F2AF9EDD|kName|kDesc|Dragon Rider: Lightning|Ride The Energetic Lightning Dragon Around Your Personal Spaces With Your Friends. This Type Shoots Blasts Of Lightning!|Furniture/Appliance|Heavy Water|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:60
33C76C24-F73C4968-97CD54AC-3589D7E2|kName|kDesc|Evil Pumpkin|This Pumpkin Is Not Exactly Evil. But When He Gets Close To Evil, He Picks Up Its Flavor - Like A Mushroom Or Something. This Is An Animated Active Item.|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:8
33CEB1D4-992E4198-BD33E7B5-4407EA3C|kName|kDesc|Personal Zero-Gravity Generator|Place This Appliance In Your Personal Space To Float In Zero-gravity, Alone Or With Guests! You Can Find This Item In The Giftinator 9000 From Hellfire Games.|Furniture/Appliance|Hellfire Games, Inc.|HDK_1.83.0.11.PUB|AUTO-REWARD|Res:27
33D44B1B-1C0147A6-8A5C7B69-F7562D18|kName|kDesc|3D Printer|Experience The Latest In Virtual-to-real Technology With The VEEMEE 3D Printer. Place In Your Personal Space And Choose From A Wide Selection Of Exclusive Virtual Items To Print Out For You And Your Friends. VEEMEE 3D Printer Vouchers Can Be Purchased From The Printer Or From The VEEMEE Store.|Furniture/Appliance|VEEMEE|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:75
349B37E6-49954E47-9898CA19-61F823AC|kName|kDesc|BoxBeats Mini: Relax|This Modern Sound System Comes Complete With Over 10 Of The Most Chilled Out And Relaxing Tracks, Perfect For Setting The Right Mood In Your Apartment. This Active Item Also Allows You To Select Specific Tracks To Play, Set The Volume And Even Randomise The Track List. This Is An Essential Item For Your Apartment. This Item Has The Same Music Tracks As The Original, But The Object Representing This Item Is 75% Smaller In Physical Size. NB - There May Be A Delay When You Place The Item Whilst The Music Tracks Download.|Furniture/Appliance|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:25
351A66FA-52D74054-98E3F395-33C264B7|kName|kDesc|Tentacle Growth|Part Of The MiniBot Alien Terrain Pack.|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|LUA-REWARD|Res:6
35B0E545-8D4F4095-AE9F666C-F1F903EB|kName|kDesc|Butterfly Perch|This Active Item Seats Three Avatars And Attracts Butterflies.|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:13
35F23733-909E46FB-927C36EB-ACD70735|kName|kDesc|Cobalt Blue Hot Pot|Get Cooking With This Interactive Pot!|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:6
360B405F-772C499D-95D58875-0895576D|kName|kDesc|Xi - Xoff Cola Machine|This Soft Drink Machine Allows You To Teleport From Your Apartment Into Aurora. Xoff Cola - Refreshing And Functional!|Furniture/Appliance|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:6
36B8DD09-A59C425D-917744C8-3B88AC8A|kName|kDesc|Doctor Who - Eternal Dalek (Yellow) Furniture|What Role Does The Mysterious Eternal Dalek Play In The Dalek Hierarchy? EXTERMINATE! Doctor Who Logo © 2013 And TM BBC. Dalek Image © BBC/ Terry Nation 1963. Licensed By BBC WW Ltd.|Furniture/Appliance|BBC Worldwide Limited|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:9
36C3F3B1-02D04DA8-B8459F7B-57D46AF0|kName|kDesc|Oildrum Barbecue|A Well Used Barbecue Made To Grill Everything To Perfection And Give It A Unique Smokey Taste. An Exclusive Reward Earned Through The Challenge System.|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.82.0.17.PUB|AUTO-REWARD|Res:2
36F1D07B-477E4498-9389EA22-34DAB8F0|kName|kDesc|Personal Texas Hold'em Poker Table|Now You Can Host Your Friends With Your Very Own Personal Poker Table. Simply Place This Table In To Any Space Of Your Choice And Let The Gaming Begin. Modeled After The Poker Experience At Paradise Springs Casino In PlayStation Home, This Six Player Table Will Make Your Apartment The Place To Be. Each Player Starts Out With A Set Amount Of Holdings, And You Play Until Someone Is The Table Champ! Play Again And Again To See Which Of Your Friends Is Truly The Most Skilled. This Is An Animated Active Item.|Furniture/Appliance|Digital Leisure|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:231
3724B911-0CA140A4-AB743756-E97EEDAE|kName|kDesc|Personal Dining Experience - 6 Person Table|Entertain Your Friends In The Privacy Of Your Own Personal Space With The VEEMEE Personal Dining Experience. Guests Can Receive Up To 4 Food Reward Items. This Table Has Six Seats.|Furniture/Appliance|VEEMEE|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:59
38138717-DF634B14-BF98573C-CB33E8A8|kName|kDesc|Chimenea|This Active Item Chiminea Creates A Warm And Cozy Fire In Any Personal Space.|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:4
38151D47-048245FA-833B8FC2-A087626A|kName|kDesc|Scramble Arcade Cabinet|Scramble Arcade Cabinet ©2013 Konami Digital Entertainment FOCAL Emulation Technology ©2009-2013 Code Mystics Inc.|Furniture/Appliance|Konami Digital Entertainment|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:3
38F66ADE-36B04E2E-A42E634E-7BDB7F8C|kName|kDesc|40'' LOOT™ Diamond EOD TV - Flatscreen|The Height Of Luxury: Own Your Very Own Blinged Out Diamond EOD TV That Let's You Watch Full Length Movies, TV Episodes, Live Shows And More With Your Friends In PlayStation®Home! The LOOT™ Entertainment On Demand TV Will Work In Any Private Space Unless The Space Comes With A Video Screen You Cant Turn Off, It Does Not Include Streaming Radio Or Audio-only Content. Now All You Need To Do Is Invite Your Friends Over, Pull Out The Popcorn And Make The Most Important Decision Of All: What Will You Watch First!? PLEASE READ BEFORE YOU PURCHASE: Due To Contractual And Rights Agreements, Some EOD Channels Are Nation Specific. Crackle Content Is ONLY Available In United States, Canada, United Kingdom, And Australia. RadioIO Is ONLY Available In The United States And Canada. In Addition, Due To Rights Issues, Countries May Not Receive The Same Content Selections Within The Channels. Only One TV Can Be Active At A Time. The LOOT™ EOD Will Work In Any Private Space, UNLESS The Space Comes With A Video Screen You Cannot Turn Off.|Furniture/Appliance|© LOOT™|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:42
393F54F0-BB04416E-BD9B90AD-2EDF6796|kName|kDesc|Baby Grand Piano|Start A Piano Bar In Your Very Own Personal Space. Use This Player Piano To Tune Into A Higher Class Of People.|Furniture/Appliance|Mass Media Games, Inc.|HDK_1.55.0.155.BETA2|NOT-RWRD|Res:8
3964377E-06B54F36-A27A4628-948DC59B|kName|kDesc|Two Player Checkers Game #5|A Green Toned Checkers Board With Red And White Pieces On Tan Coloured Patio Table. This Game Is Available For Two Players.|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.41.0.37.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:43
39A1EFE4-E95C46A5-AC8A7E1C-AFE51B50|kName|kDesc|Frozen Peak Palace Bed|This Icy Bed Set Is A Great Excuse To Snuggle Up Under The Covers. This Is An Active Item.|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:19
39E5D10F-98CD4677-BBE728C3-BFD8C014|kName|kDesc|Active Object - Dragon Etched Crystal|A Rotating Piece Of Crystal That Alternates In Colour.|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.41.0.37.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:10
3A1FBC67-E19E4E09-A25D13B2-AB812900|kName|kDesc|DIY Racer (incl. Hotrod Car)|DIY Racer Is A Fun Mini-game That Turns Your Apartment Into An Exciting Race Track! Use Your Existing Furniture Or Our Specially Designed Furniture To Create Jumps, Bridges, And Tunnels To Create The Coolest Track You Can Imagine. Invite Your Friends And Race Against Them On The Track That You Designed! Do Tricks To Unlock Some Cool Stuff! This Mini-game Includes The Hotrod RC Car!|Furniture/Appliance|Codeglue B.V.|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:85
3A49CA31-177A4B4E-855B0DF2-60C612CF|kName|kDesc|GZ Gift|A Terminal To Send A Gift To Someone Special.|Furniture/Appliance|Granzella Inc.|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:426
3AC327D7-21AE411E-9EAB71DD-E83FD984|kName|kDesc|Birthday Party - Chocolate Fountain|Mmmmmm… Chocolatey Goodness... Exclusive To The 1st Birthday Acorn Meadows Park.|Furniture/Appliance|VEEMEE|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|LUA-REWARD|Res:2
3AC5B9B8-8FE94B3F-BF93DC51-6C1AD1A0|kName|kDesc|What The Bleep Peep - Heavy Pet - Blazing Blue|What The Bleep Peep Is Bad To The Bone! This Naughty Little Peep Will Bring You Hours Of Fun In Your Apartment! You Can Control Your Peep With Custom Animations And Special Peep Moves!|Furniture/Appliance|Heavy Water|HDK_1.66.0.144.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:25
3AE4BE9E-71BE11E1-AD8B0022-19291EC2|kName|kDesc|Contemporary Double Bed - Vivid (Active Object)|Add Warmth And Charm To Your Apartment With The Contemporary Range From Cucumber. Lockwood Beds Are Active Objects With A Realistic 'lie Down' Animation, So Lie Back And Relax On This Dreamy, Comfortable Bed. Owners Of The Cucumber Contemporary Double Bed - Vivid Can Purchase The Contemporary Double Bed - Vivid (Active Object) At A Discounted Price.|Furniture/Appliance|Lockwood|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:32
3B6205A1-78E04ADB-ADF7127E-E7AEE1FC|kName|kDesc|Laptop|Laptop|Furniture/Appliance|EA SPORTS|HDK_1.3.0.130.BETA2|AUTO-REWARD|Res:2
3BFDCD3B-126E491A-8E4D2498-90E0D1E4|kName|kDesc|Oak Retro Speaker Right|The Right Light Wood Retro Speaker From The Loot™ Home Entertainment Collection.|Furniture/Appliance|© 2009 Loot™|HDK_1.3.2.16.BETA1|NOT-RWRD|Res:2
3C1D243D-70D34DE9-93CC24D7-6D627EA6|kName|kDesc|Mount Olympus Bed|This Is A Bed Fit For Any Hero. This Is An Active Item.|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.60.0.451.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:19
3C73D6A3-5804401A-AE93B7E1-36A3AD9F|kName|kDesc|LOOT™ Active Light|Take The Stage Set Light Functionality To Any Private Space You Own And Transform Them Into Locations For Shooting Your Next Movie.|Furniture/Appliance|© 2011 LOOT™. All Rights Reserved.|HDK_1.65.0.139.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:35
3D1EA140-43CE4194-BF82BCF8-BD8414E0|kName|kDesc|BoxBeats: Classical|Bringing A Touch Of Class To The BoxBeats Brand. BoxBeats: Classical Gives You Access To A Selection Of Well Known Classical Music Tracks. NB - There May Be A Delay When You Place The Item Whilst The Music Tracks Download. ※Active Items Provide More Functionality Than Normal Items. You May Only Place Limited Numbers Of The Active Items In Your Apartment Or Clubhouse At Any Time.|Furniture/Appliance|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:23
3D2CCCA1-DBAA44AF-A26A5D78-645F059D|kName|kDesc|The Nightclub: Bubble Machine|Add A Little Bit Of Extra Fun To The Nightclub With The Bubble Machine. ※Active Items Provide More Functionality Than Normal Items. You May Only Place Limited Numbers Of The Active Items In Your Apartment Or Clubhouse At Any Time.|Furniture/Appliance|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:16
3D66517E-560B4273-B285D70E-6CD81903|kName|kDesc|Calf Manger|This Active Item Unleashes Calves That Wander Around Your Apartment.|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:12
3D8413F8-ACC449D1-8EB98F7B-E5ACB529|kName|kDesc|Scribble Shooter|Take Down The Alien Hordes With This Frenzied Shoot 'em Up.|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.52.0.2.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:3
3DC7D8FA-ACF64809-992B607B-0483B5B8|kName|kDesc|240'' LOOT™ EOD TV - Flatscreen|PLEASE READ BEFORE YOU PURCHASE: Due To Contractual And Rights Agreements, Some EOD Channels Are Nation Specific. Crackle Content Is ONLY Available In United States, Canada, United Kingdom, And Australia. RadioIO Is ONLY Available In The United States And Canada. In Addition, Due To Rights Issues, Countries May Not Receive The Same Content Selections Within The Channels. Only One TV Can Be Active At A Time. The LOOT EOD Will Work In Any Private Space, UNLESS The Space Comes With A Video Screen You Cannot Turn Off. Watch Full Length Movies, TV Episodes, Live Shows And More With Your Friends On The Largest Television Screen Available In PlayStation®Home! The LOOT™ Entertainment On Demand TV Will Work In Any Private Space Unless The Space Comes With A Video Screen You Cant Turn Off, It Does Not Include Streaming Radio Or Audio-only Content. This Mammoth Of A TV Comes With The LOOT™ 240 TV Stand. Check Out The LOOT™ EOD TV Bundle For The Most Amazing Deal Weve Ever Had, Including Exclusive Wall Mounted Television Models!|Furniture/Appliance|© LOOT™|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:42
3DE107AD-BF6D4DC2-B57AAC34-4D2B74CD|kName|kDesc|MyBedroom Guy's Bed - Red/Black|A New, Designer Bed For Guys. This Is An Active Item. ※ Active Items Provide More Functionality Than Normal Items. You May Only Place Limited Numbers Of The Active Items In Your Apartment Or Clubhouse At Any Time.|Furniture/Appliance|VEEMEE|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:18
3E22F074-68AF44F9-947C4EE5-75060B83|kName|kDesc|Active Object - Indoor Waterfall|An Extravagant Indoor Waterfall.|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.41.0.37.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:6
3E347AFC-EC214633-85EBBB18-D3255905|kName|kDesc|Active Item - Orange Cat|An Orange Colored Cat That Licks Its Paws.|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.41.0.37.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:18
3E80B243-AF8645C0-B2130B09-EE2CDF11|kName|kDesc|Tennis Ball Machine|Ready, Aim, FIRE! Shoot Tennis Balls With This Nifty Tennis Ball Machine For Your Personal Space.|Furniture/Appliance|2K Sports|HDK_1.41.0.37.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:10
3EC30577-0CEE49B8-AB3AD3EC-0F6CE065|kName|kDesc|Mad Blocker: PlayStation®Home|Mad Blocker: PlayStation®Home Is A Puzzle Game Where Players Attempt To Combine Blocks Of The Same Colour.|Furniture/Appliance|Open Emotion Studios|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:3
3EE9E5E3-03D14F6E-9B08201A-D9858641|kName|kDesc|Wise Man|Wisdom Is Hard Earned And Even Harder Kept. Luckily This Wise Man Is On Hand To Remind You!|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment Europe|HDK_1.3.6.22.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:16
3F68FF67-50564C53-A59DBD27-9FA1273C|kName|kDesc|Intellivision® ASTROSMASH Cocktail Table Game|Play The Thrilling Intellivision® Game Astrosmash In This Updated Version Created Exclusively For PlayStation®Home Whenever You Want With This Astrosmash Cocktail Table Style Arcade Game! Save The World From Falling Meteors, Alien UFOs And Killer Satellites! A Fast Action Challenge That Gets Faster And Harder As You Get Better! You And Your Friends Will Love This Classic Cocktail Table Style Arcade Game With Its Bright, Colorful Game Screen And Exciting Table-top Artwork! Earn The Following Four Exclusive Astrosmash Themed Rewards During Gameplay: An Animating T-shirt, Glitzy Game Poster, Gold-plated Trophy, And 6 Foot Themed Mobile.|Furniture/Appliance|Realtime Associates, Inc.|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:3
3F95E544-992F41F7-AE870FDD-94E43632|kName|kDesc|Model Racetrack|An Animated Model Racetrack.|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|AUTO-REWARD|Res:6
3FCA0D10-62F34457-827B7009-60C3FF49|kName|kDesc|Leaf Green Blender|Get Cooking With This Interactive Blender!|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:14
40722C21-A833425E-ABF3894C-BD58951B|kName|kDesc|Decorative Fountain With Water Jets|Impress Your Guests With This Large Breathtaking Water Fountain With Water Jets.|Furniture/Appliance|Lockwood|HDK_1.3.6.22.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:2
410FE5E1-1D7F4952-ADBD96A6-F54FBF74|kName|kDesc|NDreams Clocks: Gears Of Time|A Beautiful Clock Designed To Place In Your Personal Apartment. Time Is Set According To Your PlayStation®3 Settings. Note - This Is An Appliance.|Furniture/Appliance|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:11
413A6D33-1A2C4E8E-B9E023B1-79ECDD1F|AmericanPoolName|AmericanPoolDesc|American Pool - Yellow Table|An American Pool Table, Ideal For Any Apartment. This Table Comes With Both Eight Ball And Nine Ball Versions Of Pool. The Game Can Be Played With Two Players, Or In A Single Player Practice Mode.|Furniture/Appliance|VEEMEE|HDK_1.60.0.450.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:55
41770F69-AEDA411F-83C4E00B-40375E6A|kName|kDesc|Asteroids Cabaret Cabinet|Atari's Asteroids Arcade Game In Compact Cabaret Cabinet Form. Asteroids® ©2012 Atari Interactive Inc. All Rights Reserved. Asteroids® Is A Trademark Owned By Atari Interactive Inc. Created By Code Mystics Inc.|Furniture/Appliance|Atari Interactive Inc.|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:3
419396E1-DF0C4914-94E88EFD-EF2394A3|kName|kDesc|Active Object - Toy Train Set|Relive Your Childhood With This Toy Train Set.|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.41.0.37.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:12
4263F959-9D764CF6-9288F25F-DC92717A|kName|kDesc|Active Object - Animated Goat|A Friendly Pet Goat To Play With.|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.40.0.265.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:22
426F8BDA-A6744F57-A49EB9F9-474A363D|kName|kDesc|Mahogany Retro Speaker Right|The Right Mahogany Retro Speaker From The Loot™ Home Entertainment Collection.|Furniture/Appliance|© 2009 Loot™|HDK_1.3.2.16.BETA1|NOT-RWRD|Res:2
42ABEBA2-33EB4755-8EF9514E-FAE075BA|kName|kDesc|Trigger Happy In-A-Box|Shooting Gallery Arcade Action! Ten Unique Levels! High Scores! Play Until You Can't Play Any More! The Price Of This Item Is Reduced If You Already Own The Bar Key.|Furniture/Appliance|Mass Media Games, Inc.|HDK_1.41.0.37.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:4
42BB171E-566541E6-9E16B1C3-B09A2608|kName|kDesc|Las Vegas Suite Big Brown Bed|Lie Down On This Large Comfy Bed After A Night Of Partying. This Is An Active Item.|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.60.0.451.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:24
42F7F720-85CD4D4F-B495A4AD-A4262B6E|kName|kDesc|Romantic Holiday Fireplace|The Perfect Centerpiece For Your Holiday Décor, This Fireplace Doubles As A Music Player! Plays 3 Romantic Holiday Tracks.|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:8
43955D3F-541545C8-A22A5A3E-045DB33C|kName|kDesc|Alchemical Apparatus|This Active Item Is An Essential Tool For Any Potion Brewer.|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:12
43987DBE-439E44CD-9357F0CC-8A64F581|kName|kDesc|Deluxe Aquarium|This Gorgeous Tank Will Be The Centerpiece Of Your Room. This Special Cylindrical Aquarium Comes With 5 Unique Fish, And 4 Decorations. This Tank Is Capable Of Holding Up To 60 Fish And 30 Decorations So You Can Build It Your Way. To Get Your Tank Started, Included With This Purchase Is The Animal Fish Pack And The Decoration Riverbed Pack. The Fish Included Are: Butterflyfish, Longnose Hawkfish, Pandamoor, Seahorse And Freckled Hawkfish. Plant Life Included: Hollow Log, Rocky Cave, Red Ludwigia And Green Hygrophila. This Is An Animated Active Item.|Furniture/Appliance|Digital Leisure|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:584
43C4E2B4-8EF541AA-958DAB3B-62FBE7E7|kName|kDesc|Data Pulse Hack Arcade Cabinet|Intercept Data Pulses And Reconfigure Them Into Patterns In This Fast-paced Arcade Game.|Furniture/Appliance|Jet Set Games, Inc.|HDK_1.41.0.37.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:3
43E4E9A7-D7B442F7-BC1031DA-7BABD766|kName|kDesc|Active Item - Sleeping Bulldog|A Sleeping British Bulldog With A Spiked Collar.|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.41.0.37.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:8
44025891-ED364BB7-AA476DBD-EACBA501|kName|kDesc|Robotic Canine|All The Wonders Of Having A Dog And None Of The Mess.|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment America|HDK_1.3.6.22.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:27
440B9B69-4F174873-846FECD8-4FEAAA54|kName|kDesc|INTELLIVISION® JUKE BOX|Add Some Music To Your Home With This Full-size Classic-style Juke Box With Animated Glowing Neon Lights! Plays The Themes From A Number Of Your Favorite INTELLIVISION® Games!|Furniture/Appliance|Realtime Associates, Inc.|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:5
4411F0D1-A255439C-91213530-9CB349C8|kName|kDesc|Sparkling Decorative Plant, Butterfly Palm|The Butterfly Palm Has Branches That Extend Up Like A Water Fountain. *A Gift From GZ Gift|Furniture/Appliance|Granzella Inc.|HDK_1.82.0.17.PUB|LUA-REWARD|Res:4
4427DF4E-34A34424-8DA2B3BE-FF1D677A|kName|kDesc|Lounge Around Hammock|An Advanced Furniture Item Hammock That Lets You Sprawl Out In Various Poses. This Is An Advanced Furniture Item With Added Features And Animations. The Amount Of Items Of This Type That Can Be Placed Is Limited.|Furniture/Appliance|Granzella Inc.|HDK_1.83.0.11.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:115
442CFE09-3D4140CD-BDA8256F-BC674700|kName|kDesc|Interactive Bar - Prestige|You And Up To Three Other Friends Can Sit At Your Very Own Bar And Have Your Fill Of Non-alcoholic Beverages Until The Sun Comes Up. ※Active Items Provide More Functionality Than Normal Items. You May Only Place Limited Numbers Of The Active Items In Your Apartment Or Clubhouse At Any Time.|Furniture/Appliance|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.82.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:16
4436A967-8B7C419D-9AD37BAB-3FA136F7|kName|kDesc|Two Player Chess Game #2|A Classic Chess Board On A White Marble Table. This Game Is Available For Two Players.|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.40.0.265.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:71
450AAD6E-E9A4469E-84DBA36B-E9EA228C|kName|kDesc|Happy New Year 2014 - Fireworks|An Animated Fireworks Display For Your Apartment. Exclusive To The Winter Holiday Acorn Meadows Park.|Furniture/Appliance|VEEMEE|HDK_1.82.0.17.PUB|LUA-REWARD|Res:9
46362173-3A974823-BDB12FA7-31436AC8|kName|kDesc|Code Hack Arcade Cabinet|Combine Logic With Trial And Error To Solve The Hidden Code Sequence In This Classic Puzzle Game.|Furniture/Appliance|Jet Set Games, Inc.|HDK_1.41.0.37.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:3
4670DB45-CC624DB8-8A8CB352-B15773F5|kName|kDesc|Plum Tree Pavilion Bed|This Ornate Bed Set Is The Perfect Place To Relax And Take A Nap.|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:19
470CF76B-AD8B4E86-81D160CD-B57D6D5E|kName|kDesc|Demonic Inscribed Cabinet|Even The Most Elegant Facade Can Harbor Dark Secrets. This Is An Animated Active Item.|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:8
474B9C3C-9D1B4CFC-AF149FD7-C65FAD35|kName|kDesc|Juggernaut Observer|This Active Item Lets You Move Freely About Your Space In First Person View, Activate A Spotlight, Take Videos And Pictures And Even Customize Your Shots With Photographic Filters!|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:37
48A44719-9F4748B2-B2B8C968-91CC5AC2|kName|kDesc|Active Item - Hourglass|This Ancient Clock Has Enough Sand To Time One Hour.|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.41.0.37.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:14
48C5B24A-F81144B8-B5DAF979-FC9D9611|kName|kDesc|THX|This Is An Old THX Type Houseroid That Appears In Time Of Eve. When Placing THX, Please Note That THX Will Not Work Unless The Attached Platform Is Properly Installed. With Another Avatar ( ) Near The THX, The Owner Of The THX Can Distribute The THX To Another Avatar ( ) By pointing. The Avatar Must Be Near The THX To Receive It. THX Will Stop At The Slightest Bump Due To Hover Movement. ©Yasuhiro YOSHIURA / DIRECTIONS, Inc. This Item Is An Advanced Furniture With Additional Animations And Functions. There Is A Limit To The Number Of Items Of This Type That Can Be Placed.|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.3.6.22.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:19
48CD9130-4B2B4E67-9C66551C-4A743156|kName|kDesc|Timepieces - Water Clock|Always Know What The Time Is With This Working Clock. Exclusive To The VEEMEE 3D Printer. The Time Is Automatically Set Using The Time On Your PlayStation®3. ※ Active Items Provide More Functionality Than Normal Items. You May Only Place Limited Numbers Of The Active Items In Your Apartment Or Clubhouse At Any Time.|Furniture/Appliance|VEEMEE|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|LUA-REWARD|Res:10
48E5225E-87C74743-80CF4BF1-9A689F02|kName|kDesc|Personal Slot Machine|Personal Slot Machine. This Is An Animated Active Item.|Furniture/Appliance|Digital Leisure|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:49
48F9F6A8-F1FA410A-BBAEBF9C-4D57889A|kName|kDesc|Animated Small Desk Fountain|A Calm And Soothing Personal Fountain.|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.40.0.265.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:4
49A18105-FAAF47C0-85963A95-1FBDAC44|kName|kDesc|Doctor Who - Supreme Dalek (White) Furniture|Begin Your Mission To Conquer The Universe. Lack Of Pity, Compassion And Remorse Sold Separately. EXTERMINATE! Doctor Who Logo © 2013 And TM BBC. Dalek Image © BBC/ Terry Nation 1963. Licensed By BBC WW Ltd.|Furniture/Appliance|BBC Worldwide Limited|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:9
49A1A798-61AE4AB0-9EC65D07-8EF09C87|kName|kDesc|140'' LOOT™ Gold EOD TV - Flatscreen|For Gamers Who Have It All, Here Is A Special Edition Gold EOD TV That Let's You Watch Full Length Movies, TV Episodes, Live Shows And More With Your Friends In PlayStation®Home! The LOOT™ Entertainment On Demand TV Will Work In Any Private Space Unless The Space Comes With A Video Screen You Cant Turn Off, It Does Not Include Streaming Radio Or Audio-only Content. Now All You Need To Do Is Invite Your Friends Over, Pull Out The Popcorn And Make The Most Important Decision Of All: What Will You Watch First!? PLEASE READ BEFORE YOU PURCHASE: Due To Contractual And Rights Agreements, Some EOD Channels Are Nation Specific. Crackle Content Is ONLY Available In United States, Canada, United Kingdom, And Australia. RadioIO Is ONLY Available In The United States And Canada. In Addition, Due To Rights Issues, Countries May Not Receive The Same Content Selections Within The Channels. Only One TV Can Be Active At A Time. The LOOT™ EOD Will Work In Any Private Space, UNLESS The Space Comes With A Video Screen You Cannot Turn Off.|Furniture/Appliance|© LOOT™|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:42
49BED270-C2774D83-93E32DE1-BC90CA3F|kName|kDesc|Aquarium Table|The Perfect Accent To Any Nautical Space. This Active Item Is Home To A Variety Of Tropical Fish.|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:6
49E39BCB-48114D84-8EC53FBF-66FDD997|kName|kDesc|Leaf Green Hot Pot|Get Cooking With This Interactive Pot!|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:6
4A45FA1B-FA254925-9C4F1C5B-B64E55CB|Black Workbench|Black Workbench|Black Workbench|Black Workbench|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_XX|NOT-RWRD|Res:2
4A6B28FF-1E9044B7-91AEE3D5-E9F21740|kName|kDesc|Two Player Chess Game #4|A Chess Board Placed On A Dark Brown Table. This Game Is Available For Two Players.|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.40.0.265.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:71
4AA4E6DF-D9604FC3-BA8BE584-EACB69AC|AmericanPoolName|AmericanPoolDesc|American Pool|An American Pool Table, Ideal For Any Apartment. This Table Comes With Both Eight Ball And Nine Ball Versions Of Pool. The Game Can Be Played With Two Players, Or In A Single Player Practice Mode.|Furniture/Appliance|VEEMEE|HDK_1.60.0.450.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:55
4B66AFF6-FD7F4CBD-B097D81D-F2B6C390|kName|kDesc|PlayStation4™ #4ThePlayers|Watch The Latest PS4 Trailers And Stories In The Comfort Of Your Own Apartment.|Furniture/Appliance|MakerXX|HDK_1.82.0.17.PUB|AUTO-REWARD|Res:4
4B722FBD-B4E74726-812DC8FA-70B972EB|kName|kDesc|Giftinator 9000|The Giftinator 9000 Is The Ultimate Gift Machine! Simply Place This Appliance In Your Personal Space And Gift Unique Items To Your Friends (or Yourself!) To Boost Your Karma, Upgrade Your Giftinator, And Unlock Exclusive Rewards As You Level Up.|Furniture/Appliance|Hellfire Games, Inc.|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:388
4BD0B039-D06241DB-89024A65-97F0536F|kName|kDesc|Two Player Chess Game #5|A Light Tan Patio Table With A Chess Board Placed On It. This Game Is Available For Two Players.|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.40.0.265.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:71
4C0CCD75-10EE4632-83C540F2-FFCC9947|kName|kDesc|Gothic Manor Bed|This Bed Is Perfect For Those Who Enjoy A Darkly Lit Room. This Is An Active Item.|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.55.0.155.BETA2|NOT-RWRD|Res:19
4C9EB1A4-5FA04022-B2E95540-47041039|kName|kDesc|Bat Belfry|This Active Item Features Animated Bats!|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:18
4CD54BB0-0C994D23-B8B869CC-52702FE1|kName|kDesc|BoxBeats: Nightclub Edition|Need Even More Club Tunes To Dance The Night Away? BoxBeats: Nightclub Edition Is The Perfect Addition To Any Party Space. NB - There May Be A Delay When You Place The Item Whilst The Music Tracks Download. ※Active Items Provide More Functionality Than Normal Items. You May Only Place Limited Numbers Of The Active Items In Your Apartment Or Clubhouse At Any Time.|Furniture/Appliance|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:23
4CF288B5-3AE54371-8C655C2F-BD2A97BC|kName|kDesc|White Retro Speaker Left|The Left White Retro Speaker From The Loot™ Home Entertainment Collection.|Furniture/Appliance|© 2009 Loot™|HDK_1.3.2.16.BETA1|NOT-RWRD|Res:2
4D464A51-025A4BD8-AD2626E4-A4D10B89|kName|kDesc|CAS - Mini-gun|Developed And Manufactured By The D2O Special Weapons Division. The D2O-MRX80 Stationary Mini-gun Is A Multi-barreled Chain-gun That Can Fire .50 Caliber Shells At A Rate Of 5,000 Shots Per Minute.|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment America|HDK_1.50.0.238.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:29
4D557871-A09F4917-91E69FF7-252F2E6F|kName|kDesc|Bright-coloured Wooden Bed|A Mysterious Bright-coloured Wooden Bed That Turns Dreams Into Reality, Whether You Sleep Alone Or With Someone Else.|Furniture/Appliance|Granzella Inc.|HDK_1.82.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:182
4D59921F-274F45D3-A82DEC24-A4BE49D8|Shandor|Shandor is a mysterious antique automation from years past with immeasurable wisdom and insight into things to come. Can you unlock his secrets? Available for purchase as an Active Item from the Playstation Home Mall.|Shandor|Shandor Is A Mysterious Antique Automation From Years Past With Immeasurable Wisdom And Insight Into Things To Come. Can You Unlock His Secrets? Available For Purchase As An Active Item From The Playstation Home Mall.|Furniture/Appliance|Jet Set Games, Inc.|HDK_1.40.0.265.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:18
4D5F8F9B-D2AA4770-880E9C24-6542E7E1|kName|kDesc|50s Diner - Coffee Machine|Nothing Like A Hot Cup Of Joe To Kickstart Your Morning.|Furniture/Appliance|VEEMEE|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:18
4D9193CF-A8574F26-8BF33D3C-BE6C3A36|kName|kDesc|Forsaken Planet – Turret (Active)|Guard Your HOME With This Active Turret From Forsaken Planet, A LOOT™ Entertainment Videogame For Tablets And Smart Phones! When You Purchase This Item, You Unlock A UFO Gun* For Use In The Forsaken Planet Game. This Exclusive UFO Gun Can Only Be Unlocked In PlayStation®Home! To Retrieve Your Reward, Create Or Access Your LOOT™ Entertainment Account At The Log-in Station Located At The Forsaken Planet Globe Logo In The LOOT Space Station Hub. Looking For Even Sweeter Forsaken Planet Deals And In-game Rewards? Check Out The Forsaken Planet Ultimate Bundle In The LOOT™ Store! (*UFO Gun Unlocks Specialized Gameplay Perks Within The Forsaken Planet Videogame!) Www.lootentertainment.com|Furniture/Appliance|© LOOT™|HDK_1.66.0.144.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:11
4DC15432-5D634126-BE2DE77B-C7A8468D|kName|kDesc|Pigsty|This Active Item Unleashes Piglets That Wander Around Your Apartment.|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:11
4E02FF63-37B14686-926D124C-9AB52824|kName|kDesc|Los Penguini Brothers: Apartment Arcade Cabinet|This Classic NDreams Game Is Now Available As An Attractive Apartment Arcade Cabinet. Purchasing This Mini Game Will Allow You To Teleport To The Los Penguini Brothers Space And Play As Many Times As You Want Without The Need Of Los Penguini Brothers Tickets. Also, There Are Lots Of Classic Los Penguini Brothers Rewards To Be Won From Completing Challenges.|Furniture/Appliance|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:3
4E23270D-71ED47DA-A8F6D622-B73382BB|kName|kDesc|Hot And Bothered|A Love Meter Active Item For Your Personal Space! Press The Buttons When They Light Up. The Faster You Press, The More Points You Get. The More Points You Get, The Higher You Go. The Higher You Go, The Hotter You Are. Get All The Way To The Top To Win A Fabulous T-Shirt!|Furniture/Appliance|Mass Media Games, Inc.|HDK_1.66.0.144.PUB|AUTO-REWARD|Res:44
4E340DA8-8C4A4EE3-90371BBA-FAB99221|kName|kDesc|80'' LOOT™ Diamond EOD TV - Flatscreen|The Height Of Luxury: Own Your Very Own Blinged Out Diamond EOD TV That Let's You Watch Full Length Movies, TV Episodes, Live Shows And More With Your Friends In PlayStation®Home! The LOOT™ Entertainment On Demand TV Will Work In Any Private Space Unless The Space Comes With A Video Screen You Cant Turn Off, It Does Not Include Streaming Radio Or Audio-only Content. Now All You Need To Do Is Invite Your Friends Over, Pull Out The Popcorn And Make The Most Important Decision Of All: What Will You Watch First!? PLEASE READ BEFORE YOU PURCHASE: Due To Contractual And Rights Agreements, Some EOD Channels Are Nation Specific. Crackle Content Is ONLY Available In United States, Canada, United Kingdom, And Australia. RadioIO Is ONLY Available In The United States And Canada. In Addition, Due To Rights Issues, Countries May Not Receive The Same Content Selections Within The Channels. Only One TV Can Be Active At A Time. The LOOT™ EOD Will Work In Any Private Space, UNLESS The Space Comes With A Video Screen You Cannot Turn Off.|Furniture/Appliance|© LOOT™|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:42
4E34E748-0901471C-8031BEF8-C69321BD|kName|kDesc|Drop Science Old School Boom Box (Active Item)|Fresh Beats With Some Drop Science Style.|Furniture/Appliance|Lockwood|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|LUA-REWARD|Res:10
4E84345C-96304F45-B918C824-9C13D96A|kName|kDesc|Steel-frame Bed|A Mysterious Bed Build From Steel Frames That Turns Dreams Into Reality, Whether You Sleep Alone Or With Someone Else.|Furniture/Appliance|Granzella Inc.|HDK_1.82.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:182
4EF3DE0D-3E6442D0-8679FED6-F4832B6F|kName|kDesc|Two Player Checkers Game #4|A Green Toned Checkers Board With Red And White Pieces On Polished Auburn Coloured Desk. This Game Is Available For Two Players.|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.41.0.37.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:43
4F1A1A78-06464713-A6CAE2E8-2CEEC971|kName|kDesc|Alchemist's Chest|An Essential Tool For Any Alchemist Or Potion-maker! This Active Item Allows You To Place Up To 35 Items Around Your Personal Space Including Bottles, Jars, Ingredients And Alchemical Apparatus.|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:34
4F269B85-34CB4615-99080E5E-1C6ADBFC|kName|kDesc|Two Player Chess Game #1|A Chess Board Sitting Atop A White And Turquoise Glass Table. This Game Is Available For Two Players.|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.40.0.265.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:71
4F631DCA-91E64A9A-9BE027E4-FEA425DE|kName|kDesc|Chic Black Bed|A Mysterious Black Bed That Turns Dreams Into Reality, Whether You Sleep Alone Or With Someone Else.|Furniture/Appliance|Granzella Inc.|HDK_1.82.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:183
4F8CD2BD-0B56498F-B19928BD-838648E6|kName|kDesc|LOOT™ MIB|With The LOOT™ Mobile Internet Browser You Can Access The Sony Pictures Emporium Website (www.sonypicturesemporium.com) From Your PlayStation®Home Personal Space! Does Your Avatar Have A Shirt You Want? Well, At The Sony Pictures Emporium Website You Can Purchase The Actual Shirts, Toys, Movies, And More – IRL! Stay Connected With LOOT™ And The Sony Pictures Emporium Web Store.|Furniture/Appliance|© 2010 LOOT™|HDK_1.3.6.22.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:7
4F8ED2FE-11154732-84CB10A7-C9E2A395|kName|kDesc|Zombie Grave|This Gravestone Releases A Swarm Of Monstrously Adorable Zombies That Will Wander Around Your Apartment.|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|LUA-REWARD|Res:17
4FB6BA36-4F864853-9A99D414-78FF066D|kName|kDesc|BoxBeats: Dance 2|This Stylish Sound System Comes Jam Packed With Over 10 Amazing Dance Tracks For You And Your Friends To Listen To While You Bust Some Moves. This Active Item Also Allows You To Select Specific Tracks To Play, Set The Volume And Even Randomise The Track List. This Is An Essential Item For Your Apartment. NB - There May Be A Delay When You Place The Item Whilst The Music Tracks Download.|Furniture/Appliance|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:28
4FDBA157-53C24968-9965DCB5-344E2E90|kName|kDesc|LOOT™ Giant Boombox|Fill The Air With Music! A Must Have For Any Private Or Clubhouse Space - Invite Your Friends Over And Get The Party Started! Enjoy Endless Streams Featuring Pop, Rock, Dance, And Talk. The LOOT™ Radio Delivers Real Music To The Comfort Of Your PlayStation®Home Personal Space! PLEASE READ BEFORE YOU PURCHASE Due To Contractual And Rights Agreements, Some Channels Are Nation Specific. RadioIO Is Only Available In The United States And Canada. In Addition, Due To Rights Issues, Countries May Not Receive The Same Content Selections Within The Channels. Only One Radio Or Television Can Be Active At A Time. The LOOT Radio Will Work In Any Private Space, UNLESS The Space Comes With A Tv Or Radio You Cannot Turn Off.|Furniture/Appliance|© LOOT™|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:44
500778F0-579C439C-BB561657-7A5CA198|kName|kDesc|Doctor Who - Drone Dalek (Red) Furniture|In A Warrior Universe, These Are The Warrior Supreme. You Cant Run, You Cant Hide. The Daleks Are Here! EXTERMINATE! Doctor Who Logo © 2013 And TM BBC. Dalek Image © BBC/ Terry Nation 1963. Licensed By BBC WW Ltd.|Furniture/Appliance|BBC Worldwide Limited|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:9
501664A1-951E4CF5-A7C3E343-3581D4D6|kName|kDesc|Two Player Checkers Game #2|A Green Toned Checkers Board With Red And White Pieces On A Marble Table. This Game Is Available For Two Players.|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.41.0.37.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:43
502532B9-D79F4D9D-B561DE99-8E0D0A5D|kName|kDesc|PODI|Lockwood's Pyrotechnic Overhead Display Interface, Or PODI, Is A Friendly Little Machine That Loves It When You Interact With It. Create Incredible Displays, Or Let PODI Take Care Of It For You. Keep PODI Happy For A Special Reward.|Furniture/Appliance|Lockwood|HDK_1.60.0.450.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:176
5084ACAD-01C942DB-96497DD9-660DBFCE|kName|kDesc|Demonic Sideboard|The Dark Images Etched On This Sideboard Are Not For The Faint Of Heart. This Is An Animated Active Item.|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:8
510C8F3E-FBA94003-B2575084-55A55911|kName|kDesc|Engine Grill|It Is Your Own Grill Made Out Of Engine Parts. You Can Open And Close The Lid, Plus Control The Flame Height. This Is An Interactive Active Object Item.|Furniture/Appliance|Game Mechanics|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:15
51EE95A6-04CC49AF-B194D5B0-5D74FD31|kName|kDesc|Ungawa Monument|Show Your Respect For The Ungawa Monument, Wear Your Mask And Behold The Spectacle.|Furniture/Appliance|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.41.0.37.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:15
5204014B-289844B8-9920AE96-95771487|kName|kDesc|Flaming Guitar With Solo|This Oversized Ax Is The Perfect Showcase Item For Any Rock Fan's Home Space. Activate To Hear A Solo So Hot, The Guitar Itself Bursts Into Flames!|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.52.0.2.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:14
520D01D7-5DBD4BFE-8DBA790C-E1D1EDCE|kName|kDesc|240'' LOOT™ Platinum EOD TV - Flatscreen|Discover The Benefits Of Owning Your Very Own Platinum EOD TV That Let's You Watch Full Length Movies, TV Episodes, Live Shows And More With Your Friends In PlayStation®Home! The LOOT™ Entertainment On Demand TV Will Work In Any Private Space Unless The Space Comes With A Video Screen You Cant Turn Off, It Does Not Include Streaming Radio Or Audio-only Content. Now All You Need To Do Is Invite Your Friends Over, Pull Out The Popcorn And Make The Most Important Decision Of All: What Will You Watch First!? PLEASE READ BEFORE YOU PURCHASE: Due To Contractual And Rights Agreements, Some EOD Channels Are Nation Specific. Crackle Content Is ONLY Available In United States, Canada, United Kingdom, And Australia. RadioIO Is ONLY Available In The United States And Canada. In Addition, Due To Rights Issues, Countries May Not Receive The Same Content Selections Within The Channels. Only One TV Can Be Active At A Time. The LOOT™ EOD Will Work In Any Private Space, UNLESS The Space Comes With A Video Screen You Cannot Turn Off.|Furniture/Appliance|© LOOT™|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:42
52BB0011-05ED4702-B8508EAD-256AB0BC|Stage 2 Speaker|Stage 2 Speaker Description|Stage 2 Speaker|A Wood-panelled Speaker Set Prop.|Furniture/Appliance|© LOOT™|HDK_1.66.0.144.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:2
5514B9D8-21A84C5B-BC5E9F46-4615EAAB|kName|kDesc|Spunland Plant|An Interactive Spunland Plant For Your Apartment. Responds To Gestures.|Furniture/Appliance|Madmunki|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:22
5582149E-692745A9-8FF780B8-E3AA4FA5|kName|kDesc|Mixer|Mixer|Furniture/Appliance|MakerXX|HDK_1.3.0.130.BETA2|AUTO-REWARD|Res:2
566564C1-AC6B4248-874D6240-B9AA0290|kName|kDesc|3D Printer|Experience The Latest In Virtual-to-real Technology With The VEEMEE 3D Printer. Place In Your Personal Space And Choose From A Wide Selection Of Exclusive Virtual Items To Print Out For You And Your Friends. VEEMEE 3D Printer Vouchers Can Be Purchased From The Printer Or From The VEEMEE Store.|Furniture/Appliance|VEEMEE|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:75
56DD3BF7-C6B24DE6-8554CAFF-9DBE31C3|kName|kDesc|Star Map|Boldly Go Where No User Has Gone Before With This Galactic Star Map. Exclusive To The VEEMEE 3D Printer|Furniture/Appliance|VEEMEE|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|LUA-REWARD|Res:6
56FE4277-CA334784-AD48035A-FF20D7B2|kName|kDesc|Heavy Water E3 Peeps|Heavy Water Reward From Playstation®Home's 2011 E3 Booth.|Furniture/Appliance|Heavy Water|HDK_1.41.0.37.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:17
5705465A-8A18418E-B3F68184-7BC4CB3C|kName|kDesc|Intellivision® ASTROSMASH Arcade Game|Play The Thrilling Intellivision® Game Astrosmash In This Updated Version Created Exclusively For PlayStation®Home Whenever You Want With This Astrosmash Arcade Game! Save The World From Falling Meteors, Alien UFOs And Killer Satellites! A Fast Action Challenge That Gets Faster And Harder As You Get Better! You And Your Friends Will Love This Classic-style Arcade Game With Its Bright, Colorful Game Screen And Exciting Cabinet Artwork! Earn The Following Four Exclusive Astrosmash Themed Rewards During Gameplay: An Animating T-shirt, Glitzy Game Poster, Gold-plated Trophy, And 6 Foot Themed Mobile.|Furniture/Appliance|Realtime Associates, Inc.|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:3
570D96EE-690C4B53-B09C1850-B8B1195E|kName|kDesc|MyBedroom - Burgundy - Bed|An Interactive MyBedroom Bed With Sleeping Animation.|Furniture/Appliance|VEEMEE|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:18
5726BBFD-A71642DC-BDEBE052-CD8C44F5|kName|kDesc|Charcoal Champ Soundtrack Radio|This Bass And Amp Are Sweet Like Molasses And Will Fill Your Apartment With The Sounds Of The Complete Charcoal Champ Original Soundtrack By Jeremiah Wallace.|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:4
57301EA2-B4A64520-8159AE4F-A0E3100F|kName|kDesc|PODI Halloween Edition|Lockwood's Pyrotechnic Overhead Display Interface, Or PODI, Is A Friendly Little Machine That Loves It When You Interact With It. Create Incredible Displays, Or Let PODI Take Care Of It For You. Keep PODI Happy For A Special Reward.|Furniture/Appliance|Lockwood|HDK_1.60.0.451.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:176
5828F419-8F2F4CF0-A7E4A0F4-F8118550|kName|kDesc|Clamshell Chair|Adds An Aquatic Accent To Any Space. This Active Item Is The Perfect Seat For Any Water-dweller|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:16
58DF0A52-E42E461C-AC6CBFAE-A50C7B63|kName|kDesc|Active Item - Alien Spaceship|Watch As This Alien Tries Desperately To Get His Spaceship Airborne.|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.50.0.238.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:10
5918FAED-59274690-B13D51F1-59C01890|kName|kDesc|Nautilus Chair|The Perfect Accent To Any Nautical Space, This Active Chair Opens When You Approach And Closes When You Leave.|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:16
59239189-86EF48C3-9ADCE70C-105A1C2B|kName|kDesc|LOOT™ Pink Jambox|Fill The Air With Music! A Must Have For Any Private Or Clubhouse Space - Invite Your Friends Over And Get The Party Started! Enjoy Endless Streams Featuring Pop, Rock, Dance, And Talk. The LOOT™ Radio Delivers Real Music To The Comfort Of Your PlayStation®Home Personal Space! PLEASE READ BEFORE YOU PURCHASE Due To Contractual And Rights Agreements, Some Channels Are Nation Specific. RadioIO Is Only Available In The United States And Canada. In Addition, Due To Rights Issues, Countries May Not Receive The Same Content Selections Within The Channels. Only One Radio Or Television Can Be Active At A Time. The LOOT Radio Will Work In Any Private Space, UNLESS The Space Comes With A Tv Or Radio You Cannot Turn Off.|Furniture/Appliance|© LOOT™|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:44
59708683-66EF4C59-9E174EFA-11901292|kName|kDesc|Las Vegas Suite Contemporary White Bed|Lie Down On This Cozy And Stylish Bed After A Night Of Partying. This Is An Active Item.|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.60.0.451.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:21
5990EF03-982148BA-80BE18DA-FB680B30|kName|kDesc|Personal Video Blackjack|Personal Video Blackjack. This Is An Animated Active Item.|Furniture/Appliance|Digital Leisure|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:111
59D0ED71-5B8C40F5-B062A81F-A167D900|kName|kDesc|Bearskin Rug|This Active Item Contains Custom Poses For Your Avatar.|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:23
59D0F24F-22EF47C9-84FB25D9-C1CD127A|kName|kDesc|Nebula Air Ship - Cloud Bed|Lay Back And Relax As You Count Sheep While On Top Of Your Silky Circular Bed. This Is An Active Item.|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.55.0.155.BETA2|NOT-RWRD|Res:19
59D549B2-115C4FF7-BEBB7AA1-02983727|kName|kDesc|Personal Craps Table|The Most Exciting Dice Game In The Casino Is Now Playable In Your Own Space. Just Place This Active Item Down And You, And Your Friends, Can Roll The Dice As Long As You Want. With This Personal Craps Table, You'll Be Getting The Same Experience As Players In The Paradise Springs Casino. If You Or Your Friends Run Out Of Chips Just Join The Game Again And You'll Be Topped Up. This Item Is Perfect For Hosting Your Very Own Gaming Night. This Is An Animated Active Item.|Furniture/Appliance|Digital Leisure|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:130
5A3C5BC0-8D804C51-950446B1-69A746C0|kName|kDesc|Essence Of Winter|This Active Item Will Turn Any Personal Space Into A Winter Wonderland!|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:14
5A723320-CFBC4FDC-AA1B7370-B66A1524|kName|kDesc|Hed Kandi Indoor Fireworks|Sign Up For The Free 30 Day Trial Of Music Unlimited On The PlayStation®Store To Listen To The Best In Hed Kandi And Much Much More!|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|LUA-REWARD|Res:8
5AC21D1D-227349D8-8EB5D66F-29F2228A|kName|kDesc|Essence Of The Tides|This Active Item Allows You To Turn Any Personal Space Into An Undersea Abode – Also Lets Your Avatar Swim!|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:33
5BE95FB5-BDB148A9-8A8407C5-372469AC|kName|kDesc|Escape Earth Mode: Shooter|Escape Virus Mode: Shooter Can Be Played In This Arcade Cabinet. You Can Get Home Reward If You Fulfill Certain Conditions.|Furniture/Appliance|O-Two Inc.|HDK_1.60.0.450.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:3
5BFACB7F-31F34550-B95DB5D2-FC25DEF8|kName|kDesc|LOOT™ Fog Machine|Its Time To Set The Mood With The LOOT™ Fog Machine. With Four Control Settings (Light, Moderate, Heavy And Intense) And Colour Settings, Its Perfect For Any Party. Check Out The LOOT™ Actives Bundle For An Incredible Deal!|Furniture/Appliance|©LOOT™|HDK_1.65.0.139.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:25
5C03B966-937D4554-A1398457-271257C7|kName|kDesc|Shooting Earth|This Is An Arcade Cabinet Where You Can Play Shooting Earth. You Can Get Home Rewards If You Fulfill Certain Conditions.|Furniture/Appliance|O-Two Inc.|HDK_1.60.0.450.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:3
5CDFCBA1-221544CA-8B8BA512-285E7F5B|kName|kDesc|Bit Buddy Character|This Bit Will Follow You Around Your Apartment And Speak To You. 1 For Yes, 0 For No.|Furniture/Appliance|Disney Interactive Studios|HDK_1.40.0.265.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:13
5D09B676-E103497D-9940B7DE-37AAEBC6|kName|kDesc|Frogger Arcade Cabinet|Frogger Arcade Cabinet ©2012 Konami Digital Entertainment FOCAL Emulation Technology ©2009-2012 Code Mystics Inc.|Furniture/Appliance|Konami Digital Entertainment|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:3
5D197B11-7E5E42F0-A0EB29B5-B0AE64BE|kName|kDesc|Atari CAT Box|Atari's Computer Assisted Troubleshooter Is An Essential Tool For Arcade Game Owners. Use The CAT Box To Adjust Settings In Your Arcade Games. Created By Code Mystics Inc.|Furniture/Appliance|Atari Interactive Inc.|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:3
5D22E7F0-4A674651-A5553AF7-29982551|kName|kDesc|BoxBeats: Rock|This Powerful Sound System Comes Jam Packed With Over 10 Rocking Tracks For You And Your Friends To Listen To While You Rock Out. This Active Item Also Allows You To Select Specific Tracks To Play, Set The Volume And Even Randomise The Track List. This Is An Essential Item For Your Apartment.|Furniture/Appliance|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:25
5D527426-EBF54CF6-B380A44E-955AFB71|kName|kDesc|Heavy Strike Surveillance Helicopter|Use The Latest Technology From The D2O Research Facility To Take To The Skies And Capture Incriminating And Informative Pictures. You Can Fly The Heavy Strike Surveillance Helicopter Around Any Personal Space And Take Photos Of What It Sees. Twelve Users Can Launch From One Heli-pad! 			-Fly Around Any Private Space 			-Take Photos With Or Without The Helicopter In The Shot 			-4 People Can Use The Surveillance Helicopter At Once 			-Each User Gets Assigned A Different Color To Accent Their Surveillance Helicopter|Furniture/Appliance|Heavy Water|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:42
5ECAD541-FA7D4DB4-8F487701-B7B62FB6|kName|kDesc|Slap In The Face-O-Matic|Place This Interactable Animated Slap In The Face-O-Matic In Your Apartment, And Then Proceed To Slap Yourself Or Your Friends In Their Face. Hilarity Ensues.|Furniture/Appliance|Codename Games|HDK_1.41.0.37.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:11
5FC9D014-7BA143AB-A9E9AB9E-F0D134FD|kName|kDesc|Memory Hack Arcade Cabinet|Show Off Your Brain Power As You Match Symbols In This Classic Test Of Memory.|Furniture/Appliance|Jet Set Games, Inc.|HDK_1.41.0.37.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:3
5FF3CBFC-05104471-8514EB55-F0C62FBF|kName|kDesc|Music Unlimited Outdoor Fireworks|Get To The PlayStation®Store Now And Try A 30 Day Trial Of Music Unlimited For Free. Music Unlimited Gives You Access To All The Music You Could Ever Want At Home, Online Or On The Go Via Your PlayStation®3, PlayStation®4, Mobile Phone, PlayStation®Vita, PC, Tablet Or Other Sony Connected Devices. Enjoy Millions Of Songs Advert Free And Use Offline Features To Listen To Your Playlists Even When You Have No Internet Connection!|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.82.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:8
60575C5C-98C649E2-A64DDF82-BC3002B5|kName|kDesc|240'' LOOT™ EOD TV - Wall Mounted|PLEASE READ BEFORE YOU PURCHASE: Due To Contractual And Rights Agreements, Some EOD Channels Are Nation Specific. Crackle Content Is ONLY Available In United States, Canada, United Kingdom, And Australia. RadioIO Is ONLY Available In The United States And Canada. In Addition, Due To Rights Issues, Countries May Not Receive The Same Content Selections Within The Channels. Only One TV Can Be Active At A Time. The LOOT EOD Will Work In Any Private Space, UNLESS The Space Comes With A Video Screen You Cannot Turn Off. Watch Full Length Movies, TV Episodes, Live Shows And More With Your Friends On The Largest Television Screen Available In PlayStation®Home! The LOOT™ Entertainment On Demand TV Will Work In Any Private Space Unless The Space Comes With A Video Screen You Cant Turn Off, It Does Not Include Streaming Radio Or Audio-only Content. This Bundle-exclusive Wall Mounted TV Works With The FREE LOOT™ TV Wall Mount (found In The LOOT™ Store.) Simply Hang The Mount On The Wall Like A Picture Frame Then Hook Your Wall Mounted EOD TV On It. Decorating Has Never Been So Easy!|Furniture/Appliance|© LOOT™|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:42
60A68043-2CD149D7-BC42BA4F-5095602C|kName|kDesc|What The Bleep Peep - Heavy Pet - Bone White|What The Bleep Peep Is Bad To The Bone! This Naughty Little Peep Will Bring You Hours Of Fun In Your Apartment! You Can Control Your Peep With Custom Animations And Special Peep Moves!|Furniture/Appliance|Heavy Water|HDK_1.66.0.144.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:25
60E8CABA-70E24819-87F0AC4E-9B42363F|kName|kDesc|Single Player Solitaire Game #2|Play A Game Of Solitaire On This Elaborate White Stone Table.|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.41.0.37.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:78
6122F44D-669F41F3-AAA0D288-3114EBDD|kName|kDesc|60'' LOOT™ EOD TV - Wall Mounted|PLEASE READ BEFORE YOU PURCHASE: Due To Contractual And Rights Agreements, Some EOD Channels Are Nation Specific. Crackle Content Is ONLY Available In United States, Canada, United Kingdom, And Australia. RadioIO Is ONLY Available In The United States And Canada. In Addition, Due To Rights Issues, Countries May Not Receive The Same Content Selections Within The Channels. Only One TV Can Be Active At A Time. The LOOT EOD Will Work In Any Private Space, UNLESS The Space Comes With A Video Screen You Cannot Turn Off. Watch Full Length Movies, TV Episodes, Live Shows And More With Your Friends In PlayStation®Home! The LOOT™ Entertainment On Demand TV Will Work In Any Private Space Unless The Space Comes With A Video Screen You Cant Turn Off, It Does Not Include Streaming Radio Or Audio-only Content. This Bundle-exclusive Wall Mounted TV Works With The FREE LOOT™ TV Wall Mount (found In The LOOT™ Store.) Simply Hang The Mount On The Wall Like A Picture Frame Then Hook Your Wall Mounted EOD TV On It. Decorating Has Never Been So Easy!|Furniture/Appliance|© LOOT™|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:42
6195EC88-963A41B2-81296087-986DD5A2|kName|kDesc|Clara's Saucepan|This Active Item Will Release Clara.|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.65.0.139.BETA|LUA-REWARD|Res:17
61B053A1-1666430C-BA68254D-08C96C34|kName|kDesc|The LED Ticker - Standard|Why Say It When You Can Write It! Choose From A Range Of Great Colours In Which To Display Your Message. Whether It Be A Note To Yourself Or A Friendly Message To Your Friends, Every Apartment Needs The LED Ticker. This Is A Mini Game.|Furniture/Appliance|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.82.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:5
61D617D4-260B4B9B-9613001B-DB0796F3|kName|kDesc|Carousel|This Active Item Is A Real Working Carousel!|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:14
6250386A-10BF4475-A8FBA4A4-5426E777|kName|kDesc|Sweetie Peep - Heavy Pet - Perfect Pink|Sweetie Pie Will Melt Your Heart As Your Favorite New Peep! Bring Sweetie Pie With You Into Your Apartment And Let The Fun Begin. Control Her With Custom Animations And Special Peep Moves!|Furniture/Appliance|Heavy Water|HDK_1.66.0.144.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:25
62524649-5DCE408C-96904998-D847403F|kName|kDesc|Simple Beehive|This Active Item Releases Bees That Fly Around Your Apartment.|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:6
62758C60-993E48CF-9C8187A7-90D9F217|name|description|Ghostbusters™ VHS Camcorder|A Decorative Non-functional Ghostbusters™ Prop For PlayStation®Home Personal Spaces.|Furniture/Appliance|© 2009 Columbia Pictures Industries, Inc.|HDK_1.3.6.22.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:2
63C0E782-E2B9496C-B5D44E29-31AA4E1C|kName|kDesc|BoxBeats Mini: Dance|This Stylish Sound System Comes Jam Packed With Over 10 Amazing Dance Tracks For You And Your Friends To Listen To While You Bust Some Moves. This Active Item Also Allows You To Select Specific Tracks To Play, Set The Volume And Even Randomise The Track List. This Is An Essential Item For Your Apartment. This Item Has The Same Music Tracks As The Original, But The Object Representing This Item Is 75% Smaller In Physical Size. NB - There May Be A Delay When You Place The Item Whilst The Music Tracks Download.|Furniture/Appliance|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:28
63CC18CF-4E204EAE-9A140570-9ADCF990|kName|kDesc|Valentine's Gift|This Active Item Contains Valentine Gifts For You And Your Friends. You Can Also Gift ONE Sparkling Diamond Ring (male And Female) To The Friend Of Your Choosing. Choose Wisely!|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:24
64C30B27-09D44645-96548471-0BCFDD9A|kName|kDesc|Vintage Jazz Radio|This Free Standing Radio Plays Smooth And Energetic Jazz From Yesterday And Today. All Wrapped In Our Advanced Player.|Furniture/Appliance|Game Mechanics|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:15
6530336C-6CE44CBD-8A9BBCCA-08696A4D|kName|kDesc|Adventure Cocktail Cabinet|Atari 2600's Adventure In Exclusive Arcade Table Top Form. Adventure® ©2012 Atari Interactive Inc. All Rights Reserved. Adventure® Is A Trademark Owned By Atari Interactive Inc. FOCAL Emulation Technology ©2009-2012 Code Mystics Inc.|Furniture/Appliance|Atari Interactive Inc.|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:3
653E30CC-6A8E4730-98F0BF72-0CD61F9A|kName|kDesc|Mini Lucille|Deploy This Amazing Sky Skiff And Watch It Fly Around Your Apartment|Furniture/Appliance|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.50.0.238.BETA|AUTO-REWARD|Res:9
657CF753-A11A4082-8BF4EC6D-5D9346F0|kName|kDesc|Two Player Checkers Game #1|A Green Toned Checkers Board With Red And White Pieces On A Modern Glass Table. This Game Is Available For Two Players.|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.41.0.37.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:43
6580F7C6-93F64D96-8FCC04A0-A2038ECB|kName|kDesc|Pooyan Arcade Cabinet|Pooyan Arcade Cabinet ©2013 Konami Digital Entertainment FOCAL Emulation Technology ©2009-2013 Code Mystics Inc.|Furniture/Appliance|Konami Digital Entertainment|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:3
65FD7D8F-2E34450D-9FCC311D-55CAE107|kName|kDesc|Sodium Telepads|Teleportation Has Never Been Easier! This Revolutionary New Item Contains Two Sodium Telepads - Activate The Item To Place The Second Sodium Telepad In Your Apartment. Just Walk On Top Of Either Of The Sodium Telepads And Watch Yourself Beam From One To The Other In Seconds. Explore Your Apartment In Ways You Have Never Imagined Before! Courtesy Of TelVec, For All Your Teleportation Needs. Please Note, The Sodium Telepad Does Not Function In Clubhouses.|Furniture/Appliance|Sodium - Lockwood|HDK_1.70.0.88.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:33
660116BB-FD364FF1-B67B6F71-2BD91AFF|kName|kDesc|Weapon Cabinet|This Weapon Cabinet Contains All The Essentials For Any Supernatural Hunter! Place Up To 40 Weapons Around Your Apartment To Help You Prepare For Whatever Monstrous Creature You May Need To Face.|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:46
6610D47F-B07F4148-8F09BF3C-873D5BBE|kName|kDesc|Grandfather Clock|Make Sure You Wind This Every Morning. This Is An Animated Active Item.|Furniture/Appliance|Digital Leisure|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|AUTO-REWARD|Res:7
6678AF52-817C450F-AA646CCF-88747B9E|kName|Kdesc|Go Fish Tank|A Fish Tank Populated With All The Fish You Have Caught In Go Fish|Furniture/Appliance|VEEMEE|HDK_1.60.0.450.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:68
66BC5640-5171484C-934D5C82-1612C4E6|kName|kDesc|Cobalt Blue Blender|Get Cooking With This Interactive Blender!|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:14
66DE5B7F-E8D041A9-AF60C363-A5AF3B6A|kName|kDesc|Demonic Antique Wood-Burning Stove|The Charred Remains Resting Within Seem Strangely Familiar In Shape... This Is An Animated Active Item.|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:8
678812A4-8DAB450C-96F40677-40E1D970|kName|kDesc|NDreams Luxury Hot Tub|This Luxurious, Beautifully Sculpted Hot Tub Is Perfect For Your Apartment. Hang Out With Up To Five People And Choose From A Variety Of Coloured Lights To Set The Mood. This Appliance Uses 6 Furniture Slots.|Furniture/Appliance|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:6
67C68CC5-69F842F8-A92C0889-8EB486A0|kName|kDesc|Musical Tiki Bar|Bring An Exotic Island Vibe To Your Space With The Musical Tiki Bar, Featuring Flickering Torches, Glowing Lights, And Tropical Lounge Music. Invite Your Best Friends To Pull Up A Stool, And Make Any Hour Happy Hour!|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.65.0.139.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:9
67F85C4D-950D4C89-BB966086-CE7073ED|kName|kDesc|Werewolf Tree|This Tree Attracts A Swarm Of Monstrously Adorable Werewolves That Will Wander Around Your Apartment. Awarded To The Community For Recruiting 750,000 Werewolves In Serenity Plaza.|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|LUA-REWARD|Res:14
684050E1-5AED11E1-A2670018-8BDCDECF|kName|kDesc|Gateway To Mercia: Fractured Realms|A Broken World Is In Need Of Heroes, Ready Yourself, A Battle Is Coming!|Furniture/Appliance|Lockwood|HDK_1.60.0.450.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:44
68B480CA-8A504685-82252DE1-8D524362|kName|kDesc|Dragon Rider: Golden|Ride The Majestic Golden Drake Around Your Personal Spaces With Your Friends. These Dragons Can Shoot Projectiles Of All Five Types: Fire, Ice, Lightning, Earth And Flower-power!|Furniture/Appliance|Heavy Water|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:76
68C6B1F9-66B44C21-AE8EF0B1-2F2F0CD2|kName|kDesc|Reclining Deck Armchair|Deck Armchair Advanced Furniture For Laying Down In Various Positions.|Furniture/Appliance|Granzella Inc.|HDK_1.82.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:107
68F7E5F0-54C64DBC-99B85E56-A0F9EEE9|kName|kDesc|Creepy Coffer|This Active Item Is Filled With Everything You Need To Decorate For A Haunting Halloween! Place Up To 35 Terrifying Ornaments In Any Personal Space For Only 7 Furniture Slots!|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:38
69363D4B-1E744002-BF3E0B86-418F1C0C|kName|kDesc|Brigitte - Brimstone Dancer|Meet Brigitte, Female Guardian Of Graves. Her Dance Moves Captivate All. Brigitte Will Put A Hex On You Because When She Dances, You Cant Take Your Eyes Off Her.|Furniture/Appliance|Mass Media|HDK_1.50.0.238.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:18
6A33F726-F7264F16-AA8B804F-37D00EDD|kName|kDesc|Paparazzi|This Paparazzi Might Blind You With Their Camera Flashes, But They Will Make You Feel Like The Biggest Star In The World As They Cheer For You.|Furniture/Appliance|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.52.0.2.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:7
6A968476-0FB84E67-A2E14F48-5B71AF7B|kName|kDesc|Drop Science Bling Boom Box (Active Item)|Fresh Beats With Some Drop Science Style.|Furniture/Appliance|Lockwood|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:10
6A9D3B9B-40FF4C85-9260DF28-89D0F168|kName|kDesc|Cherry Red Hot Pot|Get Cooking With This Interactive Pot!|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:6
6C31A669-C58E463F-989F1F43-BE18F158|kName|kDesc|Bootleggers '29 Radio|Listen Here, All You Hoods And Dames; The Bootleggers '29 Radio Is Now Available For Your Personal Space! Taken Straight From The Exclusive First Person Shooter For PlayStation®Home, This Active Music Item Features A Vintage Console Design And Three Swingin' Tunes From The Bootleggers Era. Pick One Up, And Give Your Joint Some Speakeasy Style Today!|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.55.0.155.BETA2|NOT-RWRD|Res:14
6C33AA44-E634488B-9DB2719A-BB640F25|kName|kDesc|PlayStation® All-Stars Battle Royale™: Beat Down|An Active Item Version Of The PlayStation® All-Stars Battle Royale™: Beat Down Mini Game.|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|AUTO-REWARD|Res:35
6C47631B-519C4F51-A53E9599-801FB2AE|kName|kDesc|Phantom 5000 Beat Machine|Add Some Bass To Your Space! The Phantom 5000 Beat Machine Features Illuminated Drum Pads, An Active Visualizer Screen, And 20 Bangin' Hip Hop Beats.|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.52.0.2.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:41
6D36B801-97464C8F-84F33039-56C27D88|kName|kDesc|Demonic Victorian Dining Chair|Dark Stains On The Wood Speak To The Horrors That Have Befallen This Chair's Former Occupants.... Or They May Have Just Been Really Messy Eaters. This Is An Animated Active Item.|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:8
6D82D92E-C2C941C7-9288192A-C279C1F6|kName|kDesc|Active Item - Birthday Cake|Happy Birthday To You!|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.50.0.238.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:7
6DA15744-1D144BA4-ACD05991-92E8B1F0|kName|kDesc|Star Projector|You Can Never Have Enough Stars To Decorate Your Room With. This Is An Active Item.|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.52.0.2.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:10
6E6935BD-871D41B5-A06B5E6A-6081A800|kName|kDesc|The Nightclub: Confetti Cannon|Bring Even More Life To The Party With The Confetti Cannon, And Set Down Several For Added Effect. ※Active Items Provide More Functionality Than Normal Items. You May Only Place Limited Numbers Of The Active Items In Your Apartment Or Clubhouse At Any Time.|Furniture/Appliance|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:9
701BFCB3-27804E8A-8A6DDC80-848B42F3|kName|kDesc|140'' LOOT™ EOD TV - Flatscreen|PLEASE READ BEFORE YOU PURCHASE: Due To Contractual And Rights Agreements, Some EOD Channels Are Nation Specific. Crackle Content Is ONLY Available In United States, Canada, United Kingdom, And Australia. RadioIO Is ONLY Available In The United States And Canada. In Addition, Due To Rights Issues, Countries May Not Receive The Same Content Selections Within The Channels. Only One TV Can Be Active At A Time. The LOOT EOD Will Work In Any Private Space, UNLESS The Space Comes With A Video Screen You Cannot Turn Off. Watch Full Length Movies, TV Episodes, Live Shows And More With Your Friends In PlayStation®Home! The LOOT™ Entertainment On Demand TV Will Work In Any Private Space Unless The Space Comes With A Video Screen You Cant Turn Off, It Does Not Include Streaming Radio Or Audio-only Content. Now All You Need To Do Is Invite Your Friends Over, Pull Out The Popcorn And Make The Most Important Decision Of All: What Will You Watch First!?|Furniture/Appliance|© LOOT™|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:42
702338DA-E9D640D1-89202260-72DF2FB8|kName|kDesc|Pulp Music Radio|Songs Reminiscent Of 1960's Spy Films, Spaghetti Westerns And Beach Movies. All Wrapped In Our Advanced Player.|Furniture/Appliance|Game Mechanics|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:15
70406CE8-C7114299-9E5F14FB-8E09C737|kName|kDesc|LOOT™ Active Camera|Record Videos Straight To Your XMB! Pause And Resume Recording For Sweet In-camera Editing. Feel Like Uploading The Video Straight To YouTube™? Well, Now You Can. Since The LOOT Active Camera Will Work In Any Of Your Personal Spaces, The Possibilities Are Endless! So Get Out There And Start Shooting, Machinimators!!|Furniture/Appliance|© 2010 LOOT™. All Rights Reserved.|HDK_1.65.0.139.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:22
706593F7-59484514-953F97DD-CF1C6237|kName|kDesc|Smoke Machine (Blue)|Add A Little Atmosphere With This Great Blue Smoke Machine.|Furniture/Appliance|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.52.0.2.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:5
710C4811-009F4F30-9FFD36CD-7158E3FD|kName|kDesc|Penguin Igloo|This Active Item Creates 3 Adorable Penguins To Roam About Your Space.|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:20
710D6A7D-6C984DFC-BB6CB559-39E57616|kName|kDesc|Holiday Music Box (Silver)|This Active Item Plays The Following Songs: Silent Night, Jingle Bells And Deck The Halls.|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:13
713F189C-0B4C4E00-A87DB426-87D2185A|kName|kDesc|60'' LOOT™ Gold EOD TV - Flatscreen|For Gamers Who Have It All, Here Is A Special Edition Gold EOD TV That Let's You Watch Full Length Movies, TV Episodes, Live Shows And More With Your Friends In PlayStation®Home! The LOOT™ Entertainment On Demand TV Will Work In Any Private Space Unless The Space Comes With A Video Screen You Cant Turn Off, It Does Not Include Streaming Radio Or Audio-only Content. Now All You Need To Do Is Invite Your Friends Over, Pull Out The Popcorn And Make The Most Important Decision Of All: What Will You Watch First!? PLEASE READ BEFORE YOU PURCHASE: Due To Contractual And Rights Agreements, Some EOD Channels Are Nation Specific. Crackle Content Is ONLY Available In United States, Canada, United Kingdom, And Australia. RadioIO Is ONLY Available In The United States And Canada. In Addition, Due To Rights Issues, Countries May Not Receive The Same Content Selections Within The Channels. Only One TV Can Be Active At A Time. The LOOT™ EOD Will Work In Any Private Space, UNLESS The Space Comes With A Video Screen You Cannot Turn Off.|Furniture/Appliance|© LOOT™|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:42
715791DD-D4414C38-BDE3BE76-FCA4B596|kName|kDesc|Timepieces - Contemporary Grandfather Clock|Always Know What The Time Is With This Working Clock. The Time Is Automatically Set Using The Time On Your PlayStation®3.|Furniture/Appliance|VEEMEE|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:8
7215DBA0-02CB4776-8DA5A247-7E864A2C|kName|kDesc|Luxury 6 Person Bed (Gothic)|You And Up To Five Other Friends Can Relax On This Interactive Bed That Includes High Quality Motion Captured Animations. ※Active Items Provide More Functionality Than Normal Items. You May Only Place Limited Numbers Of The Active Items In Your Apartment Or Clubhouse At Any Time.|Furniture/Appliance|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.82.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:17
72949E10-C0DC476E-BAD57C92-31804BDC|kName|kDesc|Mahogany Tower Speaker|The Mahogany Tower Speaker From The Loot™ Home Entertainment Collection.|Furniture/Appliance|© 2009 Loot™|HDK_1.3.2.16.BETA1|NOT-RWRD|Res:2
72DC5ED2-E47444A7-849AA7AC-419BD60F|kName|kDesc|DIY Racer (incl. Pink Car)|DIY Racer Is A Fun Mini-game That Turns Your Apartment Into An Exciting Race Track! Use Your Existing Furniture Or Our Specially Designed Furniture To Create Jumps, Bridges, And Tunnels To Create The Coolest Track You Can Imagine. Invite Your Friends And Race Against Them On The Track That You Designed! Do Tricks To Unlock Some Cool Stuff! This Mini-game Includes The Sweet Pink RC Car!|Furniture/Appliance|Codeglue B.V.|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:85
73708530-A8F94D42-AAAC7382-3FF770B0|kName|kDesc|Mummy Sarcophagus|This Sarcophagus Releases A Swarm Of Monstrously Adorable Mummies That Will Wander Around Your Apartment.|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|LUA-REWARD|Res:17
73C36656-7FFE4486-B60C346F-486DFE91|kName|kDesc|LOOT™ Tiki Torch - Single|Light Up The Party With This Tiki Torch From LOOT™ Entertainment!|Furniture/Appliance|© LOOT™|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:9
74A2A68A-76C049BB-87DFAAD4-141D11D9|kName|kDesc|Customisable Holiday Tree 2011|Deck Out Your Holiday Tree By Choosing Between The Available Holiday Decorations. It's Your Winter - Do What You Want To!|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.55.0.155.BETA2|AUTO-REWARD|Res:13
74B1246A-6FFB453C-B65D1DA9-7F903F9A|kName|kDesc|LOOT™ Grandfather Clock|Never Lose Track Of Time In HOME With The LOOT™ Grandfather Clock. The Clock Matches The Time Of Your PlayStation®3 And Chimes In The Hour With A Cuckoo Bird And Dancers. Dont Want To Wait For The Hour? Dont Worry, You Can Play The Animation Any Time. Check Out The LOOT™ Actives Bundle For An Incredible Deal!|Furniture/Appliance|©LOOT™|HDK_1.66.0.144.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:26
74BCC53C-88AC4092-AD93DED1-41DD5D19|kName|kDesc|LOOT™ Outdoor Oven|No Backyard Party Is Complete Without An Outdoor Oven!|Furniture/Appliance|© LOOT™|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:2
74C2B8BD-6B094746-81EB1369-F51772CD|kName|kDesc|Lunar Lander Cabaret Cabinet|Atari's Lunar Lander Arcade Game In Compact Cabaret Cabinet Form. Lunar Lander® ©2012 Atari Interactive Inc. All Rights Reserved. Lunar Lander® Is A Trademark Owned By Atari Interactive Inc. FOCAL Emulation Technology ©2009-2012 Code Mystics Inc.|Furniture/Appliance|Atari Interactive Inc.|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:3
75311CB0-9D044149-9A96ECA0-A02714A3|kName|kDesc|Audi Piano - Trophy Cabinet|Impress Your Friends With Your Audi Piano Trophy Collection.|Furniture/Appliance|AUDI AG|HDK_1.55.0.155.BETA2|AUTO-REWARD|Res:27
75481BEF-E4D04E2C-A9A9468E-A42A52F2|kName|kDesc|Personal Dining Experience - 2 Person Table|Entertain Your Friends In The Privacy Of Your Own Personal Space With The VEEMEE Personal Dining Experience. Guests Can Receive Up To 4 Food Reward Items. This Table Has Two Seats.|Furniture/Appliance|VEEMEE|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:59
7558EA01-116140D9-9187EBB0-1F5AC3CC|kName|kDesc|Lunar Lander Arcade Cabinet|Atari's Lunar Lander Arcade Game In A Full-sized Classic Arcade Cabinet. Lunar Lander® ©2012 Atari Interactive Inc. All Rights Reserved. Lunar Lander® Is A Trademark Owned By Atari Interactive Inc. FOCAL Emulation Technology ©2009-2012 Code Mystics Inc.|Furniture/Appliance|Atari Interactive Inc.|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:3
75876925-ED3B418E-9442F7CC-216BCB8F|kName|kDesc|Bubbling Water Feature With Flowing Water|A Beautiful Table Top Water Feature With Flowing Water Effect.|Furniture/Appliance|Lockwood|HDK_1.3.6.22.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:2
75E0E98C-F5754D97-ABE8E202-C40C2DE2|kName|kDesc|LOOT™ Firepit|Sometimes The Best Memories Come From Sitting By The Fire With Your Friends.|Furniture/Appliance|© LOOT™|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:4
7604C1B8-BAAD4D17-9895F7C3-CF838177|kName|kDesc|MyGym Apartment - Equipment - Stair Machine|Train On Your Stair Machine To Reach A New Level Of Fitness. Each New Level You Reach Will Earn You Tokens. You Can Spend The Tokens To Get The Rewards In The MyGym Token Store. Each Piece Of MyGym Equipment Trains A Different Sets Of Muscles. Increasing Your Fitness Level On One Machine Will Not Raise It For The Others. Finished Your Training Session For Today? Why Not Practice Your Technique?|Furniture/Appliance|VEEMEE|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:100
763567AD-82294097-8E365B03-49377DA9|kName|kDesc|Active Object - Fortune Cookie|What Will Your Fortune Be?|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.41.0.37.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:15
767FFEFB-2DA54A70-8300B330-0FAD3171|kName|kDesc|Muscial Snow Globe|A Snowglobe Speaker That Plays Some Jazz Holiday Songs. Includes These Tracks: Jingle Bells, What Child Is This? And O Christmas Tree.|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.40.0.265.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:14
76FECEB3-9BA24C1C-921A50E8-8200150B|kName|kDesc|Cactusizer|This Active Item Allows You To Place Up To 20 Cacti Around Your Personal Space.|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:34
77500A41-7BFE47E0-B752FF5C-FA6421CD|kName|kDesc|Herb Garden|This Active Item Allows You To Create A Customized Herb Garden With 5 Plants.|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:18
7795F13E-653A4D34-A4626856-B137F6A8|kName|kDesc|Adventure Arcade Cabinet|Atari 2600's Adventure In Exclusive Arcade Cabinet Form. Adventure® ©2012 Atari Interactive Inc. All Rights Reserved. Adventure® Is A Trademark Owned By Atari Interactive Inc. FOCAL Emulation Technology ©2009-2012 Code Mystics Inc.|Furniture/Appliance|Atari Interactive Inc.|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:3
77B566E0-919A424E-B96E5420-A520D303|kName|kDesc|Extra Large Coffin|Don't Face Eternity Alone – Keep Your Immortal Beloved Close To Your Heart With This Spacious Resting Place Built For Two.|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:20
77F59C67-C102446F-9FD00792-97DBDD58|kName|kDesc|Sinister Sideboard|This Active Item Contains Everything You Need For A Gruesome Halloween Feast! Place Up To 35 Terrifying Ornaments In Any Personal Space For Only 7 Furniture Slots!|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:35
78B1A2AC-76A94C3C-90B85DF3-B2AEA6AA|AmericanPoolName|AmericanPoolDesc|American Pool - Green Table|An American Pool Table, Ideal For Any Apartment. This Table Comes With Both Eight Ball And Nine Ball Versions Of Pool. The Game Can Be Played With Two Players, Or In A Single Player Practice Mode.|Furniture/Appliance|VEEMEE|HDK_1.60.0.450.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:55
7914A13B-7A8945C3-8B3A0D4D-2D394550|kName|kDesc|Stainless Steel Blender|Get Cooking With This Interactive Blender!|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:14
794BEED9-288F444D-9A72B0C0-F1BBAAAA|kName|kDesc|Coral Reef Sofa|Adds An Aquatic Accent To Any Space. This Active Item Attracts Swimming Fish, And Doubles As A Sofa!|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:6
794D5B51-819C4B19-A7D5F643-A127D5D5|kName|kDesc|Lanternfish Castle|Adds An Aquatic Accent To Any Space. This Active Item Releases A School Of Bioluminescent Fish With Customizable Colors. Glows In The Dark!|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:13
79C686CD-42D143E1-B2F4A8A2-F27DCEFB|kName|kDesc|Blueprint: Free Standing Punch Bag|Watch Your Avatar Become A Boxing Pro With This Fantastic Active Item. Watch As Your Avatar Punches And Weaves Their Way Through A Hard Workout. This Item Is Recommended For Use With Blueprint: Home But Can Be Used In Any Personal Space.|Furniture/Appliance|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:11
79CEB34C-09E248C5-8ACCA57C-46D8E983|kName|kDesc|Fickle Flapper Prize 5|Fickle Flapper Prize 5|Furniture/Appliance|Mass Media Games, Inc.|HDK_1.41.0.37.PUB|AUTO-REWARD|Res:2
7A20BE60-36FC4CA0-80715EE4-C13F2487|kName|kDesc|Active Object - Tesla Coil|Harness The Power Of Electricity With This Tesla Coil.|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.41.0.37.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:11
7A4F4B92-9E7E43EC-8E0EEBC0-F7C401FF|kName|kDesc|Rustic Rocking Chair|This Active Item Is A Fully Functional Rocking Chair.|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:17
7B6F12CA-36D147AE-8BA291CE-C63DF877|kName|kDesc|Fearless Records Boombox|Here Are Some Tracks From Fearless Records' New Melodic Rock Act From Tallahassee, Florida! Fans Have Seen GO RADIO On The Warped Tour, And Now You Can Have Their Music In Your Space In Home!|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.52.0.2.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:15
7B9C7F32-22994742-B486D658-B20B0ECC|kName|kDesc|Minotaur Statue - Stone|Elegant Furnishings Fit For A King. Or Queen.|Furniture/Appliance|Lockwood|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|LUA-REWARD|Res:5
7BABA03D-1FD6431D-9B829214-C484780F|kName|kDesc|Smoke Machine (Purple)|Add A Little Atmosphere With This Great Purple Smoke Machine.|Furniture/Appliance|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.52.0.2.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:5
7BC9B661-4CF04635-95474541-84FCD839|kName|kDesc|80s Television|A Decorative Non-functional Ghostbusters™ Prop For PlayStation®Home Personal Spaces.|Furniture/Appliance|© 2009 Columbia Pictures Industries, Inc.|HDK_1.3.6.22.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:2
7BD82CF9-C8314E18-8BEE5F7F-F9D3B8A1|kName|kDesc|Centipede Cocktail Cabinet|Atari's Centipede Arcade Game In Table Top Form. Centipede® ©2012 Atari Interactive Inc. All Rights Reserved. Centipede® Is A Trademark Owned By Atari Interactive Inc. FOCAL Emulation Technology ©2009-2012 Code Mystics Inc.|Furniture/Appliance|Atari Interactive Inc.|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:3
7BE5B1B3-FC0E4F94-8E0DC04A-613CF40D|kName|kDesc|Sackboy™ Play Mat|Sackboy Might Just Be The Best Room Mate You'll Ever Have, He Won't Do The Dishes But He'll Play With You Whenever You Want.|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.55.0.155.BETA2|NOT-RWRD|Res:35
7C206D16-E6834392-8DBE79E2-B3BE403D|kName|kDesc|BoxBeats Minis: Nightclub Edition|Need Even More Club Tunes To Dance The Night Away? BoxBeats Minis: Nightclub Edition Is The Perfect Addition To Any Party Space. NB - There May Be A Delay When You Place The Item Whilst The Music Tracks Download. This Item Has The Same Music Tracks As The Original, But The Object Representing This Item Is 75% Smaller In Physical Size. ※Active Items Provide More Functionality Than Normal Items. You May Only Place Limited Numbers Of The Active Items In Your Apartment Or Clubhouse At Any Time.|Furniture/Appliance|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:23
7C52D91C-AC734547-8F07BEF5-C93DE99A|kName|kDesc|A.I.- B.O.T.|Artificially Impulsive Brain-dead Only-windup Troubadour. Batteries Not Included.|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.52.0.2.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:11
7C532153-05A54A50-A2BAF6A5-EA371098|Darts Item Name|Darts Item Desc|Darts Game With Skull Dartboard|This Fantastic Skull Dartboard Comes With 4 Different Game Types. Play 301, 501, Round The Clock And Killer With Up To 3 Friends. Previously Only Available In The London Pub Apartment, This Dartboard Can Now Be Placed In Any Personal Space - Bullseye!|Furniture/Appliance|VEEMEE|HDK_1.60.0.450.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:38
7DBA8CB3-E91D46DF-AF4EE63D-2E0F6893|ObjectName|ObjectDiscription|Xevious Resurrection™|TM & Ⓒ1982 2009 NAMCO BANDAI Games Inc.|Furniture/Appliance|NBGI|HDK_XX|AUTO-REWARD|Res:3
7DE1079D-AEBB463C-B57719CE-C025F5DD|Stage 2 Receiver|Stage 2 Receiver Description|Stage 2 Receiver|A Non-functioning Hi-Fi Receiver Set Prop.|Furniture/Appliance|© LOOT™|HDK_1.66.0.144.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:2
7E41AF54-E148493F-B60A74B5-B0C5107C|kName|kDesc|Fine Harp|This Active Item Contains 5 Melodic Tracks!|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:11
7E4BAD05-0FEE488C-931A5920-1EBDD820|kName|kDesc|3D Printer|Experience The Latest In Virtual-to-real Technology With The VEEMEE 3D Printer. Place In Your Personal Space And Choose From A Wide Selection Of Exclusive Virtual Items To Print Out For You And Your Friends. VEEMEE 3D Printer Vouchers Can Be Purchased From The Printer Or From The VEEMEE Store.|Furniture/Appliance|VEEMEE|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:75
7E5E8238-A67D4B1A-89BFBB8D-563A2BA7|kName|kDesc|LOOT™ Photo Telescope (White)|This Exclusive Active Item From Your Pals At LOOT Has A Powerful Zoom Lens That Lets You Peer Far And Wide Across Any Personal Space Or Clubhouse… And Take Pictures Of Everything You See! All Pictures Are Saved To The XMB, So You Can Embarrass Your Friends On Your Favorite Social Network!|Furniture/Appliance|© 2011 LOOT™|HDK_1.51.0.60.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:48
7E5E95DB-A8CB453B-802AA5E4-AE870556|AmericanPoolName|AmericanPoolDesc|American Pool - Pink Table|An American Pool Table, Ideal For Any Apartment. This Table Comes With Both Eight Ball And Nine Ball Versions Of Pool. The Game Can Be Played With Two Players, Or In A Single Player Practice Mode.|Furniture/Appliance|VEEMEE|HDK_1.60.0.450.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:55
7E96C18D-38344656-8866AED2-B5F0FD43|kName|kDesc|PSP® (PlayStation®Portable) Go|PSP®go (PSP-N1000)|Furniture/Appliance| Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.3.0.94.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:2
8010C7A9-8A034A37-9EC3A758-7F9874D4|kName|kDesc|Ice Breaker|Keep The Ball Bouncing And Smash All Of The Ice Blocks!|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|AUTO-REWARD|Res:3
801437BC-36324187-87683B89-08E1C843|kName|kDesc|Active Item - Fireworks|Light Up This Bad Boy And Watch It Light Up The Sky!|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.50.0.238.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:26
801EC9F0-AB7945E4-91D7D494-A65514F5|kName|kDesc|Black Tower Speaker|The Black Tower Speaker From The Loot™ Home Entertainment Collection.|Furniture/Appliance|© 2009 Loot™|HDK_1.3.2.16.BETA1|NOT-RWRD|Res:2
808E4ECC-E5844FF2-BF37385A-22BA2D8E|kName|kDesc|Oak Retro Speaker Left|The Left Light Wood Retro Speaker From The Loot™ Home Entertainment Collection.|Furniture/Appliance|© 2009 Loot™|HDK_1.3.2.16.BETA1|NOT-RWRD|Res:2
810D27CE-10DB47F4-B000C54F-3C5809BE|kName|kDesc|Lockwood Auction Machine|Enter Into A Bidding War With A Rival, Increasing Your Bid Token By Token. All The Excitement Of A Real Auction Without Having To Leave LKWD HQ! Please Note, Each Auction Includes A One-off Non-returnable Entry Rate Which Is 10% Of The Starting Bid.|Furniture/Appliance|MakerXX|HDK_1.65.0.139.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:157
81C35CCF-B4294565-A79E5DAE-2DC1C574|kName|kDesc|PartyMachine 2013|This Active Item Will Turn Any Personal Space Into A Party, Complete With Music And A Dancing Disco Ball!|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:29
81F6D20A-99D3468A-99EB01E4-CE2B18FF|kName|kDesc|Sunshine Peep - Heavy Pet - Summer Rain|Let The Sunshine In With With Warm Rays Of Sunshine Peep! Bring Sunshine Peep With You Into Your Apartment And Let The Fun Begin. You Can Control Your Peep With Custom Animations And Special Peep Moves!|Furniture/Appliance|Heavy Water|HDK_1.66.0.144.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:25
83304B6F-84204A51-9CC5A8F7-488A011E|kName|kDesc|NParty Smoke Machine (Green)|This Special Edition NParty Smoke Machine Was Won From Playing The OMG Trap-O-Matic In Aurora. Make Sure You Check Out The Other NParty Items.|Furniture/Appliance|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.60.0.450.BETA|AUTO-REWARD|Res:5
8360E3ED-86404C82-87972EDC-65162E32|kName|kDesc|Animated Disco Rig With Moving Lights|Spectacular Disco Rig With Moving Flashing Lights.|Furniture/Appliance|Lockwood|HDK_1.3.6.22.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:2
836EEA97-46D74483-AE19087A-60BCF789|kName|kDesc|Music Unlimited Flame Box|Get To The PlayStation®Store Now And Try A 30 Day Trial Of Music Unlimited For Free. Music Unlimited Gives You Access To All The Music You Could Ever Want At Home, Online Or On The Go Via Your PlayStation®3, PlayStation®4, Mobile Phone, PlayStation®Vita, PC, Tablet Or Other Sony Connected Devices. Enjoy Millions Of Songs Advert Free And Use Offline Features To Listen To Your Playlists Even When You Have No Internet Connection!|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.82.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:8
83722FA3-339F4A65-958F2313-9DDE8C8B|kName|kDesc|Audi Windows - Trophy Cabinet|Impress Your Friends With Your Audi Windows Trophy Collection.|Furniture/Appliance|AUDI AG|HDK_1.52.0.2.PUB|LUA-REWARD|Res:27
83935CD9-AB0C4A1C-8A9C1513-304D9C12|kName|kDesc|Static Light Projector (Aurora)|Bring Colour And Life To Your Apartment With The Light Projector. Customise The Position And Colour Of Four Different Patterns. ※Active Items Provide More Functionality Than Normal Items. You May Only Place Limited Numbers Of The Active Items In Your Apartment Or Clubhouse At Any Time.|Furniture/Appliance|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|AUTO-REWARD|Res:13
83A63081-D5454471-A838AA9D-6E9D1E2A|kName|kDesc|Lounge Around Hammock|An Advanced Furniture Item Hammock That Lets You Sprawl Out In Various Poses. This Is An Advanced Furniture Item With Added Features And Animations. The Amount Of Items Of This Type That Can Be Placed Is Limited.|Furniture/Appliance|Granzella Inc.|HDK_1.83.0.11.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:115
83D18196-DBB9400F-BC066593-7B18311A|kName|kDesc|Active8: Apartment UFO|Cow Abduction? Does That Really Happen? Well See For Yourself With This Active Furniture Item. Gawp In Wonderment As The Invaders From Mars Fly Around Your Apartment And Ruthlessly Abduct Cows In Front Of Your Very Eyes! Amazing!|Furniture/Appliance|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.41.0.37.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:27
83F627F1-38904B2F-88395441-CF931DAB|kName|kDesc|3D Printer|Experience The Latest In Virtual-to-real Technology With The VEEMEE 3D Printer. Place In Your Personal Space And Choose From A Wide Selection Of Exclusive Virtual Items To Print Out For You And Your Friends. VEEMEE 3D Printer Vouchers Can Be Purchased From The Printer Or From The VEEMEE Store.|Furniture/Appliance|VEEMEE|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:75
8433CBB1-888F44D1-ACADE4C8-322F0F4C|kName|kDesc|Ghost-O-Vision|When Activated, This Active Item Gives You The Power Of Night Vision – Revealing The Hidden Spirits Lurking Within Your Space.|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:21
849291CA-6DE2464B-A4FB6854-93060E3A|kName|kDesc|My Bedroom Girl's Bed|A New, Designer Bed For Girls. Exclusive To The VEEMEE 3D Printer.|Furniture/Appliance|VEEMEE|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|LUA-REWARD|Res:18
84C08C00-1A804548-8D0CC79E-488B27D3|kName|kDesc|Hot Chocolate Machine|This Active Item Will Brew A Perfect Cup Of Cocoa For You To Enjoy With A Custom Drinking Animation. Caution! Beverage May Be Hot.|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:18
84CFEE15-1F724494-B1C18BF8-308C6342|kName|Kdesc|Go Fish Tank|A Fish Tank Populated With All The Fish You Have Caught In Go Fish|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment Europe|HDK_1.60.0.450.BETA|AUTO-REWARD|Res:68
8558C691-6E5A4252-8802D80C-BEE3FD5F|kName|kDesc|40'' LOOT™ Platinum EOD TV - Flatscreen|Discover The Benefits Of Owning Your Very Own Platinum EOD TV That Let's You Watch Full Length Movies, TV Episodes, Live Shows And More With Your Friends In PlayStation®Home! The LOOT™ Entertainment On Demand TV Will Work In Any Private Space Unless The Space Comes With A Video Screen You Cant Turn Off, It Does Not Include Streaming Radio Or Audio-only Content. Now All You Need To Do Is Invite Your Friends Over, Pull Out The Popcorn And Make The Most Important Decision Of All: What Will You Watch First!? PLEASE READ BEFORE YOU PURCHASE: Due To Contractual And Rights Agreements, Some EOD Channels Are Nation Specific. Crackle Content Is ONLY Available In United States, Canada, United Kingdom, And Australia. RadioIO Is ONLY Available In The United States And Canada. In Addition, Due To Rights Issues, Countries May Not Receive The Same Content Selections Within The Channels. Only One TV Can Be Active At A Time. The LOOT™ EOD Will Work In Any Private Space, UNLESS The Space Comes With A Video Screen You Cannot Turn Off.|Furniture/Appliance|© LOOT™|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:42
856BB237-E38E42CA-ADF20E98-9C157A2E|kName|kDesc|50s Diner - Jukebox|Grab Your Gal Or Guy, And Swing To The Latest Sounds With This Jukebox.|Furniture/Appliance|VEEMEE|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:27
85B389D4-B1C04B12-A90662AE-BD40CE18|kName|kDesc|MyGym Apartment - Equipment - Weights Bench|Train On Your Weights Bench To Reach A New Level Of Fitness. Each New Level You Reach Will Earn You Tokens. You Can Spend The Tokens To Get The Rewards In The MyGym Token Store. Each Piece Of MyGym Equipment Trains A Different Sets Of Muscles. Increasing Your Fitness Level On One Machine Will Not Raise It For The Others. Finished Your Training Session For Today? Why Not Practice Your Technique?|Furniture/Appliance|VEEMEE|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:100
85CB8DED-2DF34603-8719C8CC-6FE03CC6|kName|kDesc|Valentine Balloon|This Active Item Fills Your Apartment With Romantic Heart Balloons.|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:16
85CD1D02-18914DEE-99F2237D-CB4F0EB1|kName|kDesc|Boot Kicker In The Arse-O-Matic|Place This Interactable Animated Boot Kicker In The Arse-O-Matic In Your Apartment, And Then Proceed To Kick Yourself Or Your Friends In Their Arse.|Furniture/Appliance|Codename Games|HDK_1.41.0.37.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:11
85EC20BA-FE624BA9-89C0CB37-E395B330|kName|kDesc|Las Vegas Suite Exercise Bike|Jump On This Bike And Tone Those Legs For A Night Of Partying! This Is An Active Item.|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.60.0.451.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:24
862BD812-50F64A4E-BA7CF8E9-1ED8D898|kName|kDesc|3D Printer|Experience The Latest In Virtual-to-real Technology With The VEEMEE 3D Printer. Place In Your Personal Space And Choose From A Wide Selection Of Exclusive Virtual Items To Print Out For You And Your Friends. VEEMEE 3D Printer Vouchers Can Be Purchased From The Printer Or From The VEEMEE Store.|Furniture/Appliance|VEEMEE|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:75
86C3B383-93CE4A1F-AD874272-727AEEA6|kName|kDesc|Essence Of The Emerald Isle|Bring The Essence Of Éire To Any Personal Space! This Active Item Causes Clover Covered Hills To Appear Around Your Personal Space – Also Sets The Mood With Irish Music!|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:17
8725B1E1-52394C4F-9B4A61FA-F5901FD6|kName|kDesc|Intellivision® GAME CONSOLE AND PLASMA TV|This Classic Intellivision® Video Game Console Comes With A Plasma Television For Big-screen Gaming Action At Home! Requires An Intellivision® Game Cartridge To Play.|Furniture/Appliance|Realtime Associates, Inc.|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:3
877FB274-D9F24880-B373C9BF-84866E74|kName|kDesc|Crypt Keeper (Green)|This Crypt Keeper Ensures Your Safety From The Evil Creatures That Lurk Within. However, This Does Not Stop Your Apartment From Filling With An Eerie Green Fog And The Sound Of The Horrific Creatures Imprisoned Within The Crypt Below.|Furniture/Appliance|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.52.0.2.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:6
87E4115D-09FC43DA-BED1E868-4A1A1DB8|kName|kDesc|Personal Chef - Christmas|Get Chef Santa To Bake You Some Tasty Gingerbread. ※ Active Items Provide More Functionality Than Normal Items. You May Only Place Limited Numbers Of The Active Items In Your Apartment Or Clubhouse At Any Time. Exclusive To The VEEMEE 3D Printer.|Furniture/Appliance|VEEMEE|HDK_1.82.0.17.PUB|LUA-REWARD|Res:40
8834BCD5-51664A15-AA764211-E5DB9E97|kName|kDesc|Electric Tube Shocker-O-Matic|Place This Interactable Animated Electric Tube Shocker-O-Matic In Your Apartment, And Then Proceed To Electrocute Yourself Or Your Friends. With Real Electrifying Awesomeness!|Furniture/Appliance|The Odd Gentlemen|HDK_1.41.0.37.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:11
8868DEB2-68EB4319-832FCBE5-1D77E752|kName|kDesc|Goldfish Bowl|This Is The Smallest Of The Aquariums -- And It's Free! It Holds Up To 3 Fish And 3 Decorations. This Is An Animated Active Item.|Furniture/Appliance|Digital Leisure|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|AUTO-REWARD|Res:584
89A7B400-3048492A-9FF9DCB2-BD0185A5|kName|kDesc|Doctor Who - Dalek Emperor Furniture|The Supreme Ruler Of The Dalek Empire. All Must Kneel Before The Emperor! EXTERMINATE! As Featured In Doctor Who: The Eternity Clock Game. Doctor Who Logo © 2013 And TM BBC. Dalek Image © BBC/ Terry Nation 1963. Licensed By BBC WW Ltd.|Furniture/Appliance|BBC Worldwide Limited|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:9
8A123F7A-55154F87-97CE3B30-18DC89F4|kName|kDesc|Personal Dining Experience - 10 Person Table|Entertain Your Friends In The Privacy Of Your Own Personal Space With The VEEMEE Personal Dining Experience. Guests Can Receive Up To 4 Food Reward Items. This Table Has Ten Seats.|Furniture/Appliance|VEEMEE|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:59
8ACB6D3F-67444E3A-9C563F60-0E09878D|kName|kDesc|Piñata|This Active Item Awards Treats If You Can Open It!|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:50
8BE38B10-27524F17-A83A5D69-FEA4B2A4|kName|kDesc|MiniBot Spawner|This Active Item Unleashes MiniBots That Wander Around Your Apartment. Awarded For Reaching Level 39 In MiniBots In Serenity Plaza|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|LUA-REWARD|Res:26
8C34B7A5-B98B4729-B22C1954-B47F94BB|kName|kDesc|Doctor Who - Cyberman Furniture|Outline Resembles The Species Known As Cybermen! You Are Correct. Hostile Elements Will Be Deleted! Upgrade In Progress! Doctor Who Logo © 2013 And TM BBC. Cyberman Image © BBC/Kit Pedler/Gerry Davis 1966. Licensed By BBC WW Ltd.|Furniture/Appliance|BBC Worldwide Limited|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:12
8C35FB24-37484D8E-8D70B4CF-2BF192D9|kName|kDesc|White Christmas 2010|Available ONLY For The 2010 Holiday Season, This Happy Snowman Will Create A Flurry Of Snowflakes Wherever You Place Him. Happy Holidays From Codename Games!|Furniture/Appliance|Codename Games|HDK_1.3.6.22.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:7
8C7CB4DD-715144A4-8BBAC09A-D7DAC964|kName|kDesc|Picnic Basket|Enjoy A Romantic Picnic For Two With This Active Item.|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:25
8DC0CE0B-DBD74AA2-BC8E1557-0572B80F|kName|kDesc|Novus Prime Stereo|This Sleekly-abstract Stereo System Plays Tracks From The Novus Prime Score, Featuring A Blend Of Epic Orchestral Peaks And Intense Space-age Conflict.|Furniture/Appliance|Hellfire Games, Inc.|HDK_1.52.0.2.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:15
8E5B2D78-01624D8C-9DF20CE3-38772254|kName|kDesc|Stainless Steel Hot Pot|Get Cooking With This Interactive Pot!|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:6
8E941A9F-38E54CBC-AEF82384-966B0BDE|kName|kDesc|Luxury Bayfront Condo Bed|Furnish Your Luxury Bayfront Condo With This Bed. Lie Down!|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.60.0.451.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:22
8ED2336E-7A624AF4-AC24DB9C-A5A88C5D|kName|kDesc|LKWD Life Redeeminator|Spend Your LKWD Life Crowns On Fabulous PlayStation®Home Items|Furniture/Appliance|Lockwood|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|LUA-REWARD|Res:65
8F8B97F0-C6D141D0-832640B4-CDF269DD|kName|kDesc|Single Player Solitaire Game #5|Play A Game Of Solitare On This Dark Brown Table With A Glass Centre.|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.41.0.37.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:78
90823C67-BA7E4509-88EDA153-A740FB80|kName|kDesc|Gingerbread House|This Active Item Creates 3 Tasty Gingerbread Men To Roam About Your Space.|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:18
9085E310-16E44E0D-AF9663B2-4C220E76|kName|kDesc|Sheepfold|This Active Item Unleashes Lambs That Wander Around Your Apartment.|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:10
90F4233F-73A14BED-A3575276-0C9BB9C8|kName|kDesc|NDreams Luxury Hot Tub (Gothic)|This Luxurious, Beautifully Sculpted Hot Tub Is Perfect For Your Apartment. Hang Out With Up To Five People And Choose From A Variety Of Coloured Lights To Set The Mood. This Appliance Uses 6 Furniture Slots.|Furniture/Appliance|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:6
911729CB-CC2A4AB9-89AA5AC4-9CE9A5AC|kName|kDesc|GZ Gift|A Terminal To Send A Gift To Someone Special.|Furniture/Appliance|Granzella Inc.|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:426
9154CD05-6E204540-BD262480-DDE4D517|kName|kDesc|Gold Checkers|A Green Toned Checkers Board With Red And White Pieces On A Soft Brown Coloured Table. This Game Is Available For Two Players.|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.60.0.450.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:43
916C79A3-01DA4082-9A7742F7-3E8F540F|kName|kDesc|Stainless Steel Toaster|Get Cooking With This Interactive Toaster!|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:15
91885CAB-ADD048F6-A1B453DF-A653AA64|kName|kDesc|A Day At The Races|The Sport Of Kings. Genuine Imitation Horses Race Around A State Of The Art Electronic Track, While You Bet On Which Two Horses Will Come In First And Second! Start Off With A Coin Or Two To Learn And Eventually You Will Be A Pro, Winning Tons Of Coins From Your Favorite Horse Combinations! Up To 12 Players Can Play At Once. Payoffs Go From 2 For 1 To 200 For 1. It Comes With 300 Coins. Coins Can Also Be Purchased Separately.|Furniture/Appliance|Game Mechanics|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:69
91CD500F-84CC45F0-B7DDA1EC-E631D726|kName|kDesc|MyKitchen - Microwave|For Those Evenings When Cooking Is Just Too Much Of A Hassle, Pop In A Quick And Easy Meal To The Microwave. ※ Active Items Provide More Functionality Than Normal Items. You May Only Place Limited Numbers Of The Active Items In Your Apartment Or Clubhouse At Any Time.|Furniture/Appliance|VEEMEE|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:5
9282B410-11C44739-989E99E5-4A2990B5|kName|kDesc|MiniBot Builder No. 1|This Active Item Allows You To Place Up To 60 MiniBot Furniture Items Around Your Personal Space. Awarded For Reaching Level 21 In MiniBots In Serenity Plaza.|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|LUA-REWARD|Res:70
9324D91F-540447E3-8829C579-14CB7690|kName|kDesc|Ice Clock|This Clock May Be Cold But It Won't Let You Freeze Time. Exclusive To The Winter Holiday Acorn Meadows Park. The Time Is Automatically Set Using The Time On Your PlayStation®3. ※ Active Items Provide More Functionality Than Normal Items. You May Only Place Limited Numbers Of The Active Items In Your Apartment Or Clubhouse At Any Time.|Furniture/Appliance|VEEMEE|HDK_1.82.0.17.PUB|LUA-REWARD|Res:10
937AD2F0-98074FCE-B0DEE5E8-3052833F|kName|kDesc|Executioner Peep - Heavy Pet|This Special Edition Peep Is Here To Commemorate Your Quickness To Be Judge, Jury And Executioner In Your Own Avalon Keep Dungeon.|Furniture/Appliance|Heavy Water|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|LUA-REWARD|Res:29
9382A756-2BCA40D9-AB7C33FA-C779C6FB|kName|kDesc|Hed Kandi Flame Box|Get To The PlayStation®Store Now And Try A 30 Day Trial Of Music Unlimited For Free. Music Unlimited Gives You Access To All The Music You Could Ever Want At Home, Online Or On The Go Via Your PlayStation®3, Mobile Phone, PlayStation®Vita, PC, Tablet Or Other Sony Connected Devices. Enjoy Millions Of Songs Advert Free And Use Offline Features To Listen To Your Playlists Even When You Have No Internet Connection!|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|LUA-REWARD|Res:8
93CF95E1-79174810-B3417FF4-3B471EC7|kName|kDesc|Animated Horse|Bud The Miniature Horse Enjoys Standing Around In PlayStation Home, He's Just Not A Fan Of Carrying People Around.|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.41.0.37.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:11
93D85698-B5224152-B3580998-5D4A26A5|kName|kDesc|MyBedroom - Teak Wood - Bed|An Interactive MyBedroom Bed With Sleeping Animation.|Furniture/Appliance|VEEMEE|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:18
94262BEE-196D4939-987FD7BE-A74199B3|kName|kDesc|Active Object - Animated Cow|A Friendly Pet Cow To Play With.|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.41.0.37.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:22
955C17D6-8A4245E2-AB19EE91-99657955|kName|kDesc|2012 Day Of Judgment Device|The Mayan Calender Ends At December 21, 2012! If You Think That Will Be The End Of The World, Then Our Day Of Judgment Device Is The Perfect Apparatus To Keep An Eye On This Approaching Doomsday. It Might Even Give You A Surprise When The End Is Near!|Furniture/Appliance|Codeglue B.V.|HDK_1.60.0.450.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:24
95CE34A5-8FA24774-A3943807-595CC655|kName|kDesc|Pie In The Face-O-Matic|Place This Interactable Animated Pie In The Face-O-Matic In Your Apartment, And Then Proceed To Pie Yourself Or Your Friends In Their Face.|Furniture/Appliance|Codename Games|HDK_1.41.0.37.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:11
95D19701-5FF14F00-902BCEA0-BEDA38E2|kName|kDesc|Simple Bed|This Active Item Has Room For 2 Avatars With Custom Poses. You Can Also Change The Color And Pattern Of The Bedding.|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:28
96031C25-F680414F-BF038579-914A9857|kName|kDesc|Active Object - Monument Etched Crystal|A Rotating Piece Of Crystal That Alternates In Colour.|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.41.0.37.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:10
96646CD8-C259482E-A976A53B-83A8A12F|kName|kDesc|Elegant Klondike Solitaire|Classic Klondike Solitaire! The Only Way To Get This Game Is To Play It And Win It. You Win A Game And You Are Rewarded With A Copy Of The Game To Take Back And Play Anytime In Your Spaces. Then Invite Your Friends Over To Win Their Copy. This Is Truly Win-win! This Is An Interactive Active Object Item.|Furniture/Appliance|Game Mechanics|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|AUTO-REWARD|Res:69
96B093CE-A6C14404-84380F2A-B58FB679|kName|kDesc|MiniBot Weapon Pad Placer|This Active Item Allows You To Place Up To 50 MiniBot Furniture Items Around Your Personal Space. Awarded For Reaching Level 11 In MiniBots In Serenity Plaza.|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|LUA-REWARD|Res:55
96E47B5D-90CE4AA7-89C2D91A-7383CC20|kName|kDesc|Demonic Ottoman|Even Evil Seeks The Comfort Of Repose. This Is An Animated Active Item.|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:8
9733B2C5-034845E9-8DDD8DCE-782EB3EA|kName|kDesc|BoxBeats Mini: Rock|This Powerful Sound System Comes Jam Packed With Over 10 Rocking Tracks For You And Your Friends To Listen To While You Rock Out. This Active Item Also Allows You To Select Specific Tracks To Play, Set The Volume And Even Randomise The Track List. This Is An Essential Item For Your Apartment. This Item Has The Same Music Tracks As The Original, But The Object Representing This Item Is 75% Smaller In Physical Size. NB - There May Be A Delay When You Place The Item Whilst The Music Tracks Download.|Furniture/Appliance|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:25
97417F6A-402342E7-85B4D0F2-3281685A|kName|kDesc|Chef's Oven|This Active Item Oven Allows You To Bake Treats For Yourself Or Your Friends! Be Careful You Don't Overcook Them!|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:28
97E0A008-D6EB4888-A9712E2B-00657D9B|kName|kDesc|BoxBeats Mini: Rock 2|This Powerful Sound System Comes Jam Packed With Over 10 Rocking Tracks For You And Your Friends To Listen To While You Rock Out. This Active Item Also Allows You To Select Specific Tracks To Play, Set The Volume And Even Randomise The Track List. This Is An Essential Item For Your Apartment. This Item Has The Same Music Tracks As The Original, But The Object Representing This Item Is 75% Smaller In Physical Size. NB - There May Be A Delay When You Place The Item Whilst The Music Tracks Download.|Furniture/Appliance|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:28
981206ED-429D4D27-8CED9766-07E5A338|kName|kDesc|GROW HOME : Poinsettia|Grow Your Own Plantlife And Show Off Your Green Fingered Skills!|Furniture/Appliance|VEEMEE|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:55
9845218C-E9054762-BCDDEEF5-AE0259BB|kName|kDesc|Intellivision® SHARK! SHARK! Cocktail Table Game|It's Arcade Excitment With The Intellivision® Shark! Shark! Cocktail Table Style Arcade Game- In This Updated Version Of The Classic Game Created Especially For PlayStation®Home, Big Fish Eat Little Fish In This Fun And Challenging Undersea Adventure! Watch Out For The Shark, Lobsters And Poisonous Jellyfish! The Bright, Colorful Game Screen And Exciting Table-top Artwork Will Be A Thrilling Adition To Your Home! Earn The Following Three Exclusive Shark! Shark! Themed Rewards During Gameplay: An Animating T-shirt, Glitzy Game Poster, Gold-plated Trophy, And 6 Foot Themed Mobile.|Furniture/Appliance|Realtime Associates, Inc.|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:3
9855A7CA-AAD84472-A91D53C2-A2B8A647|kName|kDesc|Leaf Green Stand Mixer|Get Cooking With This Interactive Stand Mixer!|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:13
989F10CA-319A4A94-BEE03773-F265360F|kName|kDesc|Time Pilot Arcade Cabinet|Time Pilot Arcade Cabinet ©2012 Konami Digital Entertainment FOCAL Emulation Technology ©2009-2012 Code Mystics Inc.|Furniture/Appliance|Konami Digital Entertainment|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:3
98BD15DB-AF8D48FE-BBBFF68B-82C68FDA|kName|kDesc|Mystic Music Box|Take The Bramblenook Soundtrack Into Any Space!|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:16
9911B91E-EE3040E3-A617F329-FFB6B346|kName|kDesc|Active Item - Plasma Ball|An Electric Plasma Ball.|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.50.0.238.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:8
991F176F-82F64749-91B4E2B3-DD9066BE|kName|kDesc|Personal Roulette Table|Now You Can Treat Your Friends To The Gentleman's Game Of Roulette Right In Your Very Own Space. All You Have To Do Is Place This Active Item Down And You And Your Friends Are In For Endless Fun. The Exact Same Tables From The Paradise Springs Casino Can Now Be Played In The Comfort Of Your Own Home. Bet It All On Black, Or Red, And Challenge Your Friends To See Who Can Win The Most! This Is An Animated Active Item.|Furniture/Appliance|Digital Leisure|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:103
993D2306-D60C41E9-B61CFA31-1A6CE5F1|kName|kDesc|Flower Bed - Rectangle|This Active Item Allows You To Create A Customized Bed Of 15 Plants.|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:18
99857B02-8FBD4A00-81DAC1E4-22CD2037|kName|kDesc|Dragon Rider: Earth|Ride The Strong Earth Dragon Around Your Personal Spaces With Your Friends. The Type Can Hurl An Earth Clod At Frightening Speeds!|Furniture/Appliance|Heavy Water|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:60
99B627B9-C73B46EA-B02821DF-794522C4|kName|kDesc|Table|Table|Furniture/Appliance|EA SPORTS|HDK_1.3.0.130.BETA2|AUTO-REWARD|Res:2
99F5B154-19E843BD-99AB1A05-0D4447BA|kName|kDesc|Hot Tub|You And Three Friends Can Go For A Dip.|Furniture/Appliance|Digital Leisure|HDK_1.66.0.144.PUB|AUTO-REWARD|Res:6
9B2B2A0F-DF694947-B50CD843-CDB64951|kName|kDesc|BoxBeats: Nature|Sit Down, Close Your Eyes And Escape To A World Of Tranquility With BoxBeats: Nature. A Selection Of Nature Inspired Tracks To Help You Relax. NB - There May Be A Delay When You Place The Item Whilst The Music Tracks Download. ※Active Items Provide More Functionality Than Normal Items. You May Only Place Limited Numbers Of The Active Items In Your Apartment Or Clubhouse At Any Time.|Furniture/Appliance|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:27
9B4C4F6C-DC5948DA-B55F880D-FC93A695|kName|kDesc|Lock-a-doodle (Gift Edition)|Lock-a-doodle Is A Fun Social Drawing Game. Create Doodles For Your Friends To Guess, Accept Random Challenges From Other Players, Or Unlock Doodle Mode And Doodle To Your Heart's Content. The More Lock-a-doodle Doodle Packs You Own, The More Stickers, Colours And Shapes At Your Disposal For Creating Incredible Works Of Art! Includes Your First Doodle Pack For FREE!|Furniture/Appliance|Lockwood|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:108
9BCB2DBA-492C42DD-A31A2A7A-ADDBFC97|kName|kDesc|A Display Case For Your Wand|Your Wand Will Be Displayed Here When Not In Use.|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|AUTO-REWARD|Res:10
9C598972-7FE64879-8CCD2AD8-CAFDC01D|kName|kDesc|MyGym Apartment - Equipment - Cross Trainer|Train On Your Cross Trainer Machine To Reach A New Level Of Fitness. Each New Level You Reach Will Earn You Tokens. You Can Spend The Tokens To Get The Rewards In The MyGym Token Store. Each Piece Of MyGym Equipment Trains A Different Sets Of Muscles. Increasing Your Fitness Level On One Machine Will Not Raise It For The Others. Finished Your Training Session For Today? Why Not Practice Your Technique?|Furniture/Appliance|VEEMEE|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:100
9CAFA230-1F184884-B3E2F37F-AC85DCB8|kName|kDesc|Heart Beach Chair|Heart Chair For Laying Down In Various Poses. This Is An Advanced Furniture Item With Added Features And Animations.The Amount Of Items Of This Type That Can Be Placed Is Limited. *A Gift From GZ Gift|Furniture/Appliance|Granzella Inc.|HDK_1.82.0.17.PUB|LUA-REWARD|Res:108
9D372C43-0B294EA5-B90FE820-B49A9CEE|kName|kDesc|Demonic Antiquities Cabinet|Who Knows What Arcane Horrors Are Hidden Within These Delicately Carved Doors? This Is An Animated Active Item.|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:8
9D390D24-1E994C90-AA5343BA-FDD63D67|kName|kDesc|Interactive Bar (Black And White)|You And Up To Three Other Friends Can Sit At Your Very Own Bar And Have Your Fill Of Non-alcoholic Beverages Until The Sun Comes Up. ※Active Items Provide More Functionality Than Normal Items. You May Only Place Limited Numbers Of The Active Items In Your Apartment Or Clubhouse At Any Time.|Furniture/Appliance|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.82.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:16
9D6F183F-30524A3A-9641C7FE-63F0A649|kName|kDesc|Fine Gazebo|This Active Item Attracts Butterflies.|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:9
9D91A201-AD4A40BA-A0A67CE5-B849A0E1|kName|kDesc|Oak Tower Speaker|The Oak Tower Speaker From The Loot™ Home Entertainment Collection.|Furniture/Appliance|© 2009 Loot™|HDK_1.3.2.16.BETA1|NOT-RWRD|Res:2
9DA43A63-F6CF4F76-B4FA7EBB-6F874C5D|kName|kDesc|Fast Draw Showdown Arcade Machine|Give Your Apartment That Retro Feel With This Authentic Fast Draw Showdown Arcade Machine. It's Time For Some Real Fast Draw Action!|Furniture/Appliance|Digital Leisure|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|AUTO-REWARD|Res:4
9DE25E88-72374F2E-AFC22458-AB6B78D4|kName|kDesc|Stockpot|Get Cooking With This Interactive Pot!|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:6
9E441455-5B9444F3-95D3EB43-7DCDA22E|kName|kDesc|Hed Kandi Outdoor Fireworks|Sign Up For The Free 30 Day Trial Of Music Unlimited On The PlayStation®Store To Listen To The Best In Hed Kandi And Much Much More!|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|LUA-REWARD|Res:8
9E52459D-C157412D-BEE419C8-2DCD2992|kName|kDesc|Ultimate Aquarium|This Tank Is The Ultimate In Aquarium Technology. Using The Power Of Nano-technology We Have Created An Aquarium That You Can Resize To Fit Any Room In Your Space. It Comes Bundled With The Finding Fish Pack And The Under The Ocean Decoration Pack. If You're Looking To Renovate Your Apartment With A New Wall Made Of Water And Fish, This Is Your Aquarium. The Fish Included Are: Clownfish, Royal Gramma, Yellow Tang, Moorish Idol And Blue Tang. Decorations Included: Invisible Bubbler, Conch Shell, Sunken Castle, Sea Urchin And Columns. This Is An Animated Active Item.|Furniture/Appliance|Digital Leisure|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:584
9EB843A3-C58049F9-AA90DB33-000B1EEE|kName|kDesc|MyGym - Equipment - Rowing Machine|Train On Your Rowing Machine To Reach A New Level Of Fitness. Each New Level You Reach Will Earn You Tokens. You Can Spend The Tokens To Get The Rewards In The MyGym Token Store. Each Piece Of MyGym Equipment Trains A Different Sets Of Muscles. Increasing Your Fitness Level On One Machine Will Not Raise It For The Others. Finished Your Training Session For Today? Why Not Practice Your Technique?|Furniture/Appliance|VEEMEE|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:100
9F27EB0F-E0AD448F-9041BECD-158FBF1D|kName|kDesc|InFAMOUS Jukebox|The Music Just Got Louder With This Jukebox For Your Apartment Featuring Music From InFAMOUS.|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.3.6.22.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:12
9FBAFEBC-0FBF480D-B827FFBE-89613E4A|kName|kDesc|Rainbow Maker|This Active Item Creates Rainbows In Any Personal Space. Keep An Eye Out For A Pot Of Gold!|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:15
9FD4B4EA-913C4050-9B661BE9-ECBFB5F9|kName|kDesc|Lilith - Brimstone Dancer|According To Legends, Lilith Was Turned Into A Demon For Refusing To Obey So Don't Try To Tame This Wild Animal. Lilith Means belonging To The Night And That's Just When She's At Her Finest.|Furniture/Appliance|Mass Media|HDK_1.50.0.238.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:18
9FFF002D-9CB94284-8CE74DC4-3E152FC2|kName|kDesc|Personal War Table|War, What Is It Good For? It's Good For Placing In Your Own Personal Space Now. This Active Item Will Give You The Same Experience You'll Find At The Paradise Springs Casino. Bet On If You'll Beat The Dealer Or Not. If You Run Out Of Chips Just Hop Back Onto The Seat And You'll Get A Whole New Stack Of Chips. Bring Home The Casino Experience Home With You Today! This Is An Animated Active Item.|Furniture/Appliance|Digital Leisure|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:192
A0A65C71-5CAB441F-9557D38D-C4BF95B1|kName|kDesc|240'' LOOT™ Diamond EOD TV - Flatscreen|The Height Of Luxury: Own Your Very Own Blinged Out Diamond EOD TV That Let's You Watch Full Length Movies, TV Episodes, Live Shows And More With Your Friends In PlayStation®Home! The LOOT™ Entertainment On Demand TV Will Work In Any Private Space Unless The Space Comes With A Video Screen You Cant Turn Off, It Does Not Include Streaming Radio Or Audio-only Content. Now All You Need To Do Is Invite Your Friends Over, Pull Out The Popcorn And Make The Most Important Decision Of All: What Will You Watch First!? PLEASE READ BEFORE YOU PURCHASE: Due To Contractual And Rights Agreements, Some EOD Channels Are Nation Specific. Crackle Content Is ONLY Available In United States, Canada, United Kingdom, And Australia. RadioIO Is ONLY Available In The United States And Canada. In Addition, Due To Rights Issues, Countries May Not Receive The Same Content Selections Within The Channels. Only One TV Can Be Active At A Time. The LOOT™ EOD Will Work In Any Private Space, UNLESS The Space Comes With A Video Screen You Cannot Turn Off.|Furniture/Appliance|© LOOT™|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:42
A0F67350-F1AE4C70-B22024EF-031779EC|Stage 2 Fridge|Stage 2 Fridge Description|Stage 2 Fridge|An Old-fashioned Refrigerator.|Furniture/Appliance|© LOOT™|HDK_1.66.0.144.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:2
A131F551-73FE47E6-AC787094-D3BFE904|kName|kDesc|Timepieces - Traditional Alarm Clock|Always Know What The Time Is With This Working Clock. The Time Is Automatically Set Using The Time On Your PlayStation®3.|Furniture/Appliance|VEEMEE|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:6
A13353B6-B3934D04-8C0131CD-2DD8B978|kName|kDesc|140'' LOOT™ Diamond EOD TV - Flatscreen|The Height Of Luxury: Own Your Very Own Blinged Out Diamond EOD TV That Let's You Watch Full Length Movies, TV Episodes, Live Shows And More With Your Friends In PlayStation®Home! The LOOT™ Entertainment On Demand TV Will Work In Any Private Space Unless The Space Comes With A Video Screen You Cant Turn Off, It Does Not Include Streaming Radio Or Audio-only Content. Now All You Need To Do Is Invite Your Friends Over, Pull Out The Popcorn And Make The Most Important Decision Of All: What Will You Watch First!? PLEASE READ BEFORE YOU PURCHASE: Due To Contractual And Rights Agreements, Some EOD Channels Are Nation Specific. Crackle Content Is ONLY Available In United States, Canada, United Kingdom, And Australia. RadioIO Is ONLY Available In The United States And Canada. In Addition, Due To Rights Issues, Countries May Not Receive The Same Content Selections Within The Channels. Only One TV Can Be Active At A Time. The LOOT™ EOD Will Work In Any Private Space, UNLESS The Space Comes With A Video Screen You Cannot Turn Off.|Furniture/Appliance|© LOOT™|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:42
A2339D03-5CF244C4-A2AC8F37-2E89699D|kName|kDesc|Audi Gecko - Trophy Cabinet|Impress Your Friends With Your Audi Gecko Trophy Collection.|Furniture/Appliance|AUDI AG|HDK_1.52.0.2.PUB|AUTO-REWARD|Res:27
A245EB91-EA9949DB-BC9A002B-0B217CCE|kName|kDesc|BBC Active Camera|Record Videos Straight To Your XMB! Pause And Resume Recording For Sweet In-camera Editing. Feel Like Uploading The Video Straight To YouTube™? Well, Now You Can. Since The BBC Active Camera Will Work In Any Of Your Personal Spaces, The Possibilities Are Endless! So Get Out There And Start Shooting, Machinimators!! BBC Logo © BBC 1996|Furniture/Appliance|BBC Worldwide Limited|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:22
A294A886-F4AD4FB8-A309A8C7-0968FE50|kName|kDesc|Solitaire Card Mini-Game|Play This Game Of Absolute Patience In The Comfort Of Your Own Home.|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment America|HDK_1.3.6.22.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:77
A29BBCCB-3E8546AA-8A31FCD7-E2066302|kName|kDesc|Total Recall - Rekall Chair|This Will Teleport You To Rekall|Furniture/Appliance|VEEMEE|HDK_1.66.0.144.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:17
A2B6876D-6A50480C-BB709965-3EE890A1|kName|kDesc|Demonic Chest|What Demons Lurk Within? This Is An Animated Active Item.|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:8
A2CB3E56-7AC94C4B-8DE462AF-AC7A7203|kName|kDesc|Vampire Gravestone|Awarded To The Community For Recruiting 1,000,000 Vampires In Serenity Plaza.|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|LUA-REWARD|Res:18
A3B06E70-6A68477D-B2459DD0-0E42309E|kName|kDesc|Active Item - Playful Kitten|This Kitten Is Always Ready To Play With A Ball Of Yarn.|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.41.0.37.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:43
A42D02B5-32EE4641-AF0E3599-18654DF0|kName|kDesc|Bakelite Radio|Tune In To Listen To Some Swinging Songs From The Bygone Era.|Furniture/Appliance|MakerXX|HDK_1.82.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:5
A43A23F7-20FA4A0A-8ED0D84C-BE21E9A1|kName|kDesc|Bird's Nest|This Active Item Livens Up Your Apartment With Animated Birds.|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:7
A46A6BFC-21C04B34-90375C37-8A88507A|kName|kDesc|Active Object - Toy Race Track|Relive Your Childhood With This Toy Race Track.|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.41.0.37.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:14
A4B5E362-C7324353-B412BD23-E25C738E|kName|kDesc|Shamrock Table|The Perfect Table For An Irish Feast!|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:7
A4C28874-13614211-B1587F9D-F1140E15|ObjectName|ObjectDescription|Vending Machine|Place This Together With Arcade Cabinets, For An Authentic Arcade Ensemble!|Furniture/Appliance|Ⓒ2009 NBGI|HDK_XX|NOT-RWRD|Res:2
A5105CA3-6B554D62-BFC31D6A-1255A4E2|kName|kDesc|Layla - Brimstone Dancer|Meet Layla, She'll Be Making You Call Out For Your Mummy! Shes Got Moves That Havent Been Seen For Centuries. Sit And Stare While You Beg For A Wardrobe Malfunction.|Furniture/Appliance|Mass Media|HDK_1.50.0.238.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:18
A58E4E18-8FBE4394-BCF3A4BA-E3F92B43|kName|kDesc|3D Printer|Experience The Latest In Virtual-to-real Technology With The VEEMEE 3D Printer. Place In Your Personal Space And Choose From A Wide Selection Of Exclusive Virtual Items To Print Out For You And Your Friends. VEEMEE 3D Printer Vouchers Can Be Purchased From The Printer Or From The VEEMEE Store.|Furniture/Appliance|VEEMEE|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:75
A62C5F66-47E24246-8CE0B6EA-34364293|kName|kDesc|Las Vegas Suite Treadmill 2|Hop On This Treadmill And Get Your Cardio On! This Is An Active Item.|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.60.0.451.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:15
A7D64C11-B9CD4213-A9874B7C-EC43BE45|kName|kDesc|Interactive Bar - Red|You And Up To Three Other Friends Can Sit At Your Very Own Bar And Have Your Fill Of Non-alcoholic Beverages Until The Sun Comes Up. ※Active Items Provide More Functionality Than Normal Items. You May Only Place Limited Numbers Of The Active Items In Your Apartment Or Clubhouse At Any Time.|Furniture/Appliance|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.82.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:16
A7EF5F48-BF8240A0-A741733E-B8345D82|kName|kDesc|Cherry Red Stand Mixer|Get Cooking With This Interactive Stand Mixer!|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:13
A87233F0-97314303-95528B49-24E7570E|kName|kDesc|Chicken Coop|This Active Item Unleashes Chicks That Wander Around Your Apartment.|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:12
A8733FCD-CF4446FD-90A98831-81C5E6BA|kName|kDesc|MiniBots: Battlebox|Design And Control A Custom MiniBot In This Fast-paced Third Person Shooter. Fight To Survive Against Waves Of Foes. Anyone Can Play Battlebox And Complete Achievements To Unlock Unique Rewards!|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.65.0.139.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:177
A8CFCD72-E2174D25-AB0811CC-85BBB3D2|kName|kDesc|Lounge Around Hammock|An Advanced Furniture Item Hammock That Lets You Sprawl Out In Various Poses. This Is An Advanced Furniture Item With Added Features And Animations. The Amount Of Items Of This Type That Can Be Placed Is Limited.|Furniture/Appliance|Granzella Inc.|HDK_1.83.0.11.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:115
A922D19A-71E44F87-9A648FC3-667D303A|kName|kDesc|60'' LOOT™ Platinum EOD TV - Flatscreen|Discover The Benefits Of Owning Your Very Own Platinum EOD TV That Let's You Watch Full Length Movies, TV Episodes, Live Shows And More With Your Friends In PlayStation®Home! The LOOT™ Entertainment On Demand TV Will Work In Any Private Space Unless The Space Comes With A Video Screen You Cant Turn Off, It Does Not Include Streaming Radio Or Audio-only Content. Now All You Need To Do Is Invite Your Friends Over, Pull Out The Popcorn And Make The Most Important Decision Of All: What Will You Watch First!? PLEASE READ BEFORE YOU PURCHASE: Due To Contractual And Rights Agreements, Some EOD Channels Are Nation Specific. Crackle Content Is ONLY Available In United States, Canada, United Kingdom, And Australia. RadioIO Is ONLY Available In The United States And Canada. In Addition, Due To Rights Issues, Countries May Not Receive The Same Content Selections Within The Channels. Only One TV Can Be Active At A Time. The LOOT™ EOD Will Work In Any Private Space, UNLESS The Space Comes With A Video Screen You Cannot Turn Off.|Furniture/Appliance|© LOOT™|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:42
A936E65E-DCBD410F-9AE52336-A832F1DF|kName|kDesc|Smoke Machine (White)|Add A Little Atmosphere With This Great White Smoke Machine.|Furniture/Appliance|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.52.0.2.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:5
A96AA65F-1B2D4FFA-98EB098D-3EB25DCE|kName|kDesc|80'' LOOT™ EOD TV - Flatscreen|PLEASE READ BEFORE YOU PURCHASE: Due To Contractual And Rights Agreements, Some EOD Channels Are Nation Specific. Crackle Content Is ONLY Available In United States, Canada, United Kingdom, And Australia. RadioIO Is ONLY Available In The United States And Canada. In Addition, Due To Rights Issues, Countries May Not Receive The Same Content Selections Within The Channels. Only One TV Can Be Active At A Time. The LOOT EOD Will Work In Any Private Space, UNLESS The Space Comes With A Video Screen You Cannot Turn Off. Watch Full Length Movies, TV Episodes, Live Shows And More With Your Friends In PlayStation®Home! The LOOT™ Entertainment On Demand TV Will Work In Any Private Space Unless The Space Comes With A Video Screen You Cant Turn Off, It Does Not Include Streaming Radio Or Audio-only Content. Now All You Need To Do Is Invite Your Friends Over, Pull Out The Popcorn And Make The Most Important Decision Of All: What Will You Watch First!?|Furniture/Appliance|© LOOT™|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:42
A9819222-40BF45EB-8CC08400-9797580A|kName|kDesc|Saucepot|Get Cooking With This Interactive Pot!|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:6
A9A8EF97-8D3F4C3C-B46C29A7-35C30AE7|kName|kDesc|Spunland Flower|An Interactive Spunland Flower For Your Apartment. Dances When Given Attention.|Furniture/Appliance|Madmunki|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:28
A9B8FF69-877547EC-A5D8F594-DC1F136F|kName|kDesc|Active Item - Golden Retriever|A Playful Looking Pup.|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.41.0.37.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:26
A9D6B4C3-F1264D87-AF01DFBB-EBC0FEBD|kName|kDesc|Cutthroats: Battle For Black Powder Cove Music Player|This Is The Exclusive Music Player From Cutthroats: Battle For Black Powder Cove.|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.60.0.450.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:11
A9EA8333-846E4EFD-83F8FF68-F8858F5C|kName|kDesc|White Retro Speaker Right|The Right White Retro Speaker From The Loot™ Home Entertainment Collection.|Furniture/Appliance|© 2009 Loot™|HDK_1.3.2.16.BETA1|NOT-RWRD|Res:2
A9EB3B53-96114F9D-B2586556-5BE52CFE|kName|kDesc|LOOT™ Hifi|Fill The Air With Music! A Must Have For Any Private Or Clubhouse Space - Invite Your Friends Over And Get The Party Started! Enjoy Endless Streams Featuring Pop, Rock, Dance, And Talk. The LOOT™ Radio Delivers Real Music To The Comfort Of Your PlayStation®Home Personal Space! PLEASE READ BEFORE YOU PURCHASE Due To Contractual And Rights Agreements, Some Channels Are Nation Specific. RadioIO Is Only Available In The United States And Canada. In Addition, Due To Rights Issues, Countries May Not Receive The Same Content Selections Within The Channels. Only One Radio Or Television Can Be Active At A Time. The LOOT Radio Will Work In Any Private Space, UNLESS The Space Comes With A Tv Or Radio You Cannot Turn Off.|Furniture/Appliance|© LOOT™|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:44
AA7843EE-E3D14A83-9EDC8B8F-55DE7FFA|kName|kDesc|Centipede Cabaret Cabinet|Atari's Centipede Arcade Game In Compact Cabaret Cabinet Form. Centipede® ©2012 Atari Interactive Inc. All Rights Reserved. Centipede® Is A Trademark Owned By Atari Interactive Inc. FOCAL Emulation Technology ©2009-2012 Code Mystics Inc.|Furniture/Appliance|Atari Interactive Inc.|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:3
AB03C480-61614F61-9CC426A5-B6BFBA68|kName|kDesc|Phonograph Music Box (with Game)|Square Off In A Battle Of Honor, Wit, And Comedic Violence, Where The Last Man Standing Is The Only True Winner. Take To The Stage In This 2- 6 Player Strategic Duel, From The Award-winning Development Studio The Odd Gentlemen. Pie Your Friends In The Face, Drop A Piano On Them, Or Slap Them With A Giant Over-sized Glove And Much More! Purchasing This Phonograph Will Give You An All Access Pass To Slap Happys Private Tent, Where You Can Square Off Against The Pros With Four High Resolution Stages, Rewards, And Leaderboards. What Are You Waiting For? Its Time To Get Slapped Happy.|Furniture/Appliance|Codename Games|HDK_1.41.0.37.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:7
AB80CFEF-702241D1-A0BC9264-68165849|kName|kDesc|MyKitchen - Microwave - Gloss Black|An Interactive Microwave For Your Kitchen. Exclusive To The VEEMEE 3D Printer. ※ Active Items Provide More Functionality Than Normal Items. You May Only Place Limited Numbers Of The Active Items In Your Apartment Or Clubhouse At Any Time.|Furniture/Appliance|VEEMEE|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|LUA-REWARD|Res:5
ABE25EF7-F2984F3A-95C4FAE6-DE8AE84F|kName|kDesc|Gift Of The Irish|This Active Item Contains A Special Gift For Your And Your Guests.|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:3
AC1166B8-E87D405C-9F0DC3DF-31C4DF71|kName|kDesc|Chic Black Bed|A Mysterious Black Bed That Turns Dreams Into Reality, Whether You Sleep Alone Or With Someone Else.|Furniture/Appliance|Granzella Inc.|HDK_1.82.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:183
ACAF6AFA-BE094696-B70D44FF-C60FEF56|kName|kDesc|Sega Renegade Ops: Preboot - Arcade Cabinet|Play Through 15 Exciting Missions In This Renegade Ops PreBoot Arcade Game.|Furniture/Appliance|VEEMEE|HDK_1.66.0.144.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:3
AD3FB153-328647C4-A6B962CB-EF41ACF7|ObjectName|ObjectDescription|PAC-MAN™|TM & Ⓒ 1980-2009 NAMCO BANDAI Games Inc.|Furniture/Appliance|NBGI|HDK_XX|AUTO-REWARD|Res:3
AD67FB00-D045475E-B4161305-A71BDFD4|kName|kDesc|The LED Ticker - Free Standing|Why Say It When You Can Write It! Choose From A Range Of Great Colours In Which To Display Your Message. Whether It Be A Note To Yourself Or A Friendly Message To Your Friends, Every Apartment Needs The LED Ticker. This Is A Mini Game.|Furniture/Appliance|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.82.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:5
AE89BB27-0DAE4EE6-A4EBAA41-4D19B65A|kName|kDesc|The Nightclub: Lounge Seat|Take A Seat, Sit Back And Relax With A Drink. The Lounge Seat Has An Built-in Animation Where You Can Sip Your Drink. ※Active Items Provide More Functionality Than Normal Items. You May Only Place Limited Numbers Of The Active Items In Your Apartment Or Clubhouse At Any Time.|Furniture/Appliance|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:18
AF366107-DE2246AA-A58C35B7-BFDC0402|kName|kDesc|Luxury 6 Person Bed (Prestige)|You And Up To Five Other Friends Can Relax On This Interactive Bed That Includes High Quality Motion Captured Animations. ※Active Items Provide More Functionality Than Normal Items. You May Only Place Limited Numbers Of The Active Items In Your Apartment Or Clubhouse At Any Time.|Furniture/Appliance|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.82.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:17
AF5E144A-F91A4BF8-B40D6E68-B9466C1D|kName|kDesc|Animated Dog|Brutus The Dog Is A Handful To Care For, Thankfully He Keeps His Mischief To Himself Inside Of His Playpen. This Is An Active Item.|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.41.0.37.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:18
B0E05DB1-DA57462A-92AA476F-8DA42C8E|kName|kDesc|Holiday Music Box (Gold)|This Active Item Plays The Following Songs: 5 Tracks From The Nutcracker|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:15
B133E670-26284A7D-B6E56E53-5B2E40A4|kName|kDesc|KnittingMachine Mint|KnittingMachine|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.60.0.450.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:68
B1A6F0EB-25684E34-91D0B130-8999BAB7|kName|kDesc|Swing Set|Swing Into Spring With This Working Swingset Active Item.|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:20
B204C41C-AF5348D8-8FA46877-E18F79DF|kName|kDesc|3D Printer|Experience The Latest In Virtual-to-real Technology With The VEEMEE 3D Printer. Place In Your Personal Space And Choose From A Wide Selection Of Exclusive Virtual Items To Print Out For You And Your Friends. VEEMEE 3D Printer Vouchers Can Be Purchased From The Printer Or From The VEEMEE Store.|Furniture/Appliance|VEEMEE|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:75
B2174AF9-4D424828-9B2D55E0-7156CD0D|kName|kDesc|Blueprint: Punch-Man|Watch Your Avatar Become A Boxing Pro With This Fantastic Active Item. Watch As Your Avatar Punches And Weaves Their Way Through A Hard Workout. This Item Is Recommended For Use With Blueprint: Home But Can Be Used In Any Personal Space.|Furniture/Appliance|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:11
B2243CCC-F64E4E69-BFA2E1DD-C9F39E18|kName|kDesc|Heavy Strike Cannon|Deploy And Control Your Very Own Personal Artillery Piece! Unleash A Barrage Of Cannonball Fire At Your Friends, Foes, And Furniture With A Heavy Strike Cannon.|Furniture/Appliance|Heavy Water|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:37
B2420855-2CA44520-8D444845-E9E8BDC0|kName|kDesc|Musical Stocking|Listen To Classic Holiday Songs From The Comfort Of Your Own Christmas Stocking. Includes These Pop-style Infused Tracks: Jingle Bells, Deck The Halls And We Wish You A Merry Christmas.|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.3.6.22.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:13
B2887727-618F46CF-8821F7FF-0A5327A8|kName|kDesc|Personal Dining Experience - 4 Person Table|Entertain Your Friends In The Privacy Of Your Own Personal Space With The VEEMEE Personal Dining Experience. Guests Can Receive Up To 4 Food Reward Items. This Table Has Four Seats.|Furniture/Appliance|VEEMEE|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:59
B2CD6B0B-1C8D4233-A8B45689-AFF02A1E|kName|kDesc|Musical Santa With Guitar|The Perfect Holiday Ornament, A Santa Claus With Playable Solo Guitar Music. Includes These Tracks: Joy To The World, Twelve Days Of Christmas And O Come All Ye Faithful.|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.40.0.265.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:13
B3EF142C-17504E22-8FC1DB76-8B56BE49|kName|kDesc|Apartment Pets: Benjis|See Your Apartment Come To Life With These Fantastic Free-roaming Pets. For Best Results, Try Combining Them With The Other Apartment Pets Now Available From NDreams. This Is An Active Item.|Furniture/Appliance|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:17
B449963A-123848CF-AB536253-A0200705|ObjectName|ObjectDescription|TEKKEN 6 - Arcade Cabinet|An Arcade Cabinet That Launches TEKKEN 6. TEKKEN™ 6&Ⓒ1994-2009 NAMCO BANDAI Games Inc.|Furniture/Appliance|NAMCO BANDAI Games Inc.|HDK_1.40.0.265.PUB|AUTO-REWARD|Res:3
B463A613-D6A3494D-985FA4F5-E4AEF63B|kName|kDesc|Lockwood Gift Machine|Give Gifts To Your Friends! Use Lockwood Gift Tokens In The Lockwood Gift Machine To Send Presents. (Active Object)|Furniture/Appliance|Lockwood|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|LUA-REWARD|Res:116
B46C99B2-17A04B58-838398B6-B267446F|kName|kDesc|Vampire Bat Crypt|This Crypt Releases A Swarm Of Monstrously Adorable Vampire Bats That Will Wander Around Your Apartment. Awarded To The Community For Recruiting 750,000 Vampires In Serenity Plaza.|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|LUA-REWARD|Res:17
B4F4E19D-AE74430E-B629B96F-4EBED6F2|kName|kDesc|Boxing Glove In The Chest-O-Matic|Place This Interactable Animated Boxing Glove In The Chest-O-Matic In Your Apartment, And Then Proceed To Punch Yourself Or Your Friends In Their Chest.|Furniture/Appliance|Codename Games|HDK_1.41.0.37.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:11
B503BD62-EA534885-BD15FFCF-64F30DAF|kName|kDesc|Active Item - Mastiff|A Mastiff Is A Great Companion.|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.41.0.37.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:26
B5287E85-AB694462-B91D1915-295651F4|kName|kDesc|Creepy Peep - Heavy Pet - Orphan Orange|Creepy Peep Is A Playful Little Monster Who Wants To Be Your Friend! Bring Him With You Into Your Apartment And Let The Fun Begin. You Can Control Your Peep With Custom Animations And Special Peep Moves!|Furniture/Appliance|Heavy Water|HDK_1.66.0.144.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:25
B5645EEB-E6FA44B1-8ED67E7F-FBAF3F7D|kName|kDesc|Atari 2600 And Television|A Classic '70s TV Set Accompanied By An Atari 2600 And The Adventure Game Cartridge. Adventure® ©2012 Atari Interactive Inc. All Rights Reserved. Adventure® Is A Trademark Owned By Atari Interactive Inc. FOCAL Emulation Technology ©2009-2012 Code Mystics Inc.|Furniture/Appliance|Atari Interactive Inc.|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:3
B5DFAB91-28924C7A-B811CED5-69811431|kName|kDesc|WipEout® 2D|WipEout® 2D: 4 Tracks, 12 Teams. Direct From The PlayStation®Home WipEout Museum Space Comes WipEout 2D, The Top-down Twist On Sony Computer Entertainments All-time Classic Anti-gravity Racer|Furniture/Appliance|MakerXX|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|AUTO-REWARD|Res:3
B627896E-DA514393-A2BB191B-8D261D43|kName|kDesc|Vampire Bat Statue|This Statue Unlocks Master Vampire Mode In The Serenity Plaza Werewolves V. Vampires Game, Increasing Your Vampiric Powers Significantly. Also Awards Free Master Vampire Clothing (Top And Pants – Male And Female) To The Owner!|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:3
B67CD8E3-F30B4A29-899FE6D5-91753BB7|kName|kDesc|2-barrel Slurpee Machine ( LittleBigPlanet 2 )|Small Slurpee Machine - Dispenses LittleBigPlanet 2 Slurpees For Home|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.41.0.37.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:7
B732C542-C00A492B-AA8AD2A3-740F4DE9|kName|kDesc|Sea Captain's Chair|The Perfect Accent To Any Nautical Space. This Controllable Active Item Chair Gives You A Custom Pose For Your Avatar And Swivels!|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:16
B828A865-34E74E52-8AA2CE6D-9D566170|kName|kDesc|240'' LOOT™ Gold EOD TV - Flatscreen|For Gamers Who Have It All, Here Is A Special Edition Gold EOD TV That Let's You Watch Full Length Movies, TV Episodes, Live Shows And More With Your Friends In PlayStation®Home! The LOOT™ Entertainment On Demand TV Will Work In Any Private Space Unless The Space Comes With A Video Screen You Cant Turn Off, It Does Not Include Streaming Radio Or Audio-only Content. Now All You Need To Do Is Invite Your Friends Over, Pull Out The Popcorn And Make The Most Important Decision Of All: What Will You Watch First!? PLEASE READ BEFORE YOU PURCHASE: Due To Contractual And Rights Agreements, Some EOD Channels Are Nation Specific. Crackle Content Is ONLY Available In United States, Canada, United Kingdom, And Australia. RadioIO Is ONLY Available In The United States And Canada. In Addition, Due To Rights Issues, Countries May Not Receive The Same Content Selections Within The Channels. Only One TV Can Be Active At A Time. The LOOT™ EOD Will Work In Any Private Space, UNLESS The Space Comes With A Video Screen You Cannot Turn Off.|Furniture/Appliance|© LOOT™|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:42
B856BC62-F3FC43FE-87C5EB83-117FACBD|kName|kDesc|Scribble Shooter|Do You Have What It Takes To Be The Savior Of The PlayStation®Home Universe? Take Down The Evil Alien Hordes In This Frenzied Shoot 'em Up Arcade Game. (Comes With 10 FREE PlayStation®Home Rewards That Are Unlocked During Gameplay)|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.82.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:3
B88D1AB7-DF5A4FC5-8FE17529-8619A9FA|kName|kDesc|Animated Hamster On Wheel|Watch As Hamfred The Hamster Tries To Shed Some Extra Pounds By Running On His Wheel.|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.41.0.37.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:16
B8B0E26D-0EBD472F-9EF47418-2A5F0218|kName|kDesc|3D Printer|Experience The Latest In Virtual-to-real Technology With The VEEMEE 3D Printer. Place In Your Personal Space And Choose From A Wide Selection Of Exclusive Virtual Items To Print Out For You And Your Friends. VEEMEE 3D Printer Vouchers Can Be Purchased From The Printer Or From The VEEMEE Store.|Furniture/Appliance|VEEMEE|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:75
B9BDE8AC-A96C410F-A9CF0523-72DBCF7D|kName|kDesc|MyGym Apartment - Equipment - Rowing Machine|Train On Your Rowing Machine To Reach A New Level Of Fitness. Each New Level You Reach Will Earn You Tokens. You Can Spend The Tokens To Get The Rewards In The MyGym Token Store. Each Piece Of MyGym Equipment Trains A Different Sets Of Muscles. Increasing Your Fitness Level On One Machine Will Not Raise It For The Others. Finished Your Training Session For Today? Why Not Practice Your Technique?|Furniture/Appliance|VEEMEE|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:100
B9F6FC25-0A474550-B15C68DA-80164E88|kName|kDesc|Dragon's Lair II: Time Warp Arcade Machine|Princess Daphne Has Been Spirited Away To A Wrinkle In Time By The Evil Wizard Mordroc Who Plans To Force Her Into Marriage. Only You, Dirk The Daring Can Save Her.|Furniture/Appliance|Digital Leisure|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|AUTO-REWARD|Res:4
BA4213F2-F6434C55-A881F252-8230919D|kName|kDesc|Prehistoric Valley - T-Rex Crate Bundle|This Crate Is Very Special, It Contains An Inter-dimensional Portal Offering Access To A Lush Prehistoric Valley. Caution - Put Your Fingers Through The Bars At Your Own Peril! Upon Opening This Crate, The Owner Will Receive The Following: • Prehistoric Valley Personal Space • Ferus The T-Rex Companion • LMO - Ferus The T-Rex Mount • LMO - Ferus The T-Rex Jaws.|Furniture/Appliance|Lockwood|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|LUA-REWARD|Res:13
BB187929-7CCC489D-8576D402-6D7A89D8|kName|kDesc|Active Object - Crystal Clock|A Remarkable Piece Of Furniture Able To Actively Tell Time.|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.41.0.37.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:8
BB9CC985-36EC4385-AB4A97E5-A128D80F|kName|kDesc|Active Object - Modern Age Clock|A Remarkable Piece Of Furniture Able To Actively Tell Time.|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.41.0.37.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:7
BC522408-82944D08-BCAFA117-3371FCB6|kName|kDesc|Demonic Inlaid Wood Table|This Table Is Terrifyingly Normal, Or Is It? This Is An Animated Active Item.|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:8
BC548A21-90D044DE-BBF862EB-089E0B1D|kName|kDesc|Las Vegas Suite Bench Press|Pump Some Weights And Get Chiseled Abs With This Bench Press. This Is An Active Item.|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.60.0.451.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:24
BC589BBB-AC5349EE-9781CE67-3D644AFA|kName|kDesc|Confetti Bomb|This Active Item Unleashes A Storm Of Multicolored Confetti. Also Includes A Special New Year's Gift For You And Your Guests – Awarded After December 31, 2012!|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:9
BC90E505-5C4A45DD-845FA811-52D17BB6|kName|kDesc|VEEMEE Wacky Wavy Inflatable Balloon Man|Attract Customers To Your Business, Make A Splash At Your Next Presentation, Keep Grandma Company, Protect Your Crops, Confuse Your Neighbours Or Just Raise The Roof! Exclusive To The VEEMEE 3D Printer.|Furniture/Appliance|VEEMEE|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|LUA-REWARD|Res:6
BD926320-FAF7420C-A9E8F073-A63FE7A9|kName|kDesc|Active Item - Chihuahua|A Tiny Dog To Keep You Company.|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.41.0.37.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:26
BDFCAE28-53B74BF4-A15ABDC9-488FA87E|kName|kDesc|140'' LOOT™ Platinum EOD TV - Flatscreen|Discover The Benefits Of Owning Your Very Own Platinum EOD TV That Let's You Watch Full Length Movies, TV Episodes, Live Shows And More With Your Friends In PlayStation®Home! The LOOT™ Entertainment On Demand TV Will Work In Any Private Space Unless The Space Comes With A Video Screen You Cant Turn Off, It Does Not Include Streaming Radio Or Audio-only Content. Now All You Need To Do Is Invite Your Friends Over, Pull Out The Popcorn And Make The Most Important Decision Of All: What Will You Watch First!? PLEASE READ BEFORE YOU PURCHASE: Due To Contractual And Rights Agreements, Some EOD Channels Are Nation Specific. Crackle Content Is ONLY Available In United States, Canada, United Kingdom, And Australia. RadioIO Is ONLY Available In The United States And Canada. In Addition, Due To Rights Issues, Countries May Not Receive The Same Content Selections Within The Channels. Only One TV Can Be Active At A Time. The LOOT™ EOD Will Work In Any Private Space, UNLESS The Space Comes With A Video Screen You Cannot Turn Off.|Furniture/Appliance|© LOOT™|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:42
BE339091-65284A19-BF98F11D-3DE370BB|kName|kDesc|Tumbleweeds|This Active Item Creates Tumbleweeds That Blow Around Your Personal Space.|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:9
BE69B428-936E41B1-9117FE38-C0795E23|kName|kDesc|Leaf Green Toaster|Get Cooking With This Interactive Toaster!|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:15
BEE3F58B-096C4E7D-BBD3D080-783B12EE|kName|kDesc|Personal Chef - BBQ|Get The Personal Chef To Grill Up Some Tasty Steak! Invite Friends Over To Your Apartment For An Entertaining Evening And Get Your Taste Buds Going With A Selection Of Mouth-watering Barbecued Food. Once Finished You Will Receive The Consumed Item As A Reward. ※ Active Items Provide More Functionality Than Normal Items. You May Only Place Limited Numbers Of The Active Items In Your Apartment Or Clubhouse At Any Time.|Furniture/Appliance|VEEMEE|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:40
BEEF3A20-153740AC-BDF559BE-01FF49F6|kName|kDesc|Tentacle Throne|It's The Seat Of All Evil. This Is An Animated Active Item.|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:6
BF3B368D-F08D4F23-928E46DB-E9F862C7|kName|kDesc|Festive Table|This Active Item Has Seats For Up To 6 Users. Customize The Seat Pattern And Colors!|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:25
C00D9BF3-016E4D93-BC800E8F-D35FCD8E|kName|kDesc|Victoriana Gothic Bed (Active Object)|Black Is Back! Those Misunderstood Souls Amongst Us Will Appreciate This Dark Collection From Delirious Squid.|Furniture/Appliance|Lockwood|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|LUA-REWARD|Res:27
C092EA51-BB354A13-8C879620-30571547|kName|kDesc|Space Crash Arcade Cabinet|You Can Place This Cabinet Anywhere In Your Personal Space Or Club-house: It Contains A Simple 2D Score-chaser Arcade Game. Play This Addictive Infinite Scroller, Where You Have To Avoid Colliding With Obstacles To Travel As Far As Possible, And Beat Your High-score.|Furniture/Appliance|Atom Republic|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:3
C0DE8EE9-95E340FC-86A02FED-8523CF2C|kName|kDesc|PlayStation®3 Lightning Edition|The New PlayStation®3 Model Is Slimmer And Lighter With 250 GB Of HDD Memory. This Is The Limited Lightning Edition That Bundles With FINAL FANTASY XIII.|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.3.5.121.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:2
C0F5B323-931E4B5A-9C3DBE37-527CD66B|kName|kDesc|LOOT™ Searchlight|Its Not A Party Unless The LOOT™ Active Searchlight Is There! Manually Aim The Light, Set It To Automatically Rotate; You Can Even Change The Colour! Check Out The LOOT™ Actives Bundle For An Incredible Deal!|Furniture/Appliance|©LOOT™|HDK_1.66.0.144.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:12
C11E4D77-1D154000-84946D56-D05923B8|kName|kDesc|Spin The Bottle Game|Time To Engage In Some Frivolous Games. This Is An Active Item.|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.65.0.139.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:27
C1F91743-7FAA4C52-8B3CA9C1-AB0DB29D|kName|kDesc|Dragon Rider: Fire|Ride The Fierce Fire Drake Around Your Personal Spaces With Your Friends. Blast Friends With Fire Balls With This Fiery Dragon!|Furniture/Appliance|Heavy Water|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:60
C1F92ACA-AD304213-B6665D5B-FCF2FA34|kName|kDesc|Cabin Boy In Trout Trouble!|Life On The Open Seas Is Grand! Well, Maybe Not For Our Cabin Boy. Help Our Hero In This Side-scrolling Adventure Get Through The Day! Catch The Fish Lil Dickie Throws To Him, Keep Lil Missus From Burning Under The Hot Sun And Whatever You Do, Watch Out For Chairman Meow!! Get To Level 30 And Win A Free Cabin Boy Shirt: Lil Dickie For The Boys, Lil Missus For The Girls! For You Hardcore Gamers Out There, Accumulate 12,000 Points Over Time To Win The Golden Trout Trophy!|Furniture/Appliance|© 2010 LOOT™|HDK_1.3.6.22.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:3
C2179124-FA52445C-AEEC3650-E50EEA24|kName|kDesc|Dragons Lair Arcade Machine|Join Dirk The Daring As He Quest's To Rescue The Princess Daphne From The Evil Dragon Singe.|Furniture/Appliance|Digital Leisure|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|AUTO-REWARD|Res:4
C28BBB0D-50DB4087-8C5E8AA9-E3534ABD|kName|kDesc|Savage Cosmos - Arcade Cabinet|The SS Cosmos Has Been Invaded By Simsomorphs, Can You Survive Long Enough To Escape In Time?|Furniture/Appliance|VEEMEE|HDK_1.52.0.2.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:3
C2ECF34C-1DAC419F-B8BABBD5-3ECD4F42|kName|kDesc|Active Item - Bird With Cage|Listen To The Chirps Of Barry The Bird As He Flies Inside His Cage.|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.41.0.37.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:26
C379F4D9-79C14B6D-BA4FA607-F5A0569F|Grey Workbench|Grey Workbench|Grey Workbench|Grey Workbench|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_XX|NOT-RWRD|Res:2
C493BB2B-34684349-BE56311C-07F4AA55|kName|kDesc|Apartment Android: Keiko|This Friendly Female Android Will Ensure You're Never Alone In Your Apartment! She'll Roam Around, Chat, And Even React To Some Of Your Actions. This Is An Active Item. ※Active Items Provide More Functionality Than Normal Items. You May Only Place Limited Numbers Of The Active Items In Your Apartment Or Clubhouse At Any Time.|Furniture/Appliance|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:21
C4DB6902-601B4D60-A21850EB-034167B5|AmericanPoolName|AmericanPoolDesc|Skull Pool Table|A Skull Pool Table, Ideal For Any Apartment. This Table Comes With Both Eight Ball And Nine Ball Versions Of Pool. The Game Can Be Played With Two Players, Or In A Single Player Practice Mode.|Furniture/Appliance|VEEMEE|HDK_1.60.0.450.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:55
C4DD0741-4AD8481F-B1DC3F0A-65D7C4E6|kName|kDesc|Cascarones|Get Into The Spirit Of Spring With This Active Item That Allows You To Toss Confetti-filled Eggs At Your Friends.|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:25
C5A868B8-DB084F36-9B07F332-A25D3659|kName|kDesc|3D Printer|Experience The Latest In Virtual-to-real Technology With The VEEMEE 3D Printer. Place In Your Personal Space And Choose From A Wide Selection Of Exclusive Virtual Items To Print Out For You And Your Friends. VEEMEE 3D Printer Vouchers Can Be Purchased From The Printer Or From The VEEMEE Store.|Furniture/Appliance|VEEMEE|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|LUA-REWARD|Res:75
C64B1BD5-B1C84F61-91407EBF-AAF3CFF0|kName|kDesc|Werewolf Statue|This Statue Unlocks Alpha Werewolf Mode In The Serenity Plaza Werewolves V. Vampires Game, Increasing Your Wolfish Powers Significantly. Also Awards Free Alpha Werewolf Costume To The Owner! (male And Female - With Custom Animations)|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:3
C666C336-3ED94CA4-AA881A99-602B7E44|kName|kDesc|MyGym - Equipment - Running Machine|Train On Your Running Machine To Reach A New Level Of Fitness. Each New Level You Reach Will Earn You Tokens. You Can Spend The Tokens To Get The Rewards In The MyGym Token Store. Each Piece Of MyGym Equipment Trains A Different Sets Of Muscles. Increasing Your Fitness Level On One Machine Will Not Raise It For The Others. Finished Your Training Session For Today? Why Not Practice Your Technique?|Furniture/Appliance|VEEMEE|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:99
C69DAF52-E02A4835-8B6D4B7B-7C8C1DE0|kName|kDesc|Two Player Checkers Game #3|A Green Toned Checkers Board With Red And White Pieces On A Soft Brown Coloured Table. This Game Is Available For Two Players.|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.41.0.37.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:43
C6D7F102-2211472A-BB306B07-57295BF0|kName|kDesc|Demonic Chest Of Drawers|Some Accursed Object Within These Drawers Compels You... Will You Succumb To The Madness Within? This Is An Animated Active Item.|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:8
C76A1DB7-E3484E4D-90DF89B4-A6781D16|kName|kDesc|Dragon Rider: Garden Variety|Ride This Typical Dragon Around Your Personal Spaces With Your Friends. This Type Can Shoot A Whimsical Ball Of Flowers!|Furniture/Appliance|Heavy Water|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:60
C77B40D4-94D94071-8F0FF23D-73DE3607|kName|kDesc|MyKitchen - Refrigerator|A Refrigerator. ※ Active Items Provide More Functionality Than Normal Items. You May Only Place Limited Numbers Of The Active Items In Your Apartment Or Clubhouse At Any Time.|Furniture/Appliance|VEEMEE|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:6
C7811E1D-FB124FFE-A268C06C-56952DC3|kName|kDesc|Miu Miu Chamber|Arcade Mmc|Furniture/Appliance|O-Two Inc.|HDK_1.65.0.139.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:3
C845BF80-5EB14B80-A519D927-F718D7FE|kName|kDesc|Flower Bed - Square|This Active Item Allows You To Create A Customized Bed Of 9 Plants.|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:18
C868988C-86EC4B2E-813891D3-DCD9B1C6|kName|kDesc|Demonic Reading Chair|Curl Up With Your Favorite Forbidden Tome. This Is An Animated Active Item.|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:8
C903CA81-6E2B4C34-A41A540A-E7DF39F2|kName|kDesc|Gold Chess|A Black And White Chess Board Placed On A Polished Wooden Table. This Game Is Available For Two Players.|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.60.0.450.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:57
C9365896-8974420B-8CFF1FD4-38224715|kName|kDesc|DIY Racer (incl. Yellow Car)|DIY Racer Is A Fun Mini-game That Turns Your Apartment Into An Exciting Race Track! Use Your Existing Furniture Or Our Specially Designed Furniture To Create Jumps, Bridges, And Tunnels To Create The Coolest Track You Can Imagine. Invite Your Friends And Race Against Them On The Track That You Designed! Do Tricks To Unlock Some Cool Stuff! This Mini-game Includes The Burning Yellow RC Car!|Furniture/Appliance|Codeglue B.V.|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:85
C9751B79-C7294E55-B9A301E1-0F64F6CE|kName|kDesc|Turntable|Turntable|Furniture/Appliance|EA SPORTS|HDK_1.3.0.130.BETA2|AUTO-REWARD|Res:2
C979823C-E5BE4360-83B5D2B5-65B0D8C5|kName|kDesc|MyBedroom Girl's Bed - Purple/White|A New, Designer Bed For Girls. This Is An Active Item. ※ Active Items Provide More Functionality Than Normal Items. You May Only Place Limited Numbers Of The Active Items In Your Apartment Or Clubhouse At Any Time.|Furniture/Appliance|VEEMEE|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:18
C984295E-5FB54D9F-B5965563-57E5DF09|kName|kDesc|New PlayStation®3|New PlayStation®3 (CECH-2000A)|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.3.0.94.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:2
C9B176E6-E2FB477E-95213AE4-0383D411|kName|kDesc|Lamp Of The Inferno|This Active Item Will Unleash A Fiery Conflagration That Follows You Throughout Your Apartment.|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|LUA-REWARD|Res:13
CA1D8AF4-7AAC4EDE-8C0E2206-002E96FF|kName|kDesc|Escape Virus Mode: Normal|Escape Virus Mode: Normal Can Be Played In This Arcade Cabinet. You Can Get Home Reward If You Fulfill Certain Conditions.|Furniture/Appliance|O-Two Inc.|HDK_1.60.0.450.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:3
CA94E982-2B6B40CF-A67EB3B5-7DAE20AB|kName|kDesc|LOOT™ Jukebox|Fill The Air With Music! A Must Have For Any Private Or Clubhouse Space - Invite Your Friends Over And Get The Party Started! Enjoy Endless Streams Featuring Pop, Rock, Dance, And Talk. The LOOT™ Radio Delivers Real Music To The Comfort Of Your PlayStation®Home Personal Space! PLEASE READ BEFORE YOU PURCHASE Due To Contractual And Rights Agreements, Some Channels Are Nation Specific. RadioIO Is Only Available In The United States And Canada. In Addition, Due To Rights Issues, Countries May Not Receive The Same Content Selections Within The Channels. Only One Radio Or Television Can Be Active At A Time. The LOOT Radio Will Work In Any Private Space, UNLESS The Space Comes With A Tv Or Radio You Cannot Turn Off.|Furniture/Appliance|© LOOT™|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:44
CA9F7DCA-B794441F-9C976B91-A20B0601|kName|kDesc|Electrokid - Arcade Cabinet|Can You Help Electrokid Overcome The Company And Destroy Their Top Secret Headquarters?|Furniture/Appliance|VEEMEE|HDK_1.52.0.2.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:3
CB220057-595446B9-B297BDA9-51CC30DF|kName|kDesc|BBQ Grill|This Active Item BBQ Allows You To Grill Up Treats For Yourself Or Your Friends! Be Careful You Don't Overcook Them!|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:27
CB257B8D-4F1C476E-A5149179-FA1375A3|kName|kDesc|50s Diner - Cash Register|Make Sure Those Greasers Pay Their Way!|Furniture/Appliance|VEEMEE|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:21
CB357F28-425043E2-8AE99507-C19C9C22|kName|kDesc|Life-Sized Chess Game|With Pieces Almost As Tall As Your Avatar, This Chess Set Is As Decorative As It Is Playable. Go Head-to-head From Across The Room With This Fully Functioning Giant Sized Chessboard And Pieces. Walk Around While The Game Is Going On So You Can View It From Every Angle. This Chess Set Is Designed For Those Who Want The Big Picture. Literally.|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.51.0.60.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:40
CB8EE400-25434793-8FC439AB-0A19591F|kName|kDesc|Grandfather Clock|Elegant Yet Intimidating, A Grandfather Clock Always Demands A Sense Of Respect For Its Classic Appeal.|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.3.6.22.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:9
CC561FEB-326C4F83-85E3DEBF-B49C2C7D|kName|kDesc|MyGym Apartment - Equipment - Cycling Machine|Train On Your Cycling Machine To Reach A New Level Of Fitness. Each New Level You Reach Will Earn You Tokens. You Can Spend The Tokens To Get The Rewards In The MyGym Token Store. Each Piece Of MyGym Equipment Trains A Different Sets Of Muscles. Increasing Your Fitness Level On One Machine Will Not Raise It For The Others. Finished Your Training Session For Today? Why Not Practice Your Technique?|Furniture/Appliance|VEEMEE|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:98
CC9BFACB-19A34182-8DBE4600-15B0F1D4|kName|kDesc|Fine Cupboard|This Active Item Allows You To Place Up To 40 Pieces Of Dinnerware In Any Personal Space.|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:41
CD373E1D-5C9541A5-9AF01218-F9E45DC7|kName|kDesc|The Pearl Diver Mini-Fish Tank Reward|For Those Special Owners Of The Pearl Diver Apartment, Heres A Reward Thats Sure To Be Noticed By Your Guests.|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|LUA-REWARD|Res:16
CDEACBD7-68304207-9C42C887-EFB05636|kName|kDesc|Fred The Drinking Bird|Will He Ever Stop Drinking?|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.83.0.11.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:7
CE48D7F4-57D949B9-A0ACDBE5-87F986F0|kName|kDesc|Forsaken Planet – Zombie (Animated)|Zombies! Run! Wait, Its Just Standing There. Its Okay! It Just Wants To Be Friends. Looking For Even Sweeter Forsaken Planet Deals And In-game Rewards? Check Out The Forsaken Planet Bundles In The LOOT™ Store!|Furniture/Appliance|©LOOT™|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|AUTO-REWARD|Res:6
CF713A13-887D4A93-88D237D9-461C2E76|kName|kDesc|60'' LOOT™ EOD TV - Flatscreen|PLEASE READ BEFORE YOU PURCHASE: Due To Contractual And Rights Agreements, Some EOD Channels Are Nation Specific. Crackle Content Is ONLY Available In United States, Canada, United Kingdom, And Australia. RadioIO Is ONLY Available In The United States And Canada. In Addition, Due To Rights Issues, Countries May Not Receive The Same Content Selections Within The Channels. Only One TV Can Be Active At A Time. The LOOT EOD Will Work In Any Private Space, UNLESS The Space Comes With A Video Screen You Cannot Turn Off. Watch Full Length Movies, TV Episodes, Live Shows And More With Your Friends In PlayStation®Home! The LOOT™ Entertainment On Demand TV Will Work In Any Private Space Unless The Space Comes With A Video Screen You Cant Turn Off, It Does Not Include Streaming Radio Or Audio-only Content. Now All You Need To Do Is Invite Your Friends Over, Pull Out The Popcorn And Make The Most Important Decision Of All: What Will You Watch First!?|Furniture/Appliance|© LOOT™|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:42
D0262779-7CD04763-8599FC6D-98DBB08B|kName|kDesc|MyBedroom Girl's Bed - Gold/Cream|A New, Designer Bed For Girls. This Is An Active Item. ※ Active Items Provide More Functionality Than Normal Items. You May Only Place Limited Numbers Of The Active Items In Your Apartment Or Clubhouse At Any Time.|Furniture/Appliance|VEEMEE|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:18
D0705B8E-29274CDF-B6234D68-8FA48FC8|kName|kDesc|Apartment Android: Lux|This Quirky Female Android Will Ensure You're Never Alone In Your Apartment! She'll Roam Around, Chat, And Even React To Some Of Your Actions. This Is An Active Item. ※Active Items Provide More Functionality Than Normal Items. You May Only Place Limited Numbers Of The Active Items In Your Apartment Or Clubhouse At Any Time.|Furniture/Appliance|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:23
D0B5FBED-87AD4A6A-8D001B00-F10E429B|kName|kDesc|22'' LOOT™ EOD TV - Flatscreen|PLEASE READ BEFORE YOU PURCHASE: Due To Contractual And Rights Agreements, Some EOD Channels Are Nation Specific. Crackle Content Is ONLY Available In United States, Canada, United Kingdom, And Australia. RadioIO Is ONLY Available In The United States And Canada. In Addition, Due To Rights Issues, Countries May Not Receive The Same Content Selections Within The Channels. Only One TV Can Be Active At A Time. The LOOT EOD Will Work In Any Private Space, UNLESS The Space Comes With A Video Screen You Cannot Turn Off. Watch Full Length Movies, TV Episodes, Live Shows And More With Your Friends In PlayStation®Home! The LOOT™ Entertainment On Demand TV Will Work In Any Private Space Unless The Space Comes With A Video Screen You Cant Turn Off, It Does Not Include Streaming Radio Or Audio-only Content. Now All You Need To Do Is Invite Your Friends Over, Pull Out The Popcorn And Make The Most Important Decision Of All: What Will You Watch First!?|Furniture/Appliance|© LOOT™|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:42
D1A2A117-DCB844C7-A7CCFC1A-961B6261|kName|kDesc|NDreams Clocks: Modern|A Beautiful Clock Designed To Place In Your Personal Apartment. Time Is Set According To Your PlayStation®3 Settings. Note - This Is An Appliance.|Furniture/Appliance|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:9
D2196649-0B2D4CE5-BC4145C6-0F2CF8D0|kName|kDesc|Lamp Of The Zephyr|This Active Item Will Release A Horde Of Roaming Wind Djinns.|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.65.0.139.BETA|LUA-REWARD|Res:15
D21E023F-0F804BC5-AD05E9A3-51188B52|Darts Item Name|Darts Item Desc|Darts Game With Chromium Dartboard|This Fantastic Chromium Dartboard Comes With 4 Different Game Types. Play 301, 501, Round The Clock And Killer With Up To 3 Friends. Previously Only Available In The London Pub Apartment, This Dartboard Can Now Be Placed In Any Personal Space - Bullseye!|Furniture/Appliance|VEEMEE|HDK_1.60.0.450.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:38
D237F993-18F24D2F-B2FB2EF4-6A2A6C8E|kName|kDesc|Freestyle Dance Floor|Bring The Party Back To Your Pad With The Freestyle Dance Floor. With Pulsating, Multi-colored Floor And Lights, A Bubble Machine, And An Exclusive Dance Music Mix, You And Your Friends Will Be Dancing The Night Away In The Comfort Of Your Own Personal Space On The Freestyle Dance Floor!|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.60.0.450.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:18
D2D98678-46244DF0-B2164C34-9D1F1389|kName|kDesc|Active Object - Gypsy Fortune Teller|Ask Anything About Your Future, Just Don't Ask To Be Big.|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.41.0.37.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:19
D2DBB34B-68B6408C-BBE1876C-3215605B|EnglishPoolName|EnglishPoolDesc|English Pool|An English Pool Table, Ideal For Your London Pub Or Any Apartment. This Table Comes With Black Ball - The Traditional British Variation Of Pool Played With Red And Yellow Balls. The Game Can Be Played With Two Players, Or In A Single Player Practice Mode.|Furniture/Appliance|VEEMEE|HDK_1.60.0.450.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:43
D30AB0D1-1A0542E2-A9779BDE-7D48CA11|kName|kDesc|TV|Exclusive High-definition TV Taken From The Assassin's Hideout.|Furniture/Appliance|Ubisoft|HDK_1.3.6.22.PUB|LUA-REWARD|Res:2
D38CC6E0-A5EB4A28-A8B62D8C-E24D1EEB|kName|kDesc|BoxBeats: Relax|This Modern Sound System Comes Complete With Over 10 Of The Most Chilled Out And Relaxing Tracks, Perfect For Setting The Right Mood In Your Apartment. This Active Item Also Allows You To Select Specific Tracks To Play, Set The Volume And Even Randomise The Track List. This Is An Essential Item For Your Apartment. NB - There May Be A Delay When You Place The Item Whilst The Music Tracks Download.|Furniture/Appliance|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:25
D394C7F9-2D2742E4-A4D87B3B-BE7FF406|kName|kDesc|40'' LOOT™ Gold EOD TV - Flatscreen|For Gamers Who Have It All, Here Is A Special Edition Gold EOD TV That Let's You Watch Full Length Movies, TV Episodes, Live Shows And More With Your Friends In PlayStation®Home! The LOOT™ Entertainment On Demand TV Will Work In Any Private Space Unless The Space Comes With A Video Screen You Cant Turn Off, It Does Not Include Streaming Radio Or Audio-only Content. Now All You Need To Do Is Invite Your Friends Over, Pull Out The Popcorn And Make The Most Important Decision Of All: What Will You Watch First!? PLEASE READ BEFORE YOU PURCHASE: Due To Contractual And Rights Agreements, Some EOD Channels Are Nation Specific. Crackle Content Is ONLY Available In United States, Canada, United Kingdom, And Australia. RadioIO Is ONLY Available In The United States And Canada. In Addition, Due To Rights Issues, Countries May Not Receive The Same Content Selections Within The Channels. Only One TV Can Be Active At A Time. The LOOT™ EOD Will Work In Any Private Space, UNLESS The Space Comes With A Video Screen You Cannot Turn Off.|Furniture/Appliance|© LOOT™|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:42
D3CAF7E3-95EC4220-8F7ADC60-D0FEC3C5|kName|kDesc|Rustic Bed|This Active Item Has Room For 2 Avatars With Custom Poses. You Can Also Change The Color And Pattern Of The Bedding.|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:26
D5AFA304-F31941AD-81468765-CAAC8D32|kName|kDesc|140'' LOOT™ EOD TV - Wall Mounted|PLEASE READ BEFORE YOU PURCHASE: Due To Contractual And Rights Agreements, Some EOD Channels Are Nation Specific. Crackle Content Is ONLY Available In United States, Canada, United Kingdom, And Australia. RadioIO Is ONLY Available In The United States And Canada. In Addition, Due To Rights Issues, Countries May Not Receive The Same Content Selections Within The Channels. Only One TV Can Be Active At A Time. The LOOT EOD Will Work In Any Private Space, UNLESS The Space Comes With A Video Screen You Cannot Turn Off. Watch Full Length Movies, TV Episodes, Live Shows And More With Your Friends In PlayStation®Home! The LOOT™ Entertainment On Demand TV Will Work In Any Private Space Unless The Space Comes With A Video Screen You Cant Turn Off, It Does Not Include Streaming Radio Or Audio-only Content. This Bundle-exclusive Wall Mounted TV Works With The FREE LOOT™ TV Wall Mount (found In The LOOT™ Store.) Simply Hang The Mount On The Wall Like A Picture Frame Then Hook Your Wall Mounted EOD TV On It. Decorating Has Never Been So Easy!|Furniture/Appliance|© LOOT™|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:42
D619F591-03DE4B60-BC01BF0C-47A609CF|kName|kDesc|Single Player Solitaire Game #1|Play A Game Of Solitaire On This Polished Brown Table.|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.41.0.37.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:78
D6D41F1A-9DE249D5-A08F8492-B5361B03|kName|kDesc|Active Object - Victorian Clock|A Remarkable Piece Of Furniture Able To Actively Tell Time.|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.41.0.37.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:7
D7E4F0B0-C5B04CA6-8BAC885A-929BE52A|kName|kDesc|English Pool Coffee Table|A Coffee Table For Sports Fans Which Also Doubles As A Portal To The Original V Store.|Furniture/Appliance|VEEMEE|HDK_1.3.6.22.PUB|LUA-REWARD|Res:4
D807DDF5-A18B47A5-95936A9B-7C113FA9|kName|kDesc|The Romantisizer|This Active Item Equips You With The Romanticizer And Enables You To Spread The Love... All Over.|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:38
D84FF194-08E541C8-9861BD7E-9DDBD8FC|kName|kDesc|3D Printer|Experience The Latest In Virtual-to-real Technology With The VEEMEE 3D Printer. Place In Your Personal Space And Choose From A Wide Selection Of Exclusive Virtual Items To Print Out For You And Your Friends. VEEMEE 3D Printer Vouchers Can Be Purchased From The Printer Or From The VEEMEE Store.|Furniture/Appliance|VEEMEE|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:75
D8D8462F-BE064A7A-A5C0A5C3-E0514FE7|kName|kDesc|Rainforest Parrot|Reward Item Exclusive To Rainforest Lodge|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.60.0.451.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:7
D8F1DEDE-22374C09-BC42EBF5-2EDA29DF|kName|kDesc|MyBedroom Guy's Bed - Black/Grey|A New, Designer Bed For Guys. This Is An Active Item. ※ Active Items Provide More Functionality Than Normal Items. You May Only Place Limited Numbers Of The Active Items In Your Apartment Or Clubhouse At Any Time.|Furniture/Appliance|VEEMEE|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:18
D9340812-7FCE41D0-A69BF066-6BA76AEA|Red Workbench|Red Workbench|Red Workbench|Red Workbench|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_XX|NOT-RWRD|Res:2
D991797A-40894E0F-8EA4B15E-379CCC74|kName|kDesc|Forsaken Planet – Globe Logo (Active)|Show Off Your Love Of Forsaken Planet™ With This Sweet Trophy! To Retrieve Your Rewards, Create Or Access Your LOOT™ Entertainment Account By Logging In By Using The Forsaken Planet Globe Logo In The LOOT Space Station Hub. All Rewards Are Exclusive To PlayStation®Home Users And Can Only Be Retrieved Inside Home. Purchasing The Following Items From The LOOT™ Store Unlocks Rewards In The Forsaken Planet Game: Companion Unlocks A Hat. The Companions Bundle Unlocks A Character And The Hat. The Turret (Active) Unlocks A Gun. Purchasing The Forsaken Planet Ultimate Bundle Unlocks The Character, The Hat, The Gun And A UFO. All Rewards Unlock Specialized Gameplay Perks Within The Forsaken Planet Videogame!|Furniture/Appliance|© LOOT™|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|AUTO-REWARD|Res:4
DA55A390-0BA04D96-A2030F76-21FBFC11|kName|kDesc|Poltergeist Puzzle Box|Stage Your Own Haunting With This Terrifying Box Of Tricks! Place Possessed Objects Around Your Space And The Mischievous Poltergeist Within This Active Item Will Gleefully Toss Them At Nearby Victims.x|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.65.0.139.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:26
DAFE2ECE-E8D9472E-93678134-CB8B3E82|kName|kDesc|Sunshine Peep - Heavy Pet - Blue Skies|Let The Sunshine In With Warm Rays Of Sunshine Peep! Bring Sunshine Peep With You Into Your Apartment And Let The Fun Begin. You Can Control Your Peep With Custom Animations And Special Peep Moves!|Furniture/Appliance|Heavy Water|HDK_1.66.0.144.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:25
DB118089-86754ED3-9AF84294-712DE98B|kName|kDesc|Musical New Year's Ball|A Great Way To Listen To Some Music As You Await The New Year. Includes This Track: Auld Lang Syne.|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.40.0.265.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:11
DB64A98C-6EA54BA5-8FE8962A-9B6CD8DF|kName|kDesc|Witch's Cauldron|Double Double Toil And Trouble: Fire Burn And Cauldron Bubble! Brew Up Some Trouble With This Active Item Cauldron.|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:11
DBB66608-C6FD437E-8D1545D2-2E778141|kName|kDesc|Demonic Candelabra|The Oppressive Darkness Weighs On You... Not Even This Finely-wrought Candelabra Can Save You Now. This Is An Animated Active Item.|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:10
DC19650B-B854438C-B5969675-055545BD|kName|kDesc|MyGym - Equipment - Cycling Machine|Train On Your Cycling Machine To Reach A New Level Of Fitness. Each New Level You Reach Will Earn You Tokens. You Can Spend The Tokens To Get The Rewards In The MyGym Token Store. Each Piece Of MyGym Equipment Trains A Different Sets Of Muscles. Increasing Your Fitness Level On One Machine Will Not Raise It For The Others. Finished Your Training Session For Today? Why Not Practice Your Technique?|Furniture/Appliance|VEEMEE|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:98
DC67B1FC-3C4D4D45-BB9121CF-260D6159|kName|kDesc|Personal Big Six Wheel|The Big Six Wheel Can Now Spin In Your Own Space With This Personal Table. You Can Now Recreate The Exciting Big Six Experience For You And Your Friends Just By Placing Down This Active Item. The Experience Is Exactly The Same As To What You'll Find When You Go To The Paradise Springs Casino, So You Know You're Getting The Best. Make Your Personal Space The Gaming Hot Spot For Your Friends With This Unlimited Big Six Wheel Experience. This Is An Animated Active Item.|Furniture/Appliance|Digital Leisure|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:76
DE4512B7-AAF14EB8-B9147F1E-12CC4152|kName|kDesc|Essence Of The Seven Winds|This Lamp Gifts Your Avatar With The Awesome Power Of Flight.|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:33
DE99D5D1-A4D04C92-9FCA0856-3BD29892|kName|kDesc|Timepieces - Traditional Grandfather Clock|Always Know What The Time Is With This Working Clock. The Time Is Automatically Set Using The Time On Your PlayStation®3.|Furniture/Appliance|VEEMEE|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:8
DED86367-CA394589-90DC5589-DF737A36|kName|kDesc|Active Item - Globe Of City Lights|Watch The Ethereal Beauty Of The World's City Lights On Display.|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.50.0.238.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:2
DEDE9C74-266E49EA-80774B3A-DFBC879A|kName|kDesc|1950s Wireless Radio|This Classic 1950's Design Wireless Will Look Amazing In Your Apartment, And It Also Plays Music From The Sound Track Of Killer Plants From Outer Space.|Furniture/Appliance|FluffyLogic Development Ltd.|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:5
DFADECDF-A0424BF6-972C0E7A-EB718C53|kName|kDesc|Egg Hunt|The Perfect Activity For A Spring Day. This Active Item Allows You To Hide Eggs Around Any Personal Space And Challenge Your Friends To An Egg Hunt!|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:45
E0A0CC8B-7EB74EBA-982122DC-5A7AE680|kName|kDesc|Chim Peep - Heavy Pet - Black On Black|More Fun Than A Barrel Of Monkeys Is Chim Peep! Dressed To The Nines In His Monkey Suit, Bring Him Into Your Apartment And Get Down To Business! You Can Control Him With Custom Animations And Special Peep Moves!|Furniture/Appliance|Heavy Water|HDK_1.66.0.144.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:25
E117152A-795249C5-B69EC7CF-578857D8|kName|kDesc|Brimstone Poker Table|A Devilishly Fun Poker Table.|Furniture/Appliance|Mass Media|HDK_1.3.6.22.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:160
E169AEB5-C19741F5-88F991C9-ABC33405|kName|kDesc|Aurora Teleport|Once Activated, This Brilliant Piece Of Technology Will Allow You To Teleport Straight To Aurora!|Furniture/Appliance|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|AUTO-REWARD|Res:9
E1896FD8-25D447EB-8DF6C7AD-6209B44D|kName|kDesc|Haunted Organ|This Active Item Organ Plays 5 Spooky Songs – But Who's Playing It?!|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:15
E1E0995B-57C54967-AB56BE33-A6262B48|kName|kDesc|Musical Valentine's Heart Shaped Box|Let That Special Someone Show How Much You Care. Includes These Tracks: I Only Have Eyes For You And Feel Like Makin' Love.|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.40.0.265.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:12
E25A68E7-135F4AD5-805D9DE3-DE691465|kName|kDesc|DIY Racer (incl. Cardboard Car)|DIY Racer Is A Fun Mini-game That Turns Your Apartment Into An Exciting Race Track! Use Your Existing Furniture Or Our Specially Designed Furniture To Create Jumps, Bridges, And Tunnels To Create The Coolest Track You Can Imagine. Invite Your Friends And Race Against Them On The Track That You Designed! Do Tricks To Unlock Some Cool Stuff! This Mini-game Includes The Cardboard RC Car!|Furniture/Appliance|Codeglue B.V.|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:85
E25D60B8-D5FA4770-A2F32B2A-A736849B|kName|kDesc|Interactive Bar - Blue|You And Up To Three Other Friends Can Sit At Your Very Own Bar And Have Your Fill Of Non-alcoholic Beverages Until The Sun Comes Up. ※Active Items Provide More Functionality Than Normal Items. You May Only Place Limited Numbers Of The Active Items In Your Apartment Or Clubhouse At Any Time.|Furniture/Appliance|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.82.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:16
E278013F-67444757-BB478237-1F178C8D|kName|kDesc|Single Player Solitaire Game #3|Play A Game Of Solitare On This Contemporary Mahogany Table.|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.41.0.37.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:78
E28F0284-DE254BF5-9FE431F9-1BF2C17A|kName|kDesc|Luxury 6 Person Bed (Arabian Royalty)|You And Up To Five Other Friends Can Relax On This Interactive Bed That Includes High Quality Motion Captured Animations. ※Active Items Provide More Functionality Than Normal Items. You May Only Place Limited Numbers Of The Active Items In Your Apartment Or Clubhouse At Any Time.|Furniture/Appliance|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.82.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:17
E293F8FB-E11A47AC-B476BBC5-78FC148F|kName|kDesc|The LED Ticker - Wall Mounted|Why Say It When You Can Write It! Choose From A Range Of Great Colours In Which To Display Your Message. Whether It Be A Note To Yourself Or A Friendly Message To Your Friends, Every Apartment Needs The LED Ticker. This Is A Mini Game.|Furniture/Appliance|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.82.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:5
E329FFFB-FDFB4C6F-AC55368D-33CDF75B|kName|kDesc|Lock-a-doodle Display Easel (Gift Edition)|Show Off All Your Doodles As A Slideshow, Or Select Your Favourite One And Put It On Display For All Your Friends To See.|Furniture/Appliance|Lockwood|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:52
E34441F8-E93540CF-B9BA5633-4D142B70|kName|kDesc|Lil' Snow Peep - Heavy Pet - Powder Pink|Lil' Snow Peep Has Lost Her Sheep And Needs A Friend To Guide Her. Bring Her With You Into Your Apartment And Let The Fun Begin. You Can Control Your Peep With Custom Animations And Special Peep Moves!|Furniture/Appliance|Heavy Water|HDK_1.66.0.144.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:25
E3617AC6-246A4B07-B5C4F1FE-B1CE03D3|kName|kDesc|Small Aquarium|This Tank Is The Easiest Way To Start Your Fish Collection. It's Very Economical And Holds Up To 10 Small Fish And 5 Small Decorations. To Get Your Tank Started, Included With This Purchase Is The Small Fish Pack. The Fish Included Are: Coral Beauty Angelfish, Fire Fish, Flame Angelfish, Serpae Tetra, And Catalina Goby. This Is An Animated Active Item.|Furniture/Appliance|Digital Leisure|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:584
E39A7ED6-32BC4121-B4BEC9AD-8F9D447F|kName|kDesc|Scary Fairy Peep - Heavy Pet - Rotten Redhead|Scary Fairy Is One Twisted Sister Peep! Bring Sweetie Pie With You Into Your Apartment And Let The Fun Begin. Control Her With Custom Animations And Special Peep Moves!|Furniture/Appliance|Heavy Water|HDK_1.66.0.144.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:25
E41FCDCB-71FE4B80-8A5A5A94-617BACD9|kName|kDesc|My Bedroom Guy's Bed|A New, Designer Bed For Guys. Exclusive To The VEEMEE 3D Printer.|Furniture/Appliance|VEEMEE|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|LUA-REWARD|Res:18
E42B24EB-81E7439C-879699B4-5300D7EF|kName|kDesc|Apartment Pets: Nippers|See Your Apartment Come To Life With These Fantastic Free-roaming Pets. For Best Results, Try Combining Them With The Other Apartment Pets Now Available From NDreams. This Is An Active Item.|Furniture/Appliance|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:17
E47AB321-DD1D4440-906ABE51-45C16D37|kName|kDesc|LOOT™ Boombox|Fill The Air With Music! A Must Have For Any Private Or Clubhouse Space - Invite Your Friends Over And Get The Party Started! Enjoy Endless Streams Featuring Pop, Rock, Dance, And Talk. The LOOT™ Radio Delivers Real Music To The Comfort Of Your PlayStation®Home Personal Space! PLEASE READ BEFORE YOU PURCHASE Due To Contractual And Rights Agreements, Some Channels Are Nation Specific. RadioIO Is Only Available In The United States And Canada. In Addition, Due To Rights Issues, Countries May Not Receive The Same Content Selections Within The Channels. Only One Radio Or Television Can Be Active At A Time. The LOOT Radio Will Work In Any Private Space, UNLESS The Space Comes With A Tv Or Radio You Cannot Turn Off.|Furniture/Appliance|© LOOT™|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:44
E50C6911-3D4145AD-A0D00D7A-0986FC99|kName|kDesc|3D Printer|Experience The Latest In Virtual-to-real Technology With The VEEMEE 3D Printer. Place In Your Personal Space And Choose From A Wide Selection Of Exclusive Virtual Items To Print Out For You And Your Friends. VEEMEE 3D Printer Vouchers Can Be Purchased From The Printer Or From The VEEMEE Store.|Furniture/Appliance|VEEMEE|HDK_1.83.0.11.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:156
E5797319-BFD14BF1-AD04A203-3B9D5B3B|kName|kDesc|Musical St. Patrick's Pot O'Gold|Songs For St. Patrick's Day And All Year Round Including Three Traditional Celtic Tracks.|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.60.0.450.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:13
E5C2210E-E49A4D1D-8759679F-9E18CA21|kName|kDesc|Moon Forest Luxury Bed|Normally Youd Sleep On The Floor When You Go Camping. But This Isnt Regular Camping; This Is Camping On A Classier Level.|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.55.0.155.BETA2|NOT-RWRD|Res:19
E73E9D7F-CC3A4C04-B4262E1C-0A2CBB09|kName|kDesc|Crypt Keeper (Red)|This Crypt Keeper Ensures Your Safety From The Evil Creatures That Lurk Within. However, This Does Not Stop Your Apartment From Filling With An Eerie Red Fog And The Sound Of The Horrific Creatures Imprisoned Within The Crypt Below.|Furniture/Appliance|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.52.0.2.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:6
E776D9A9-C11741EB-A47A3094-C7567E9D|kName|kDesc|Toaster|A Toaster. It Is A Reward From The SeaClyff Retreat Personal Space.|Furniture/Appliance|Game Mechanics|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|AUTO-REWARD|Res:2
E82BDECC-9A284093-9A8D7010-7F387996|kName|kDesc|Abduct Earth|This Is An Arcade Cabinet Where You Can Play Abduct Earth. There Are 5 Stages In Total. You Can Get Home Reward If You Fulfill Certain Conditions.|Furniture/Appliance|O-Two Inc.|HDK_1.60.0.450.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:3
E889C62A-1C7943CD-8910D48D-5EF2FE15|kName|kDesc|Super Cobra Arcade Cabinet|Super Cobra Arcade Cabinet ©2013 Konami Digital Entertainment FOCAL Emulation Technology ©2009-2013 Code Mystics Inc.|Furniture/Appliance|Konami Digital Entertainment|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:3
E8B24919-E7154EA5-A440B169-3AB5F77B|kName|kDesc|Ballerina Music Box|Ever Wanted One Of These As A Kid? Well Now You Can.|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.3.6.22.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:9
E8E25085-06EF4DBF-A4A85A9E-A62FBB3E|kName|kDesc|Flower Bed - Round|This Active Item Allows You To Create A Customized Bed Of 4 Plants.|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:18
E956B160-A88B4318-8AB2A544-19F7599C|kName|kDesc|Home Tycoon Record Player|Listen To The Home Tycoon Soundtrack From The Privacy Of Your Personal Space With The Home Tycoon Record Player. Comes With A Radio For Your Vehicles In Home Tycoon!|Furniture/Appliance|Hellfire Games, Inc.|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:12
E99EB7CB-D09640CD-B167E15B-069DC058|Refrigerator Name|Refrigerator Desc|TORO Refrigerator|A Must-have For This Series. A Great Thing To Have!|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.3.6.22.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:2
EA41A8C7-1DB84BF3-A12CD7DF-8C29F6B4|kName|kDesc|Luxury 6 Person Bed (Leopard)|You And Up To Five Other Friends Can Relax On This Interactive Bed That Includes High Quality Motion Captured Animations. ※Active Items Provide More Functionality Than Normal Items. You May Only Place Limited Numbers Of The Active Items In Your Apartment Or Clubhouse At Any Time.|Furniture/Appliance|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.82.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:17
EA4F7812-A0EA4D11-8CAAD6CD-DF636FC3|kName|kDesc|Small Alien Plant|Part Of The MiniBot Alien Terrain Pack.|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|LUA-REWARD|Res:6
EADD228A-E81B46FE-A18FB9A0-36D73483|kName|kDesc|Drop Science The G's Boom Box (Active Item)|Fresh Beats With Some Drop Science Style.|Furniture/Appliance|Lockwood|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:10
EAE036A3-3BC844B1-A2511D69-9B9698DA|kName|kDesc|Yie Ar Kung Fu Arcade Cabinet|Yie Ar Kung Fu Arcade Cabinet ©2013 Konami Digital Entertainment FOCAL Emulation Technology ©2009-2013 Code Mystics Inc.|Furniture/Appliance|Konami Digital Entertainment|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:3
EB2F8F6E-75A84D01-85A58491-D6CB7406|kName|kDesc|The Shimmer Sphere|This Fantastic Active Item Will Have All Of Your Friends Begging For An Invite To Your Party. Marvel At The Ever Changing Neon Flooring, Boogie Around The Dance Pole And Be In Awe Of The Animated Disco Ball That Sends Specks Of Psychedelic Light All Around Your Apartment.|Furniture/Appliance|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.65.0.139.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:5
EB51193C-2FE74F71-9EBDD666-1CE6D50B|kName|kDesc|Cherry Red Toaster|Get Cooking With This Interactive Toaster!|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:15
EB77EC45-721F46F6-80848CCA-76EF4F68|kName|kDesc|Timepieces - Art Deco Table Clock|Always Know What The Time Is With This Working Clock. The Time Is Automatically Set Using The Time On Your PlayStation®3.|Furniture/Appliance|VEEMEE|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:6
EBFF4875-81354007-B02F1462-739FD0F6|kName|kDesc|Active Object - Golden Orrery|Keep Track Of The Planets With This Shiny Golden Orrery.|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.41.0.37.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:18
EC47F58B-89834067-BFB155BC-427063A6|kName|kDesc|Customizable Christmas Tree|This Active Item Lets You Design A Christmas Tree To Compliment Your Space. Includes A Variety Of Decorations, Toppers And Custom Colors.|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:33
ECCC63B3-CACC44C6-AE9DCDF4-6BC2BF34|kName|kDesc|Espionage 9: Apartment Arcade Cabinet|This Classic NDreams Game Is Now Available As An Attractive Apartment Arcade Cabinet. Purchasing This Mini Game Will Allow You To Play As Many Games As You Want Without The Need For Espionage 9 Tickets. Also, There Are Lots Of Classic Espionage 9 Rewards To Be Won From Completing Challenges.|Furniture/Appliance|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:40
ECEB0181-D80248C7-976F84EE-042239F6|kName|kDesc|Super Powered Peep - Heavy Pet - Bolting Blue|Super Powered Peep Is Fueled By Heavy Water For All Of His Mad Skills! Bring Him With You Into Your Apartment And Let The Fun Begin. You Can Control Your Peep With Custom Animations And Special Peep Moves!|Furniture/Appliance|Heavy Water|HDK_1.66.0.144.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:25
ED28D64C-F3534D97-8257E76A-274FAFE4|kName|kDesc|Personal Video Poker|Personal Video Poker. This Is An Animated Active Item.|Furniture/Appliance|Digital Leisure|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:131
ED2FAB0F-894F4CD5-B4F92223-15BE56FC|kName|kDesc|Dragon Rider: Ice|Ride The Steely Ice Dragon Around Your Personal Spaces With Your Friends. Blast Your Personal Spaces With Icy Dragon Breath!|Furniture/Appliance|Heavy Water|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:60
ED814323-98BD46C4-BF5B206C-F418D9E5|kName|kDesc|LOOT™ Microhifi|Fill The Air With Music! A Must Have For Any Private Or Clubhouse Space - Invite Your Friends Over And Get The Party Started! Enjoy Endless Streams Featuring Pop, Rock, Dance, And Talk. The LOOT™ Radio Delivers Real Music To The Comfort Of Your PlayStation®Home Personal Space! PLEASE READ BEFORE YOU PURCHASE Due To Contractual And Rights Agreements, Some Channels Are Nation Specific. RadioIO Is Only Available In The United States And Canada. In Addition, Due To Rights Issues, Countries May Not Receive The Same Content Selections Within The Channels. Only One Radio Or Television Can Be Active At A Time. The LOOT Radio Will Work In Any Private Space, UNLESS The Space Comes With A Tv Or Radio You Cannot Turn Off.|Furniture/Appliance|© LOOT™|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:44
ED82C3AE-3EE649A2-A7628E68-F63F8AC7|kName|kDesc|Music Unlimited Dry Ice Machine|Get To The PlayStation®Store Now And Try A 30 Day Trial Of Music Unlimited For Free. Music Unlimited Gives You Access To All The Music You Could Ever Want At Home, Online Or On The Go Via Your PlayStation®3, PlayStation®4, Mobile Phone, PlayStation®Vita, PC, Tablet Or Other Sony Connected Devices. Enjoy Millions Of Songs Advert Free And Use Offline Features To Listen To Your Playlists Even When You Have No Internet Connection!|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.82.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:6
EDEFC48B-5C344C36-B12DB87B-A924DC2E|kName|kDesc|Interactive Bar - Black|You And Up To Three Other Friends Can Sit At Your Very Own Bar And Have Your Fill Of Non-alcoholic Beverages Until The Sun Comes Up. ※Active Items Provide More Functionality Than Normal Items. You May Only Place Limited Numbers Of The Active Items In Your Apartment Or Clubhouse At Any Time.|Furniture/Appliance|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.82.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:16
EE19501B-B7A04DA0-BB1A8044-A43F2098|kName|kDesc|Demonic Victorian Sofa|Seats Three Comfortably... And Possibly... Eternally. This Is An Animated Active Item.|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:7
EE3D3AC4-D37A431B-B2836E59-1E6B5BA9|kName|kDesc|Party Spotlight|This Active Spotlight Follows Your Avatar. Customize The Mode With Color, Filter And More!|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:25
EE688794-028B40DF-BE55C5DF-2D79B519|ObjectName|ObjectDescription|Galaga™|TM & Ⓒ 1981-2009 NAMCO BANDAI Games Inc.|Furniture/Appliance|NBGI|HDK_XX|AUTO-REWARD|Res:3
EE874D90-955E4E04-99DFF3A1-F0BE1992|kName|kDesc|TORO! Let's PartyDear. Television|This TV Can Load TORO! Let's Party.|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.3.6.22.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:3
EF3928AA-CA9843C2-B978BB8B-6E37EAC1|kName|kDesc|Single Player Solitaire Game #4|Play A Game Of Solitaire On This Brown And Gold Outline Wooden Table.|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.41.0.37.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:78
EFD9F073-E97242B9-91AFB5AC-29B1D6D8|kName|kDesc|Mad Blocker: PlayStation®Home|Mad Blocker: PlayStation®Home Is A Puzzle Game Where Players Attempt To Combine Blocks Of The Same Colour.|Furniture/Appliance|Open Emotion Studios|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:3
F0A357D7-C21E4486-981B1255-F8AF5256|kName|kDesc|DUALSHOCK®3 Lightning Edition|The Wireless Controller For The PS3™ System Provides Intuitive Gameplay Experience With Its SIXAXIS Motion Sensor And Vibration Feature. This Is The Asia Limited FINAL FANTASY XIII Lightning Edition.|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.3.5.121.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:2
F0E788C6-07434F94-9EEC6EA5-B9A80E84|kName|kDesc|Sandwich Cart|This Active Item Allows You To Place Up To 40 Food Items Around Your Personal Space. Awarded For Reaching Level 41 In MiniBots In Serenity Plaza.|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|LUA-REWARD|Res:49
F17B640F-7E5249A1-9A19E4BA-A23B369B|kName|kDesc|American Pool Coffee Table|A Coffee Table For Sports Fans Which Also Doubles As A Portal To The Original V Store.|Furniture/Appliance|VEEMEE|HDK_1.3.6.22.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:4
F1B80B45-53504566-B205E699-2C070B93|kName|kDesc|Giftinator 9000|The Giftinator 9000 Is The Ultimate Gift Machine! Simply Place This Appliance In Your Personal Space And Gift Unique Items To Your Friends (or Yourself!) To Boost Your Karma, Upgrade Your Giftinator, And Unlock Exclusive Rewards As You Level Up.|Furniture/Appliance|Hellfire Games, Inc.|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|AUTO-REWARD|Res:388
F1D3A337-A5F04482-999C187E-63525E82|kName|kDesc|Cherry Red Blender|Get Cooking With This Interactive Blender!|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:14
F1F91C44-FD5E4905-930AC86F-F673C5CD|kName|kDesc|Music Unlimited Indoor Fireworks|Get To The PlayStation®Store Now And Try A 30 Day Trial Of Music Unlimited For Free. Music Unlimited Gives You Access To All The Music You Could Ever Want At Home, Online Or On The Go Via Your PlayStation®3, PlayStation®4, Mobile Phone, PlayStation®Vita, PC, Tablet Or Other Sony Connected Devices. Enjoy Millions Of Songs Advert Free And Use Offline Features To Listen To Your Playlists Even When You Have No Internet Connection!|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.82.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:8
F29812BA-5AE74843-B45C0860-C5226F18|kName|kDesc|Musical Gift-Wrapped Box|No Need To Unwrap The Box, Simply Press Play And Enjoy A Bit Of Rock Music. Includes Festive Music With A Rock-style Sound. Includes These Tracks: Joy To The World, Deck The Halls And We Wish You A Merry Christmas.|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.3.6.22.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:13
F2BDEF82-0B1A416B-9C93A85F-FB452539|kName|kDesc|Steampunk Time Travel Machine|Get Ready To Turn Back Those Hands Of Time.|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.41.0.37.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:14
F34B71D0-08E64925-87654379-D463AAE9|kName|kDesc|BBC Active Light|Take The Stage Set Light Functionality To Any Private Space You Own And Transform Them Into Locations For Shooting Your Next Movie. BBC Logo © BBC 1996|Furniture/Appliance|BBC Worldwide Limited|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:35
F3BD532D-C41C4C33-A5D5011C-8AF6A466|kName|kDesc|Active Item - Robotic Feline|A Mechanical Kitty.|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.60.0.451.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:31
F3CFD8B0-A21D46D0-9EDFAEED-E2C91F9B|kName|kDesc|LOOT™ Modern Hifi|Fill The Air With Music! A Must Have For Any Private Or Clubhouse Space - Invite Your Friends Over And Get The Party Started! Enjoy Endless Streams Featuring Pop, Rock, Dance, And Talk. The LOOT™ Radio Delivers Real Music To The Comfort Of Your PlayStation®Home Personal Space! PLEASE READ BEFORE YOU PURCHASE Due To Contractual And Rights Agreements, Some Channels Are Nation Specific. RadioIO Is Only Available In The United States And Canada. In Addition, Due To Rights Issues, Countries May Not Receive The Same Content Selections Within The Channels. Only One Radio Or Television Can Be Active At A Time. The LOOT Radio Will Work In Any Private Space, UNLESS The Space Comes With A Tv Or Radio You Cannot Turn Off.|Furniture/Appliance|© LOOT™|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:44
F3DD5626-75AF4DB3-8C263929-BAAE8529|name|description|Feature Film Camera On Heavy Duty Tripod.|A Decorative Non Functional 35mm Film Camera Prop On A Heavy Duty Tripod.|Furniture/Appliance|© 2009 LOOT™|HDK_1.3.6.22.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:2
F4058055-F8484203-BFBD526A-53506589|kName|kDesc|Lockwood Gift Machine|Give Gifts To Your Friends! Use Lockwood Gift Tokens In The Lockwood Gift Machine To Send Presents - Comes With A One Off Reward Of 61 FREE Tokens To All New Gift Machine Users. (Active Object)|Furniture/Appliance|Lockwood|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:116
F48429CB-12E3459C-AB8BE6BD-3E910531|kName|kDesc|GROW HOME : Sunflower Bush|Grow Your Own Plantlife And Show Off Your Green Fingered Skills!|Furniture/Appliance|VEEMEE|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:55
F4AA3884-B1824BED-8DA9B9DC-84632857|kName|kDesc|Scary-Go-Round|Enjoy A Ghoulish Ride On This Active Item Carousel!|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:16
F4AA9B49-5A054252-9F15455C-36BD3E64|kName|kDesc|EL-P Boombox|The Classic Boombox Has Been Updated For PlayStation®Home! This One Comes Equipped With Mind Blowing Beats From Legendary Hip Hop Producer EL-P. Explicit Content - Parental Advisory|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.60.0.450.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:15
F4E2480F-06CC41AB-B5322ED3-9BFD9160|kName|kDesc|Large Aquarium|You'll Be The Envy Of Your Friends With Your Brand New 480 Gallon Tank Complete With 5 Premium Large Fish. This Tank Will Hold Up To 30 Fish And 20 Decorations Of All Sizes. This Tank Is A Must-have For All Serious Aquarium Lovers. To Get Your Tank Started, Included With This Purchase Is The Large Fish Pack. The Fish Included Are: Livingston's Cichlid, Cortez Angelfish, Clown Trigger, Threadfin Snapper And Harlequin Sweetlips. This Is An Animated Active Item.|Furniture/Appliance|Digital Leisure|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:584
F506F869-44C94F56-9F10E19E-E93E86C0|kName|kDesc|MyKitchen - Toaster|The Linchpin Behind Every Well Rounded Breakfast. ※ Active Items Provide More Functionality Than Normal Items. You May Only Place Limited Numbers Of The Active Items In Your Apartment Or Clubhouse At Any Time.|Furniture/Appliance|VEEMEE|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:5
F51E0C6D-E59D449F-A0AA20D8-C19FCCB0|kName|kName 1|BoxBeats Mini: Nature|Sit Down, Close Your Eyes And Escape To A World Of Tranquility With BoxBeats: Nature. A Selection Of Nature Inspired Tracks To Help You Relax. NB - There May Be A Delay When You Place The Item Whilst The Music Tracks Download. This Item Has The Same Music Tracks As The Original, But The Object Representing This Item Is 75% Smaller In Physical Size. ※Active Items Provide More Functionality Than Normal Items. You May Only Place Limited Numbers Of The Active Items In Your Apartment Or Clubhouse At Any Time.|Furniture/Appliance|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:27
F52EE6B8-24684915-91DBC6FA-3888FCC6|kName|kDesc|Black Retro Speaker Right|The Right Black Retro Speaker From The LOOT™ Home Entertainment Collection.|Furniture/Appliance|© LOOT™|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:2
F533F04E-6C344408-BC686FD2-0E1DF3D1|kName|kDesc|Luxury 6 Person Bed (Safari)|You And Up To Five Other Friends Can Relax On This Interactive Bed That Includes High Quality Motion Captured Animations. ※Active Items Provide More Functionality Than Normal Items. You May Only Place Limited Numbers Of The Active Items In Your Apartment Or Clubhouse At Any Time.|Furniture/Appliance|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.82.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:17
F55E57EC-CE074400-8DE6B371-125DCEBD|kName|kDesc|4-barrel Slurpee Machine ( Killzone 3 )|Large Slurpee Machine - Dispenses Killzone 3 Slurpees For Home|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.41.0.37.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:7
F6480F58-53824D70-ADA18B7A-CE282CF4|kName|kDesc|Customizable Snowman|This Active Item Lets You Design A Snowman To Compliment Your Space. Includes A Variety Of Hats, Faces, Arms, Decorations And Custom Colors!|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:46
F67157F8-A6C446D0-B7DFE0C9-DA670F43|kName|kDesc|Personal Chef - French|Let The Chef Work His Magic And Whip You Up A Delicious Crêpe. Gather Your Friends In Your Personal Space, Grab A Plate And Indulge On The Chef's Masterpiece. Once Finished You Will Receive The Consumed Item As A Reward. ※ Active Items Provide More Functionality Than Normal Items. You May Only Place Limited Numbers Of The Active Items In Your Apartment Or Clubhouse At Any Time.|Furniture/Appliance|VEEMEE|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:40
F6F48F43-42404C7D-BBA49E51-0EAAF6F6|kName|kDesc|Bubble Fissure|Adds An Aquatic Accent To Any Space. This Active Item Creates A Spray Of Bubbles In Your Apartment|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:5
F761BB66-C1594267-9BE40E33-C86B3EFB|kName|kDesc|The Nightclub: Laser Display|Every Club Needs Lasers, Right? This Laser Display Is Perfect For The Nightclub To Help Keep The Party Going. ※Active Items Provide More Functionality Than Normal Items. You May Only Place Limited Numbers Of The Active Items In Your Apartment Or Clubhouse At Any Time.|Furniture/Appliance|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:16
F763AA48-DD9347E9-8DC3F7BB-DE5BE315|kName|kDesc|Nautilus Shell Lamp|The Perfect Accent To Any Nautical Space, This Active Item Lamp Is Animated And Lets You Customize The Color!|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:13
F76F6373-F1244D1C-A30C902A-C09D22B0|kName|kDesc|Growing Plant|A Flower's Life Cycle Is Like Watching Each Star Light Up The Night Sky.|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.3.6.22.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:26
F78E35B2-2D4A410C-8622DF31-707844B7|kName|kDesc|Fine Bed|This Active Item Has Room For 2 Avatars With Custom Poses. You Can Also Change The Color And Pattern Of The Bedding.|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:28
F797A95F-C1654663-AF370705-E589A5F0|kName|kDesc|Ghostling Pets|Set Down Your Ghostling's Tombstone To Let Your Pets Roam Around. Mind The Ectoplasm!|Furniture/Appliance|Heavy Water|HDK_1.66.0.144.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:8
F79E21E0-F0C548AD-AB8BDB2A-A012A6E9|kName|Kdesc|Go Fish Tank|A Fish Tank Populated With All The Fish You Have Caught In Go Fish|Furniture/Appliance|VEEMEE|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|AUTO-REWARD|Res:68
F7D4B4D4-81AD4526-A68F3B6E-C41DA86E|kName|kDesc|Miniature Dragon|I Wonder If They Have Manuals On How To Train Your New Dragon?|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.3.6.22.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:13
F81ABBEF-73F94A06-8D3AC408-3A3BCE11|kName|kDesc|ScrubBot 9000|This Active Item Unleashes ScrubBots That Wander Around Your Apartment. Awarded For Reaching Level 49 In MiniBots In Serenity Plaza.|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|LUA-REWARD|Res:18
F81E7B29-9F82485A-BCBF4793-A59B5A65|kName|kDesc|Minotaur Statue - Gold|Elegant Furnishings Fit For A King. Or Queen.|Furniture/Appliance|Lockwood|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|LUA-REWARD|Res:6
F822B18F-45134A41-A759BF06-49EC13C7|kName|kDesc|MiniBot Builder No. 2|This Active Item Allows You To Place Up To 50 MiniBot Furniture Items Around Your Personal Space. Awarded For Reaching Level 47 In MiniBots In Serenity Plaza.|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|LUA-REWARD|Res:54
F8DABF9E-E7124029-9E33DAEC-6E6CD526|kName|kDesc|Duck Down Records Boombox|Put Your Apartment On Blast With Hip Hop Hits From Duck Down Music Artists Boot Camp Clik, Skyzoo And Illmind, And Pharoahe Monch! Explicit Content - Parental Advisory|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.60.0.450.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:15
F8E4606F-538D4B88-9B35A58E-29E444A3|kName|kDesc|22'' LOOT™ Platinum EOD TV - Flatscreen|Discover The Benefits Of Owning Your Very Own Platinum EOD TV That Let's You Watch Full Length Movies, TV Episodes, Live Shows And More With Your Friends In PlayStation®Home! The LOOT™ Entertainment On Demand TV Will Work In Any Private Space Unless The Space Comes With A Video Screen You Cant Turn Off, It Does Not Include Streaming Radio Or Audio-only Content. Now All You Need To Do Is Invite Your Friends Over, Pull Out The Popcorn And Make The Most Important Decision Of All: What Will You Watch First!? PLEASE READ BEFORE YOU PURCHASE: Due To Contractual And Rights Agreements, Some EOD Channels Are Nation Specific. Crackle Content Is ONLY Available In United States, Canada, United Kingdom, And Australia. RadioIO Is ONLY Available In The United States And Canada. In Addition, Due To Rights Issues, Countries May Not Receive The Same Content Selections Within The Channels. Only One TV Can Be Active At A Time. The LOOT™ EOD Will Work In Any Private Space, UNLESS The Space Comes With A Video Screen You Cannot Turn Off.|Furniture/Appliance|© LOOT™|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:42
F8FFB8DC-8A414D7A-8471F33F-E83D241E|kName|kDesc|Doctor Who - K-9 Furniture|If A Dog Is Man's Best Friend, Then K-9 Is A Doctor's Best Friend! Doctor Who Logo © BBC 2013. K-9 Image © BBC/Bob Baker/Dave Martin 1977. Licensed By BBC Worldwide Limited.|Furniture/Appliance|BBC Worldwide Limited|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:12
F9A3A054-FE824E2A-B3504874-E5E81839|kName|kDesc|The Scary-achis Skeleton Mariachi Band|Liven Up Your Halloween And Day Of The Dead Celebrations With The Scary-achis Skeleton Mariachi Band! Featuring Traditional Mariachi Tunes And Life-sized, Moving Band Members, These Stiffs Are Sure To Be The Life Of The Party!|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.52.0.2.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:18
FA05D178-08554186-BD23C750-52F1223F|kName|kDesc|Peakvox Warp Core|By Launching, You Can Transfer To The Lounges Related In Peakvox. This Item Is The Furniture That Has Active Animations And Functions Associated With It. There Is A Limit To How Many Items Of This Type You Can Put In Place.|Furniture/Appliance|O-Two Inc.|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|AUTO-REWARD|Res:9
FA3D3E7B-7C6D4090-9DE90AED-5EF9A72E|kName|kDesc|50s Diner - Pinball Machine|No Need To Be In The Amusement Hall To Play Some Mean Pinball With This Machine. Exclusive To The VEEMEE 3D Printer. ※ Please Note : This Is Not A Playable Game.|Furniture/Appliance|VEEMEE|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|LUA-REWARD|Res:2
FA444D73-286F40F9-813CC6F9-44D8C0DC|kName|kDesc|40'' LOOT™ EOD TV - Flatscreen|PLEASE READ BEFORE YOU PURCHASE: Due To Contractual And Rights Agreements, Some EOD Channels Are Nation Specific. Crackle Content Is ONLY Available In United States, Canada, United Kingdom, And Australia. RadioIO Is ONLY Available In The United States And Canada. In Addition, Due To Rights Issues, Countries May Not Receive The Same Content Selections Within The Channels. Only One TV Can Be Active At A Time. The LOOT EOD Will Work In Any Private Space, UNLESS The Space Comes With A Video Screen You Cannot Turn Off. Watch Full Length Movies, TV Episodes, Live Shows And More With Your Friends In PlayStation®Home! The LOOT™ Entertainment On Demand TV Will Work In Any Private Space Unless The Space Comes With A Video Screen You Cant Turn Off, It Does Not Include Streaming Radio Or Audio-only Content. Now All You Need To Do Is Invite Your Friends Over, Pull Out The Popcorn And Make The Most Important Decision Of All: What Will You Watch First!?|Furniture/Appliance|© LOOT™|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:42
FA849135-71FD40F2-B59381AC-F9CB79FB|kName|kDesc|Intellivision® SHARK! SHARK! Arcade Game|It's Arcade Excitment With The Intellivision® Shark! Shark! Arcade Game In This Updated Version Of The Classic Game Created Especially For Playstation®Home. Big Fish Eat Little Fish In This Fun And Challenging Undersea Adventure! Watch Out For The Shark, Lobsters And Poisonous Jellyfish! Catch The Mermaid And See What Happens Next! The Bright, Colorful Game Screen And Exciting Cabinet Artwork Will Be A Thrilling Adition To Your Home! Earn The Following Four Exclusive Shark! Shark! Themed Rewards During Gameplay: An Animating T-shirt, Glitzy Game Poster, Gold-plated Trophy, And 6 Foot Themed Mobile.|Furniture/Appliance|Realtime Associates, Inc.|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:3
FA897CC9-4D44464F-B8D79172-397E28A2|kName|kDesc|Santa's Chair|This Active Item Has Room For 2, With Custom Sit Animations.|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:18
FAAF6AAE-3EF640D4-A97D0BE9-D7895DB7|kName|kDesc|Cauldron Of The Sunless Kingdom (Active Object)|Former Treasure Of The Rulers Of The Sunless Kingdom, Legend Tells That The Cauldron Could Bestow Plentiful Rewards Upon Those Who Use It. Collect Ingredients And Fuel For The Fire, Watch The Display As Your Spells Are Unleashed.|Furniture/Appliance|Lockwood|HDK_1.52.0.2.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:89
FB867646-DD93497B-8F27A1CD-06925043|kName|kDesc|Active Object - Galaxy Etched Crystal|A Rotating Piece Of Crystal That Alternates In Colour.|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.41.0.37.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:10
FBE5B4EF-CFF54E48-A73BB656-F366D048|kName|kDesc|PlayStation® All-Stars Battle Royale™: Sticker Album|A Fantastic Sticker Album For The Stickers Won By Playing The PlayStation® All-Stars Battle Royale™: Beat Down Mini Game.|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|AUTO-REWARD|Res:29
FC0B3914-EB3744DD-83212EC8-C6D6DBBE|kName|kDesc|Lamp Of The Terra|This Lamp Is Imbued With The Essence Of The Earth, Granting Any Space The Vibrant Beauty Of A Garden Paradise.|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.65.0.139.BETA|LUA-REWARD|Res:19
FC8CD1BF-0CAB4F65-9519E0AB-E387B4A2|kName|kDesc|Active Object - Earth Orbit Orrery|Watch The Earth Spin On It's Axis With This Orrery.|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.41.0.37.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:13
FCDE0B31-12314790-BEE2462E-8EF6428E|kName|kDesc|BoxBeats: Rock 2|This Powerful Sound System Comes Jam Packed With Over 10 Rocking Tracks For You And Your Friends To Listen To While You Rock Out. This Active Item Also Allows You To Select Specific Tracks To Play, Set The Volume And Even Randomise The Track List. This Is An Essential Item For Your Apartment. NB - There May Be A Delay When You Place The Item Whilst The Music Tracks Download.|Furniture/Appliance|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:28
FCF27A61-CD2F4B0D-8495E3C5-C17AD846|kName|kDesc|Personal Closet|Use Your Personal Closet To Display All Your Digital Leisure Outfits. Unlock Closet Upgrades By Owning More Outfits. Visit The Digital Leisure Shop To Purchase More Outfits Or Win Outfits At The Casino. This Is An Animated Active Item.|Furniture/Appliance|Digital Leisure Inc.|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|AUTO-REWARD|Res:141
FD15D62F-5034451B-96684F4B-EA9C766B|kName|kDesc|Timepieces - Steampunk Clock|Always Know What The Time Is With This Working Clock. Exclusive To The VEEMEE 3D Printer. The Time Is Automatically Set Using The Time On Your PlayStation®3. ※ Active Items Provide More Functionality Than Normal Items. You May Only Place Limited Numbers Of The Active Items In Your Apartment Or Clubhouse At Any Time.|Furniture/Appliance|VEEMEE|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|LUA-REWARD|Res:9
FD174CF7-FD094C74-B8177267-84BBD8DB|kName|kDesc|DUALSHOCK®3|Wireless PS3® Controller (CECHZC2J)|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.3.0.94.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:2
FD89C1F3-8FAC45D6-84300495-5FADBAC6|kName|kDesc|Las Vegas Suite Treadmill 1|Hop On This Treadmill And Get Your Cardio On! This Is An Active Item.|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.60.0.451.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:15
FDA37525-4BD34919-8E604085-9596B9DF|kName|kDesc|Snowball Pile|This Active Item Lets You Throw Snowballs With [CROSS] - Snowball Fight!|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:25
FDF25607-E96545B2-AA518189-9DAD752C|kName|kDesc|Magic Globe|This Animated Active Item Is A Must Have For Any Astronomy Enthusiast|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:6
FDF80D8F-FA104E48-918DBE6E-DFA33861|kName|kDesc|Mysterious Doll|There's Something About This Doll...|Furniture/Appliance|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.41.0.37.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:36
FE1B38A1-71BD11E1-ACA70022-19291EC2|kName|kDesc|Modernist Double Bed - Romance (Active Object)|Clean Modern Lines With A Touch Of Romance! Lockwood Beds Are Active Objects With A Realistic 'lie Down' Animation, So Lie Back And Relax On This Dreamy, Comfortable Bed. Owners Of The Cucumber Modernist Double Bed - Romance Can Purchase The Modernist Double Bed - Romance At A Discounted Price.|Furniture/Appliance|Lockwood|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:32
FE8280F2-3597435D-9D3BAD1C-1EB95357|kName|kDesc|Romantic Fireplace|This Fireplace Active Item Plays Classy Jazz Music.|Furniture/Appliance|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:7
FE9A4211-31C645C1-97B1B372-FCAE3ED4|ObjectName|ObjectDescription|XEVIOUS™|TM & Ⓒ 1982-2009 NAMCO BANDAI Games Inc.|Furniture/Appliance|NBGI|HDK_XX|AUTO-REWARD|Res:3
