BD8D559F-9E554E7E-9D51A766-62E08C99|||GDC 2007 Harbour Studio|The 0.41 GDC Demo Harbour studio, ported to new engine by Pongo|Scene/Entitlement|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_0.41/1.86|NON_REWARD|0|Ported by Pongo
00C4E166-D83A48EC-9A89767E-5F1F1410|kName|kDesc|MotorStorm® Pacific Rift Camp|Unwind After A Day Of Brutal Racing In Your Beachfront Campsite.|Scene/Entitlement|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.3.2.16.BETA1|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
02F15FC6-DE494F61-A2856059-3765740B|Name|Desc|The Prairie Saloon|Mosey On Down To The Saloon For A Rootin' Tootin' Good Time. Put On A Performance On The Stage, Ride Around The Expansive Grounds, Or Tend To Your Horse. Includes: • Horse Care Game With 7 In-game Rewards • 4 Exclusive Saloon Rewards This Space Is A Clubhouse.|Scene/Entitlement|Lockwood|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
03DE7562-803A4BCC-A28ACD3C-8F3AB87D|Name|Desc|Pharaoh's Tomb|Loosely Translated From The Hieroglyphs: Here Lies Pharaoh Homenkhammun, About Whom Dancers Rejoice And Upon Whom The Eye Of Horus Lingers. Loved By All, May He Find Further Glory In The West.|Scene_Entitlement|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.52.0.2.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
042A70AF-C4C641B7-AAB55602-1FE708AC|kName|kDesc|The Spunland Cottage|Take Up Residence In The Spunland Cottage, With Scenic Views Of The Purple Skies And Hills Of Spunland. Includes A Garden Area With A Grazing Flusho Spunner, Suitable For Relaxing In The Afternoon. Explore The Maze In The Darker Depths Of The Cottage When The House Lumino Spunner Permits Access. Trigger Sonic Spunners For Your Own Combination Of Soundtrack, Or Invite Your Friends Over For A Score Challenge And Start The Spun Clock: Who Can Catch The Most Rabbits, Collect The Most Fruit And Find The Most Eggs In The Spun Time Limit? Become A Spun Home Owner Today!|Scene/Entitlement|Madmunki|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
046B3B88-640B45ED-A1A0AF17-9EEFC570|kName|kDesc|Musicality Apartment|Description.|Scene/Entitlement|NDreams|HDK_1.3.2.16.BETA1|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
04E65407-CAC7407E-A862359E-8B4E176D|kName|kDesc|The Halloween Tour Bus Clubhouse|The Time Has Come To Hit The Road And Party. Take Full Advantage Of The Freedoms A Virtual World Provides, Slip The Bus Into Cruise Control And Join The Party At Full Speed! Just Remember… What Goes On Tour, Stays On Tour!|Scene/Entitlement|JAM Games Ltd|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
051F2E74-69BF4FDD-B637F49D-EFD679B9|kName|kDesc|Discotheque Clubhouse|Dance The Night Away In This Stylish Discotheque! Featuring Animated Disco Balls, Spotlights And Lasers, This Vast Underground Night-club Even Contains A Rythm-action Dance Mini-game, With A High-score Leaderboard! Scoring 100,000 Points Will Give You An Exclusive Reward... Whether You Prefer To Challenge Your Friends At The Mini-game, Party On The Animated Illuminated Dance Floor, Sit On The Stools At The Bar, Or Relax On The Comfy Armchairs, This Is The Perfect Place To Invite Your Friends!|Scene/Entitlement|Atom Republic|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
053159ED-F78E43D3-B58BEEDE-CC3A6831|kName|kDesc|Obsidian Officer's Quarters|Earth Fleet Has Constructed A New Residency Wing Of The Novus Prime Space Station For High-ranking Obsidian Pilots. Each Apartment Includes A Zero-Gravity Simulation System For The Owner And Guests.|Scene/Entitlement|Hellfire Games, Inc.|HDK_1.83.0.11.PUB|AUTO-REWARD|Res:0
0537BA1A-F8934743-BFB06EEF-5819D61E|Name|Desc|Men In Black™ Headquarters|Get An All-access Pass When You Own The Men In Black™ Headquarters As Your Own Private Space!  Enjoy Being The Boss Of The Most Top-secret Organization Established To Monitor Alien Activity On Earth! Hang Out With Frank The Pug In The MIB™ Offices, Shop In The Armory And Relax In The Break Room! So Suit Up And Get Ready For The Explosive Return Of Agents Kay And Jay In Men In Black™ III And The Epic New Video Game Men In Black: Alien Crisis™!|Scene/Entitlement|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.65.0.139.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
054FAFA9-D5DF4164-ADE3FC96-4F6C2A75|kName|kDesc|The Nightclub: Clubhouse|The Nightclub Is The Perfect Venue For A Fantastic Night Out. Dance To Pumping Music Tracks On The Dance Floor, Sip On Drinks In The Lounge Area, Or Activate The Foam Cannon For An Extra Crazy Night! Please Note, In Order To Access This Clubhouse You Will Need To Have Purchased The Clubhouse Slot From Either The Estates Store Or The Clubs Menu (available In Options).|Scene/Entitlement|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
0716BAC9-CBE74C2B-95E69620-0B42F835|kName|kDesc|A Dark Wizards Mansion|Who Knows What Dark Magic Has Been Performed Within These Walls? This Centuries-old Stately Home Is The Perfect Residence For The Aspiring Dark Witch Or Wizard. Please Be Aware That Only Pottermore Furniture Can Be Placed In Pottermore Personal Apartments And That All Chat Functions Have Been Disabled. Pottermore Furniture Can Be Purchased From The Pottermore Shop. [#PMExtraCommerce]|Scene/Entitlement|MakerXX|HDK_1.82.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
07357F60-FC504982-9E946020-1702D76A|kName|kDesc|Glittering Sands Secluded Retreat|Spend Your Holiday On A Luxurious Private Beach. The Clear Blue Sea, The White Sandy Beach, And The Cottage On The Ocean Are All Yours. With A Friend, Or With That Special Someone. Your Holiday Has Just Begun.|Scene/Entitlement|Granzella Inc.|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
08A50448-25C6408F-93B42144-556321E7|kName|kDesc|The Spunland Cottage|Take Up Residence In The Spunland Cottage, With Scenic Views Of The Purple Skies And Hills Of Spunland.|Scene/Entitlement|MadMunki|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
099A248E-806944C7-887FB154-064F33D3|kName|kDesc|Xi: Continuum - Vertigo Apartment|This Fantastical Outdoor Apartment, Situated On The Side Of A Skyscraper Overlooking The Continuum, Defies Belief. This Apartment Grows In Size As You Play Through Xi: Continuum, Resulting In A Massive And Amazing Home.|Scene/Entitlement|NDreams|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
09E3FE8D-5AEC4942-8AEE85EF-B4C3B3C9|kName|kDesc|Country Chic - Tour Bus|The Time Has Come To Hit The Road And Party. Take Full Advantage Of The Freedoms A Virtual World Provides, Slip The Bus Into Cruise Control And Join The Party At Full Speed! Just Remember… What Goes On Tour, Stays On Tour!|Scene/Entitlement|JAM Games Ltd|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
0A64C871-7C434211-98163DE4-7D8712B5|Name|Desc|Discotheque|Dance The Night Away In This Stylish Discotheque! Featuring Animated Disco Balls, Spotlights And Lasers, This Vast Underground Night-club Even Contains A Rythm-action Dance Mini-game, With A High-score Leaderboard! Getting A High Score Will Give You An Exclusive Reward... Whether You Prefer To Challenge Your Friends At The Mini-game, Party On The Animated Illuminated Dance Floor, Sit On The Stools At The Bar, Or Relax On The Comfy Armchairs, This Is The Perfect Place To Invite Your Friends!|Scene/Entitlement|Atom Republic|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
0AA250D3-05B24899-B256646A-D78D9E8E|kName|kDesc|Audi Technology Apartment|The Audi Technology Apartment Is Your Reward For Configuring And Racing Your Perfect Car In The Audi Technology Experience. Inside The Apartment You Can Relax, Entertain Your Friends, Or Simply Admire The View Of The City Below.|Scene/Entitlement|AUDI AG|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|LUA-REWARD|Res:0
0ABB6079-08A1450F-9BBFC56B-B89AC16A|kName|kDesc|Secret Peacekeeping Base, Yuma Café|At A Glance It Appears To Be A Tasteful Coffee Shop, But Behind A Door In The Rear Is A Secret Base For Heroes That Utilise The Most Advanced Science To Battle Evil. Well Then, Let's Defend Our Tranquil Planet Earth From The Clutches Of Evil!|Scene/Entitlement|Granzella Inc.|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
0D9584EC-0FC64A01-A7134965-E39748BF|Name|Desc|The War Room Clubhouse|The War Room - Perfect For Clan Meetings, Socialising And Plotting World Domination. You And Your Fellow Warmongerers Can Have Your Face And Commands Displayed On Large Screens Throughout This High Tech Facility.|Scene/Entitlement|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.55.0.155.BETA2|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
0E54B445-040D401C-AF083E48-8139E4D4|kName|kDesc|Japanese Teahouse|A Remote Mountain Location, With Abundant Vegetation And Water. A Small Teahouse Stands Past The Gate, Beyond The Garden Stepping Stones.The Confined Teahouse Built According To The Principles Of Wabi And Sabi Allows One To Draw Near To Visitors. Spend A Brief Moment In Silence.|Scene/Entitlement|Granzella Inc.|HDK_1.60.0.450.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
0E5D3D72-B67D421A-A626C84B-5237A634|kName|kDesc|Moonlight Room|When The Sun Sets, Darkness Reigns The Night And Only The Magic Of The Moon Lights Up The Streets. At That Precise Moment, The Moonlight Room Comes To Life. Its Dark Tones And Silver Trims Are Full With Beauty, Class And Distinction. This Is A Shelter For Lovers Of The Night.|Scene/Entitlement|KOVOK LTD|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
0F3C9BF0-FA9C4B3B-A3071A0A-411B0DC7|Name|Desc|LOOT™'s Space Apartment|Enjoy The Luxury Of The Future With This Three-story Apartment With Loft. Experience The Expansive Views Of Earth, Space And The LOOT™ Space Station. Watch Jellyfish Swim In The Two-story Aquarium Located In The Center Of The Apartment. Relax In The Aquatic Meditation Environment Located On The Bottom Level. This Wonderful Personal Space Is Also Equipped With Your Own Space Apartment Remote Access (S.A.R.A.). With S.A.R.A.s Help You Can: View Up To 5 Different Twitter Feeds On A News Ticker; Choose Out Of 8 Screen Locations To View Your LOOT EOD; Search For Photos On FlickR And Display Them On Any Or All Of The 16 Photo Screens Available Throughout The Space. Each Photo Screen Even Lets You Set-up Slideshows. S.A.R.A.s Also Lets You Control Your Environment With Retractable Ceiling, Automated Blinds And Dynamic Lighting Options. In Space, You Couldnt Ask For A Better Friend.|Scene/Entitlement|LOOT™|HDK_1.52.0.2.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
0F51150B-D31C4F40-96B20FEF-AC82FEBD|kName|kDesc|Acorn Meadows Park Apartment - 1st Birthday!|Join Us In In Celebrating Acorn Meadows Park's 1st Birthday! Your Own Little Private Slice Of Acorn Meadows Park, This Lakeside Garden Apartment Provides The Perfect Place To Relax And Take Time Away From The Main Park Without Leaving The Acorn Meadows Environment. Awarded In The 1st Birthday Acorn Meadows Park After Completing All 22 Birthday Challanges.|Scene/Entitlement|VEEMEE|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|LUA-REWARD|Res:0
102DFC5F-2B8C4DCF-BD51BA1B-EA9BE2E5|kName|kDesc|Acorn Meadows Park Apartment - Winter|Your Own Little Private Slice Of Acorn Meadows Park, This Lakeside Garden Apartment Provides The Perfect Place To Relax And Take Time Away From The Main Park Without Leaving The Acorn Meadows Environment.|Scene/Entitlement|VEEMEE|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
1095EC78-EE204E80-A07EE02D-D2664E88|kName|kDesc|Toro House|This 8-mat Room Is Modeled After The Room Toro Lived In On Mainichi Issho. It Has A Kitchen And Toilet.|Scene/Entitlement|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.3.6.22.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
110C12A4-3B924418-82BC3C59-F90B14C2|kName|kDesc|The Sports Bar|Spend Time With Your Friends In This Sports-themed Bar, Complete With Darts Game. Exclusive To The VEEMEE 3D Printer.|Scene/Entitlement|VEEMEE|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|LUA-REWARD|Res:0
11A90C45-2C6F4968-B102B468-72D4614B|kName|kDesc|Loco Island|This Personal Space Is Your Very Own Tropical Island Inhabited By LocoRoco™ Characters. The Tropical Retreat Is Full Of Exciting Activities. Collect Berries That Fall From The Trees, And Communicate With Islanders To Expand The Facilities. Enjoy The Swing, Slide, Jukebox, And Games For Two Players! And The More Time You Spend On Loco Island, The More Vibrant And Exciting The Paradise Becomes! Treat Yourself To This Fun-filled Personal Space!|Scene/Entitlement|Sony Computer Entertainmnet|HDK_1.3.2.27.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
11BFD9EE-F0DD4BAC-A114B216-106678CE|Name|Desc|Gothic Cathedral|This Ancient Abandoned Cathedral On The Cliff Is A Sanctuary And A Place You Call Home.  From The Majestic Room, Moonlit Courtyard, To The Massive Candlelit Hall, You Can Be The Ruler Of The Night.|Scene/Entitlement|Konami|HDK_1.65.0.139.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
11F3AD9E-72174F8B-91705D78-D39048BE|kName|kDesc|The Jam Jar Clubhouse|The Jam Jar Was Established In The 1940s As THE Place To Go. Discover The Opulence And Grandeur Of This By Gone Era In A Building Rescued And Restored To Its Rightful Glory! Whether You Decide To Return It To It's Full Boutique Status, Use It's Exquisite Detail As A Backdrop For A Gallery Or As The Venue Of The Latest Fashion Event, The Jam Jar Will Still Prove To Be THE Place To Be Seen!|Scene/Entitlement|JAM Games Ltd|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
12DD1398-68EB4301-9A7FE3BF-BC551325|kName|kDesc|Abbey Hill Cottage|In A Picturesque Setting Beside The River, Stands The Timeless Abbey Hill Cottage. Dating Back To The 17th Century, This Period House Was Home To The Lord Ronald Phillipson – Distant Cousin To The Inventor Of The Watering Can. The Cottage Now Nestles In Serenity, Amongst Stunning Scenery, Enveloped By A Breathtaking Countryside Scene.|Scene/Entitlement|Lockwood|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
12E77FEB-354F4FFE-AB0684EF-6303485F|kName|kDesc|City Of Flowers Penthouse Window To The World|Make This Apartment Penthouse In Downtown Paris Yours, Between The Eiffel Tower And The Arc De Triomphe. Your Life In The City Of Flowers, Paris, Begins Here.|Scene/Entitlement|Granzella Inc.|HDK_1.60.0.450.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
130CC37C-8FBA4D64-A629246F-CF54C524|Name|Desc|Nostalgic School Days|Make The First Floor Of A School Building Yours, Including Two Classrooms, A Shop, And A Hallway. The Layout Of Desks, Chairs, And Other Items Is Up To You. Make Your Own Unique Classroom And Enjoy School Life Along With Your Friends! Be Careful Not To Stay At School Until Late At Night. You Never Know What Might Happen...|Scene/Entitlement|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
13CA27D2-243C4F63-BCE0193A-88AAA80A|Name|Desc|Nightlife Lounge Apartment|Spend A Night Out On The Town In Your Very Own Nightlife Lounge. Inside, You Can Wine And Dine Your Guests As They Walk Down The Fashion Runway Inside. Get Cozy And Have A Drink In The Lounge Area. Are You Ready To Party?|Scene/Entitlement|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.66.0.144.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
16609817-77F646D8-878789D7-135196C6|kName|kDesc|Japanese Apartment|A Traditional Japanese Apartment. Serene And Tranquil.|Scene/Entitlement|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.3.5|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
1662E4E3-4C2846BC-9EF46DE8-A86169B5|kName|kDesc|Abbey Hill Cottage - Winter Retreat|When Winter Descends, Abbey Hill Takes On A New Form Of Beauty. Revel In The Stark White Charm Of The Riverside Cottage In The Festive Season. Escape From The Cold In The Fireside Or Explore The Gardens To Earn The 7 Daily Rewards On Offer. If You're Feeling Really Adventurous, Why Not Go For A Skate On The Frozen Surface Of The River?|Scene/Entitlement|Lockwood|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
186BE0D9-22DE4333-A7395829-E9CB3B6A|Name|Desc|Red Bull House Of Skate|FOR SALE: Red Bulls 10,000 Sq Ft House Of Skate Including Scenic Views Of The Hollywood Hills, Steamy Hot Tub And A Playable Skate Game. Flip, Grind, And Ollie Your Way Through This Modern Skate Haven While Earning Medals And Street Cred. Make It Your Own!|Scene/Entitlement|Red Bull|HDK_1.55.0.155.BETA2|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
18824AB2-6D524781-9E478811-3C9E7200|kName|kDesc|The Dream Yacht|Have The Lifestyle You Always Dreamed Of With The Dream Yacht From Figment. Three Decks Of Opulent Living, Two Hot Tubs And More Than 20 Collectable Rewards, Plus An Exclusive Commerce Point Only Available Through The Dream Yacht. Live The Dream!|Scene/Entitlement|Lockwood|HDK_1.55.0.155.BETA2|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
18F0F0C6-38D24084-BE4DA40F-1EC02165|kName|kDesc|Luxury Train Apartment|Sometimes You Can't Spend All Day In Your Apartment As You Have To Head To Important Meetings And Social Events. Take A Trip Through A Scenic Environment Whilst Relaxing With Your Friends As The World Outside Passes You By.|Scene/Entitlement|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.82.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
1917DB58-A04D42B5-85D08416-CDD2E416|kName|kDesc|Seasons-themed Room|A Personal Space To Enjoy The Changing Seasons.|Scene/Entitlement|O-Two Inc.|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
191F955B-4BD24508-90A8A889-DAFF792C|kName|kDesc|A House In Hogsmeade|The Only All-wizarding Village In Britain, Hogsmeade Is Situated Close To Hogwarts. The Hogwarts Express Travels To And From The Village's Station. Please Be Aware That Only Pottermore Furniture Can Be Placed In Pottermore Personal Apartments And That All Chat Functions Have Been Disabled. Pottermore Furniture Can Be Purchased From The Pottermore Shop. [#PMExtraCommerce]|Scene/Entitlement|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
1A30EAA8-AEAA4233-928A66FD-CBE32880|Name|Desc|Demonic Cutteridge Estate|The Abysmal Darkness Will Imprison Your Soul For Eternity.|Scene/Entitlement|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.65.0.139.BETA|LUA-REWARD|Res:0
1A485810-8150433B-A0D6BFC6-F4B01942|kName|kDesc|The London Pub|[Only For Those Above 18 Years Old. Please Verify That You Are 18 Years Of Age Or Older To Purchase.] Located In London, England, The Pub Comes With Its Own Fantastic Darts Game And High Score Tables, Working Drink Pumps And A Bunch Of Hidden Surprises And Rewards. Cheers!|Scene_Entitlement|VEEMEE|HDK_1.55.0.155.BETA2|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
1B2C4D74-C86949D3-BCC4A238-B0514542|kName|kDesc|The Complex 2: Clubhouse|This Clubhouse, Brought To You By NDreams, Is Based On The Complex 2 Apartment. This Luxurious Cliff-side Complex Comes With All Additional Rooms And Rewards Already Unlocked.|Scene/Entitlement|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
1C74781B-CABB4D85-B8244868-FED66129|kName|kDesc|Meekum Industries Skylab|Meekum Industries Skylab|Scene/Entitlement|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.82.0.17.PUB|AUTO-REWARD|Res:0
1CC3FC83-AD55454C-B2A32C67-5D55B95D|Name|Desc|Hollywood Hills House Nighttime Estate (with Home Theatre)|Gaze Upon Glistening Los Angeles As Hollywood Hills Royalty, In Your Private Mansion Above The LA Skyline! Features Include: • Built-in Entertainment On Demand Theatre System; • A Swimming Feature For The Infinity Pool! THIS Is The Spot To Entertain Your Closest Friends And Clients. Purchase Of This Estate Comes Bundled With The LOOT™ Active Camera And Active Light, So You Can Film Your Parties And Upload Them To YouTube! PLEASE READ: Due To Contractual And Rights Agreements, All Content May Not Be Available In All Countries. Content Availability Is Dependent On The Geolocation Of The Device. CRACKLE Content Is Only Available In US, CA, UK, And AU. RADIOIO Is Only Available In US And CA. Only One LOOT™ TV Or LOOT™ Radio Can Be Active At A Time.|Scene/Entitlement|© LOOT™|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
1D021442-7BD7468F-BA141BF9-66FDF589|Name|Desc|Infinite Oasis Ranch Clubhouse|The Perfect Place For A Mid-summer Retreat, The Infinite Oasis Ranch Has It All. From Lively Cacti And Ageless Palm Trees To Panoramic Views Of The Surrounding Mountain Ridge, This Space Packs It All. The Infinite Oasis Ranch Space Is A Clubhouse Where Everyone Is Invited To Join.|Scene/Entitlement|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
1E99D78A-109444AD-95763330-D304BB9C|Name|Desc|Darla's Den|This Is Our Gift To You Just For Visiting The Midway. Admire Your Prowess On The Prize Runway, Win Access To The Steamy Hot Tub, Earn Your Entry Into The Big Bang Game, Purchase A Personal Arcade Shooter, And Ultimately Entertain Darla In The Disco!|Scene/Entitlement|Mass Media|HDK_1.41.0.37.PUB|AUTO-REWARD|Res:0
1E9A6095-B9B045B9-B61AA895-A0211CFD|Name|Desc|Crystal Seashores Clubhouse|Crystal Seashores Is A Lavish Waterfront Home Meant For Those With Extravagant Lifestyles. A Split Staircase, Open Foyer, And Backyard Swimming Pool Are Just Footnotes When Compared To The Ocean View This Home Has To Offer. The Crystal Seashores Space Is A Clubhouse Where Everyone Is Invited To Join.|Scene/Entitlement|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
1F06C254-A7E64A30-B6D21BDC-AA465F64|Name|Desc|The Dream Yacht|Have The Lifestyle You Always Dreamed Of With The Dream Yacht From Figment. Three Decks Of Opulent Living, Two Hot Tubs And More Than 20 Collectable Rewards, Plus An Exclusive Commerce Point Only Available Through The Dream Yacht. Live The Dream!|Scene/Entitlement|Lockwood Publishing|HDK_1.55.0.155.BETA2|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
1F6031AD-BC924534-AA6C070D-F402AB71|Name|Desc|Aurora-Champion-Apartment|To Reward You For Your Hard Work And Dedication To Aurora, We Have Gifted You This Aurora Champion Apartment.|Scene_Entitlement|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.55.0.155.BETA2|AUTO-REWARD|Res:0
1F80696E-77F141C2-8E0AEEBF-41E0943D|kName|kDesc|South Island Retreat|An Isolated Island In The South Sea Where We Washed Up. The Sun Was Shining, The Sea Was Calm, And The Wind Was Fresh! I Forgot To Go Home And Built A House On The Cliff. The Back Door Of The Log House Will Allow You To Go To The Private Garden Of The Lounge South Island Retreat. In Addition, Various Elements Will Be Added To This Personal Space In The Future.|Scene/Entitlement|Granzella Inc.|HDK_1.52.0.2.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
1FA691D0-0F0444E1-8406D8F9-701754E7|kName|kDesc|Dream Forest Paradise Clubhouse|Throw A Dance Party In The Great Outdoors, A Treetop Pot-luck, Or A Swim Party In The Natural Lagoon, The Dream Forest Paradise Clubhouse Has Plenty Of Room For Up To 32 Of You. As Well As The Unparalleled Natural Beauty You'll Find The Usual Exquisite Architecture You've Come To Expect From Figment, And Unique Rewards Too. Live The Dream!|Scene/Entitlement|Lockwood|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
1FEAC29F-8B014DF2-9EE260D1-0A68D863|kName|kDesc|Inferno Apartment|Literally The Hottest Place To Hang Out In PlayStation®Home. Amongst The Fire And Brimstone You Will Make Your Home, Welcome To Hell!|Scene/Entitlement|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
2184D212-54FF4735-81E3EA0D-3CBC4644|Name|Desc|Doctor Who TARDIS|TARDIS Stands For Time And Relative Dimension In Space. The TARDIS Looks Like A 1950s Wooden Police Phone Box On The Outside, But Is Of Infinite Proportions On The Inside. Amaze Your Friends When They Discover The Wonder Of Time Lord Technology. Doctor Who Logo © 2013 And TM BBC. Licensed By BBC WW Ltd.|Scene/Entitlement|BBC Worldwide Ltd.|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
2192F52B-7E944DC9-9A40F760-F12033E4|Name|Desc|Iron Fusion Vault (Male)|Hidden In A Top Secret Location, This Vault Is Filled With A Collection Of New Suits From Iron Fusion, Each With Their Own Individual Mechanics. The Iron Fusion Vault Holds The Secrets To Metering Out Swift Justice In PlayStation®Home. Upon Entering The Iron Fusion Vault, The Owner Will Be Awarded Mechjet – Epic Plus Four Special Suits: Panthabot – Bhaltair, Barrin Mech Suit, Mechjet – Magnor And Mechsuit Pilot – Diablo.|Scene/Entitlement|Lockwood Publishing|HDK_1.82.0.17.PUB|LUA-REWARD|Res:0
225510C0-B3B64333-8B8C840D-6E1D2FE4|kName|kDesc|Summer Sunflowers In Bloom|A Personal Space Where You Can Enjoy The Good Old Japanese Summer.|Scene/Entitlement|O-Two Inc.|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
2299E927-A704446A-92F7BBF0-28703E9A|kName|kDesc|Bowling Apartment SEO|Bowling Apartment SEO|Scene/Entitlement|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.82.0.17.PUB|AUTO-REWARD|Res:0
229F3980-C3394E99-B2BCFB15-6EDD4D17|Name|Desc|Nightlife Lounge Clubhouse|Spend A Night Out On The Town In Your Very Own Nightlife Lounge. Inside, You Can Wine And Dine Your Guests As They Walk Down The Fashion Runway Inside. Get Cozy And Have A Drink In The Lounge Area. Are You Ready To Party? The Nightlife Lounge Is A Clubhouse Where Everyone Is Invited To Join.|Scene/Entitlement|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.66.0.144.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
22B9041C-510E41C9-B2A9FD1B-F714C14F|Name|Desc|Villain's Lair|The Only Place A Super Villain Like You Can Hide Is In This Volcanic Lair. Complete With Everything A Dastardly Leader Needs To Overthrow The Establishment; A Mini-game Of World Domination, An Entire Village To Destroy At Your Whim, And A Laser Guarded Display Area For All Your Treasures.|Scene_Entitlement|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.3.2.27.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
237914DD-BF554245-8EDE0BEF-EB9F7F70|Name|Desc|Tree House Personal Apartment|A Stunning Circular Treehouse Built Around The Trunk Of An Ancient Tree High Up In The Mountains. Made Of Wood And Circular In Design, There Are Two Levels Each Offering Spectacular Views Of The Waterfalls And Mountains Outside.|Scene/Entitlement|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.3.6.22.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
24173B77-ABAA41F0-A6FD488D-745960B5|kName|kDesc|The Boutique Apartment: Clubhouse|This Clubhouse From NDreams Is The Perfect Place For The Suave And Sexy Socialites Of PlayStation®Home - Based On The Boutique Apartment. This Luxury Clubhouse Comes With All The Additional Rooms Already Unlocked.|Scene/Entitlement|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
24A7086F-40CF45F6-B5245CA5-11796C8B|Name|Desc|Rapture Metro Apartment|From Sinclair Solutions, Please Enjoy Your New Apartment In Rapture. As A Valued Sinclair Solutions Tester, We Know You Need A Place To Relax After Trying Out Our New Products. Remember To Explore The Space And See All That Rapture Has To Offer.|Scene/Entitlement|2K Games|HDK_1.3.5.121.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
24F5461A-E7E14954-8DD17411-D3A3BC24|Name|Desc|Anime Style Apartment|Anime Fans, Rejoice! A Personal Space For The Otaku In All Of Us.|Scene_Entitlement|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.41.0.37.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
25D7BA23-D7EE47C1-80C5C244-A9BA124E|Name|Desc|The Prairie Ranch|Git Along Little Doggie! You Can't Call Yourself A Bona Fide Ranch Owner Until You've Put Your Horse Handling Skills To The Test. Groom And Feed Your Horse – The Owners Who Take The Best Care Of Their Horses Are Most Richly Rewarded! Includes: • Horse Care Game With 7 In-game Rewards • 4 Exclusive Ranch Rewards, 1 Of Which Is Also Available To Guests! This Space Is An Apartment.|Scene/Entitlement|Lockwood|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
264D8C56-07FF4310-96DE5B89-AC8AAF8B|kName|kDesc|Secret Base To Keep The Peace Yuma Cafe|At First Glance, The Cafe Looks Quaint, But Behind The Door Is A Secret Base Where Heroes Fight Evil Using The Most Advanced Scientific Power. Now, You Must Protect The Peaceful Earth From The Hands Of Evil!|Scene/Entitlement|Granzella Inc.|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
287F383E-76304151-A60A94A1-37840CBD|kName|kDesc|Dream Adventure|Explore Stunning Tropical Islands And Discover Hidden Rewards Aboard The Dream Adventure Yacht. Leave The Yacht On Cruise And Relax On The Deck Watching The World Go By, Or Get Active On The Water Craft Or Treasure Hunting Minigames! With 12 Exclusive Rewards.|Scene/Entitlement|Lockwood|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
28ADC591-B63448AC-B326E5DF-FC17A223|Name|Desc|Playstation®Home Mansion - Ground Floor|Welcome To The PlayStation®Home Mansion, An Extravagant Space Filled With Some Of The Rarest Items Around. On The Ground Floor Youll Find Your Mansion Comes Equipped With The Best Security Money Can Buy: A Live Tiger! An Imperial Staircase Will Lead You To The First Floor While Your Kitchen Comes Fully Stocked With Gold Appliances To Fit Your Cooking Needs And An Adjacent Dining Room For You And Your Guests. Best Of All, Youll Be Able To Walk Around While Wearing Your Very Own 100 % Gold-virtual-thread Lounge-wear That Comes As A Reward For Purchasing The New Space. And For An Added Bonus The PlayStation®Home Mansion Also Allows For Up To 5 Gold Rewards For Each Of Your Guests. Enjoy Your Time In The Good Life!|Scene/Entitlement|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.55.0.155.BETA2|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
2935147C-2D4043C9-87E252B8-B960C809|kName|kDesc|Ghostbusters™ Firehouse|Own The Ghostbusters™ Firehouse HQ, A Three Floor Personal Space With Ghost Containment, Garage/office And Living Areas. Also Included Are A Full-size Ecto-1, An Interactive Camera And A Flying Slimer.|Scene/Entitlement|© 2009 Columbia Pictures Industries, Inc. All Rights Reserved.|HDK_1.3.6.22.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
29397063-00C041E6-96009BC5-5DD3D992|Name|Desc|Moonlight Space|This Is The Personal Space Of Peakvox Ninja, Japanese Lounge.|Scene/Entitlement|O-Two Inc.|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
298D3979-079048B5-AA6E88E8-1BED6E70|kName|kDesc|MyGym Apartment|The Luxurious MyGym Apartment Is Perfect Way To Get In Shape Or Relax After A Hard Day. Train Your Avatar On The Built-in MyGym Equipment: ● MyGym - Equipment - Weights Bench ● MyGym - Equipment - Stair Machine ● MyGym - Equipment - Cross Trainer ● MyGym - Equipment - Rowing Machine ● MyGym - Equipment - Running Machine ● MyGym - Equipment - Cycling Machine There Are Many Ways To Keep Fit In The MyGym Apartment, Head To The Weights Room To Build Some Muscle Or Find Your Centre In The Yoga Room. After Your Work Out Use The MySpa Changing Room To Get Into Your Swimming Clothes Then Head To The Sauna, Hot Tub Or Relax In The Infinity Pool With A Beautiful View Of The Nearby Tropical Islands.|Scene/Entitlement|VEEMEE|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
2A12CD40-E8D5450A-8E588773-4B37571B|kName|kDesc|Masquerade Ball - The Ballroom|The Perfect Personal Space To Host A Lavish Masquerade Ball. Entertain Your Guests In This Beautiful Ballroom. Deck Out Your Ballroom With The Masquerade Ball Furniture Range For Extra Authenticity.|Scene/Entitlement|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
2A1841E3-A5584FCF-82CE49E9-A6091868|Name|Desc|Dolphy Room|A Relaxing Virtual Space Where You Can Raise And Interact With Your Own Dolphy.|Scene/Entitlement|Hudson Entertainment, Inc.|HDK_1.3.6.22.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
2A90AC9C-35EE4A9D-B9C2DA00-7B5BB1E8|Name|Desc|Paris Clock Tower Apartment|Take A European Vacation Without Ever Leaving Your Living Room! Enjoy A Beautiful Parisian Vista From The Luxury Of Your Loft Style Apartment Located In An Old Clock Tower.|Scene/Entitlement|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.41.0.37.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
2B21B916-5CA84F03-B40C2539-4AD5B055|Name|Desc|Paradise At Sea Clubhouse|Explore The Seven Seas In Style Aboard The Grandiose Paradise At Sea Clubhouse. With Both A Pool And Hot Tub Located At The Bow Of The Ship, Youll Never Tire Of The Soft Summer Rays Giving You That Perfect Tan. Better Yet, Grab A Drink At The Bar Inside And Enjoy The Day From The Comfort Of Your Own Window Side Booth. The Paradise At Sea Is A Clubhouse Where Everyone Is Invited To Join.|Scene/Entitlement|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.66.0.144.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
2B2AC754-5DA64B09-BC99CE7E-00D37FEF|Name|Desc|Blueprint: Home|Blueprint: Home Is An Apartment That You Can Design, Build And Customise. You Can Tailor Each Aspect Of Your Apartment Including The Walls, Ceilings, Floors, Outer Walls, Windows, Doorways, Room Sizes And Positions, Environment And Skies, As Well As Place Fantastic Feature Items In Any Rooms You Like. Purchasing This Apartment Will Give You Access To The Following Content: /n/n * Blueprint: Home (Apartment) /n * Blueprint: Home - Minimalist Style Pack /n * Blueprint: Home - Classic Paint Style Pack /n * Blueprint: Home - Idyllic Valley Environment /n * Blueprint: Home - Paradise Island Environment /n * Blueprint: Home - Blue Sky /n * Blueprint: Home - Dusky Purple Sky /n/n ※ All Of The Above Items Will Become Available In Blueprint: Home Once Purchased. Additional Content Sold Separately.|Scene/Entitlement|NDreams|HDK_1.65.0.139.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
2BB4A258-50C94E43-B9FF7F58-1D122B23|kName|kDesc|The London Pub|Located In London, England, The Pub Comes With Its Own Fantastic Darts Game And High Score Tables, Working Beer Pumps And A Bunch Of Hidden Surprises And Rewards. Cheers!|Scene/Entitlement|VEEMEE|HDK_1.3.2.16.BETA1|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
2CAEDC62-04CF4895-9C54E738-35EBB888|kName|kDesc|LOOT™'s Space Apartment (Plugged-in)|Enjoy The Luxury Of The Future With This Three-story Apartment With Loft. Experience The Expansive Views Of Earth, Space And The LOOT™ Space Station. Watch Jellyfish Swim In The Two-story Aquarium Located In The Centre Of The Apartment. Relax In The Aquatic Meditation Environment Located On The Bottom Level. This Wonderful Personal Space Is Also Equipped With Your Own Space Apartment Remote Access (S.A.R.A.). With S.A.R.A.s Help You Can: View Up To 5 Different Twitter Feeds On A News Ticker And Choose Out Of 8 Screen Locations To View Your LOOT EOD. S.A.R.A.s Also Lets You Control Your Environment With Retractable Ceiling, Automated Blinds And Dynamic Lighting Options. In Space, You Couldnt Ask For A Better Friend.|Scene/Entitlement|© 2012 LOOT™. All Rights Reserved.|HDK_1.60.0.450.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
2CF5180D-20B04572-BB17FFC4-D452FAB6|kName|kDesc|Aurora Island|Your Very Own Slice Of Aurora - It Is A Place To Relax And Contemplate. Well, When Aurora Isn't Under Attack!|Scene/Entitlement|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.41.0.37.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
2D6DFF7D-8DF84C06-9068E13C-AA514C49|Name|Desc|Crystal Seashores Apartment|Crystal Seashores Is A Lavish Waterfront Home Meant For Those With Extravagant Lifestyles. A Split Staircase, Open Foyer, And Backyard Swimming Pool Are Just Footnotes When Compared To The Ocean View This Home Has To Offer. Reward Yourself And Your Friends With The Exclusive Crystal Seashores Palm Tree, Only Available In The Crystal Seashores Apartment.|Scene/Entitlement|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
2D711676-E22C47FA-9AA3389B-7198F92E|kName|kDesc|CubicResidence|A Room On The Northwest Side Of The Cube-shaped Apartment Adjacent To Home Square. The Calm Sea And Soft Sunlight Spreading Out Below, And The Calm Room Decorated With Trees And Stones Are Different From The Bustle Of The Square, And Will Help You Have A Good Time With Your Friends.|Scene/Entitlement|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.41.0.37.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
2E4992AD-AB924F85-829E80E8-CEB34064|Name|Desc|Post Apocalypse Apartment|Part Apartment, Part Fortress, This Home Will Protect You From The Hazards Of The Outside World.|Scene_Entitlement|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_XX|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
2E7DCB48-B61C4304-AEF5532F-049E07AC|Name|Desc|Paradise At Sea Apartment|Explore The Seven Seas In Style Aboard The Grandiose Paradise At Sea Apartment. With Both A Pool And Hot Tub Located At The Bow Of The Ship, Youll Never Tire Of The Soft Summer Rays Giving You That Perfect Tan. Better Yet, Grab A Drink At The Bar Inside And Enjoy The Day From The Comfort Of Your Own Window Side Booth.|Scene/Entitlement|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.66.0.144.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
2E962339-5B474D6B-B5330518-E9C24241|kName|kDesc|The Dream Yacht Clubhouse|Have The Lifestyle You Always Dreamed Of With The Dream Yacht From Figment. Three Decks Of Opulent Living, Two Hot Tubs And 10 Collectable Rewards, Plus An Exclusive Commerce Point Only Available Through The Dream Yacht. Live The Dream!|Scene/Entitlement|Lockwood|HDK_1.83.0.11.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
2F08E187-A7EA4DD7-858B2968-C769DA9C|Name|Desc|Silicon Lounge|This Magical Party Space Is The Perfect Solution To All Your Entertaining Needs. Set In A Secret Desert Location, The Silicon Lounge Contains Everything You Need To Host Parties the Likes Of Which PlayStation®Home Has Never Seen. Make A Statement In This Neon Paradise, Show Off Your Moves On The Interactive Animated Hexagonal Dance Floor Or Surprise Your Friends With Luxurious Gifts From The Integrated Lockwood Gift Machine.  And When Youre All Partied Out, Relax In The Spaces Hidden Underground Chill-out Snug – If You Can Find It That Is!|Scene/Entitlement|Lockwood Publishing|HDK_1.52.0.2.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
2F2DD20F-59284CB3-96234BB3-22CD5793|Name|Desc|The Ranch House|Welcome To Your Very Own Ranch Where The Sun Never Sets. This Huge Plot Of Land Comes With An Open Paddock, A Peaceful Pond, A Spacious House For You To Rest At After A Long Day At Red Rock Springs.|Scene/Entitlement|Digital Leisure Inc.|HDK_1.82.0.17.PUB|AUTO-REWARD|Res:0
30354DAC-F0A44FCC-89C8621E-003A9BDA|kName|kDesc|Dream Island Clubhouse|Live The Life You Always Dreamed Of With Dream Island From Figment. Your Very Own Secluded Tropical Island Hideaway. Swim In The Ocean, Find The Hidden Cave And Discover The Island's Vibrant Wildlife To Obtain Rewards. Invite Friends To Visit You At The Island's Impressive Condo Or Host A Barbecue On Your Private Pier. Live The Dream!|Scene/Entitlement|Lockwood|HDK_1.83.0.11.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
304C0815-FC6546CD-932AF75D-15373378|kName|kDesc|Dream Hideaway Clubhouse|Enjoy The Splendour Of This Exquisite Woodland Hideaway And Relax In The Luxurious Surroundings . You'll Also Be Able To Collect 8 Exclusive Reward Items, So Why Not Treat Yourself Today?|Scene/Entitlement|Lockwood|HDK_1.83.0.11.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
31175539-761C4388-B4EFB946-1B8E4928|kName|kDesc|Penthouse In The City Of Flowers -From The Window Of The World-|Your Apartment Penthouse Is Located In The City Center Of Paris, Almost In The Center Of The Eiffel Tower And Arc De Triomphe. Life In Paris, The City Of Flowers, Starts Here.|Scene/Entitlement|Granzella Inc.|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
316889B7-88BC4064-9641C189-6F0FC67E|kName|kDesc|The Windmill Apartment|The Windmill Apartment From NDreams Is The Perfect Picturesque Setting If You Enjoy Peace And Quiet. Surrounded By Green Fields And Great Views From The Top Of The Windmill, This Is The Perfect Home Away From Home In PlayStation®Home.|Scene/Entitlement|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
33229FDB-120042BB-8B13026E-4CD7EBF0|Name|Desc|Dream Island|Live The Life You Always Dreamed Of With Dream Island From Figment. Your Very Own Secluded Tropical Island Hideaway. Swim In The Ocean, Find The Hidden Cave And Discover The Island's Vibrant Wildlife To Obtain Rewards. Invite Friends To Visit You At The Island's Impressive Condo Or Host A Barbecue On Your Private Pier. Live The Dream!|Scene/Entitlement|Lockwood|HDK_1.65.0.139.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
33B5B837-145C43C9-B5DEC937-2846B10E|Name|Desc|French Chateau|Enjoy The Summer In Your New French Chateau. This Stunning Chateau Has A Giant Foyer And Balcony, Where You Can Bask In The Light From Your Chandelier. But The Real Jewel Is Out Back. Take A Leisurely Stroll In The Courtyard, Complete With A Birdbath Fountain, And Perfectly Manicured Trees And Bushes. All This Natural Beauty May Inspire You To Hang Up Some New Art In Your Not So Humble Abode. Reward Your Guests With A French Chateau Painting, Exclusive To The French Chateau Personal Space.|Scene/Entitlement|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
340CBF11-24864097-97A0991A-65010FF3|Name|Desc|The Dragon's Lair|You've Conquered The Dragon So Why Not Take Up His Lair As Your Own? The Dragon's Lair Is The Perfect Place To Host Your Friends, Show Off Your Rewards Or Simply Relax With Your Riches Surrounding You.|Scene/Entitlement|Digital Leisure|HDK_1.41.0.37.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
3545546E-C5504203-AF3848F9-C892B074|kName|kDesc|Secret Peacekeeping Base, Yuma Café|At A Glance It Appears To Be A Tasteful Coffee Shop, But Behind A Door In The Rear Is A Secret Base For Heroes That Utilize The Most Advanced Science To Battle Evil. Well Then, Let's Defend Our Tranquil Planet Earth From The Clutches Of Evil!|Scene/Entitlement|Granzella Inc.|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
35CBACD7-1AFB4F04-B1556E7B-60B32FD7|kName|kDesc|Winter Wonderland Apartment|Winter Has Arrived So Come And Enjoy The Festive Atmosphere In The Company Of Santa! |Scene/Entitlement|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
36FD3416-11974A8D-84E03132-1EFFE9E9|Name|Desc|Whimsy Hollow|A Fantastical Den Hidden Away In The Hillside, Whimsy Hollow Is A Mystical Place With Exquisite Carved Wood Features, Cosy Roaring Fires, Candlelit Twisting Corridors And, Rumour Has It, Some Interesting Company…|Scene/Entitlement|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|LUA-REWARD|Res:0
3768A4F9-559841DE-A5056F70-E756387F|kName|kDesc|Skyscraper Lounge: Apartment|In The Sleek New Skyscraper Lounge From NDreams, You Can Wind Down And Chill Out In Style!|Scene/Entitlement|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.83.0.11.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
376F1616-D7784F91-AC937178-F9E86626|Name|Desc|Silent Hill: Downpour Diner|This Diner Has Been Abandoned For… Who Knows How Long. Still, There's A Chance I'll Get A Few Answers As To Where I Am If I Look Around.|Scene/Entitlement|Konami|HDK_1.55.0.155.BETA2|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
3777372A-8FD24BAE-B47472C7-9DCBCECA|kName|kDesc|PersonalSpace In Shouei Kingdom|Let's Enjoy Your Personal Life In Shouei Kingdom!!|Scene/Entitlement|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
37D5041F-9D6F44EC-94680913-26991BE0|kName|kDesc|Skyscraper Lounge: Clubhouse|In This Sleek New Skyscraper Lounge From NDreams, You Can Wind Down And Chill Out In Style!|Scene/Entitlement|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.83.0.11.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
3986D071-7E4A4E11-B33CB19C-66006819|kName|kDesc|Serenity Lake|On An Untouched And Mystical Lake Hidden In The Depths Of Eastern Asia, Lies The Floating Serenity Pagoda. The Serenity Pagoda Is Said To Be A Place Of Retreat, Rest And Relaxation. Enveloped By Beautiful Scenery, It Is The Perfect Place For Meditation - Allowing Visitors To Achieve Inner Peace And Clarity Of Mind. Some Even Say That When Mastering The Art Of Meditation, One Can Gain Power Over The Seasons.|Scene/Entitlement|Lockwood|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
3AE42847-9F474798-9F9FC837-6C1CE7F6|kName|kDesc|Blaster's Bay|The Notoriously Addictive TankTop Shooter Is Back In This Awesome Private Bay. Now You Can Gift This Epic Personal Space So Your Friends Can Blast Their Way To High Scores Amongst The Palm Trees, Looming Rock Formations And Stunning Waterfalls, As Well As Unlock 10 Exclusive Rewards.|Scene/Entitlement|Lockwood|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|LUA-REWARD|Res:0
3B88C71A-937445DF-8CAB9275-5F511FAB|kName|kDesc|Sno Valley Personal Garden|It Is A Personal Garden In The Snow Valley Region. The Snowy Landscape All Around And The Huge Waterwheel That Pumps Up Hot Spring Water Are Truly Spectacular. The Wind Blowing In The Valley Waves Red Kites And Flags, And Peaceful Background Music Plays In This Garden For Relaxation.|Scene/Entitlement|MakerXX|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
3C28B7EE-56224884-85D5C5C4-F5D12542|kName|kDesc|My Private Hideaway|Washed Ashore On A Solitary Island In The South Seas.The Blazing Sun, The Quiet Ocean, The Refreshing Breeze. . . Oops! I Built A House On Top Of A Cliff And Even Forgot To Go Home. You Are Now Able To Go To The Southern Island Hideaway From The Back Door Of The Loghouse.|Scene/Entitlement|Granzella Inc.|HDK_1.60.0.450.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
3DA4FDD8-2F134917-91E09ECC-DE8FDC5D|kName|kDesc|Cassie's Dance Studio Apartment|Cassie's Dance Studio Is The Perfect Place To Hang Out If You Want To Work On Your Dance Moves With Your Friends.|Scene/Entitlement|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
3DCA3C46-AAE54E72-BCB30EAC-3F58F795|Name|Desc|Salt Shooter Game|Welcome To The Dedicated Salt Shooter Launch Area. Play The Extreme Sport Of The Future Or Relax And Find Out More About The Advanced Hover Craft Of Sodium.|Scene/Entitlement|Lockwood Publishing|HDK_1.3.6.22.PUB|AUTO-REWARD|Res:0
3E45A335-82644B19-A8330A84-0D8D64EF|kName|kDesc|Acorn Meadows Park Apartment - Night|Your Own Little Private Slice Of Acorn Meadows Park, This Lakeside Garden Apartment Provides The Perfect Place To Relax And Take Time Away From The Main Park Without Leaving The Acorn Meadows Environment: Rewarded In Acorn Meadows Park After Completing Five Specific Tasks; Task 1 Is Only Available To People With The Rank Of Visitor Or Higher; Task 2 Is Only Available To People With The Rank Of Groundkeeper Or Higher; Task 3 Is Only Available To People With The Rank Of Landscaper Or Higher; Task 4 Is Only Available To People With The Rank Of Steward Or Higher; Task 5 Is Only Available To People With The Rank Of Ranger Or Higher.|Scene/Entitlement|VEEMEE|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|LUA-REWARD|Res:0
3E76DA58-66394897-A9F75514-1DC3450B|kName|kDesc|Luxury Glass House|A Marvel Of Modern Architecture, This Waterside Property Boasts An Open, Airy Layout And An Expansive View Of The Bayfront City's Dazzling Skyline. Retreat From The Busyness Of The Business District In This Posh And Plush Property And Live The Luxurious Life Of The PlayStation®Home Elite.|Scene/Entitlement|MakerXX|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|AUTO-REWARD|Res:0
3E9193C5-9D204C8C-A9D4B937-1CE3028B|kName|kDesc|Discotheque|Dance The Night Away In This Stylish Discotheque! Featuring Animated Disco Balls, Spotlights And Lasers, This Vast Underground Night-club Even Contains A Rythm-action Dance Mini-game, With A High-score Leaderboard! Scoring 100,000 Points Will Give You An Exclusive Reward... Whether You Prefer To Challenge Your Friends At The Mini-game, Party On The Animated Illuminated Dance Floor, Sit On The Stools At The Bar, Or Relax On The Comfy Armchairs, This Is The Perfect Place To Invite Your Friends!|Scene/Entitlement|Atom Republic|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
40BEF872-075A45E8-A3133BC4-0885EFFF|kName|kDesc|Assassin's Creed Personal Space|This 15th Century Italian Renaissance-style Mansion Is Where Culture And Art Were Born. Enjoy The Beauty Of Venice's Canals From The Windows Of This Beautifully Decorated Interior, Furnished With Your Choice Of Furnishings.|Scene/Entitlement|Ubisoft|HDK_1.3.6.22.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
42A93F08-A44747F5-BE68CF89-F5F753DC|kName|kDesc|Eden - Primarch's Vigilarium|Personal Space That Recreates The Primarch's Vigilarium From FINAL FANTASY XIII. ©2009, 2010 SQUARE ENIX Co. Ltd. All Rights Reserved. CHARACTER DESIGN: TETSUYA NOMURA|Scene_Entitlement|SQUARE ENIX, INC.|HDK_1.3.2.27.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
44544873-E5DD4EA7-B6C2D5F1-C1E44D87|kName|kDesc|PetrolHead Apartment|Like Cars? Like Workshops? Want To Live In A Workshop Full Of Cars? Then This PetrolHead Apartment Is The Place For You...|Scene/Entitlement|MakerXX|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|AUTO-REWARD|Res:0
44AA58F9-9021454A-A135CE0B-CA42C9C0|kName|kDesc|Original Home Square Apartment|Take A Stroll Down Memory Lane, Take A Left At Nostalgia Avenue And You'll Find Yourself In The Original Home Square!|Scene/Entitlement|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
45809925-D39949AE-8802B4AB-06C7927F|kName|kDesc|SFRGBT!! Tropical Island|Enjoy A Penalty Shoot-out Against The Worlds Greatest Robot Goalkeeper On Your Very Own Tropical Island At Dusk. Comes Complete With Beach Shelter, Roaring Fire And A Boat To Take You Home Again.|Scene/Entitlement|Sony Computer Entertainment Europe|HDK_1.3.6.22.PUB|LUA-REWARD|Res:0
45EB2736-2F2A4883-A2A43927-5ECDAE89|kName|kDesc|Twingate Castle - Apartment|Every Story Has Two Sides, Every Day Has It's Night And Every Soul Has It's Dark Side. What Would Happen If These Two Sides Were Ever Parted, If Magic Entered The Roots Of Your Soul And Divided It Into Two? The Curse Hung In The Air Filling Every Corner Of The Castle. The Splitting Of A Soul In Two, One Side To Hold All That Was Good, Great And Beautiful, The Other Half To Be Filled With The Darkness Of Evil, Bitterness And Hatred. Here Everything Is Light, The Feeling Of Hope And Happiness Is Palpable. But This Is Twingate Castle...|Scene/Entitlement|JAM Games Ltd|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
460E16D8-92DA46C6-8D6C58A8-9C98DF49|Name|Desc|Hollyridge Estate|The Hollyridge Estate Is The Perfect Setting For An Elegant Winter Soiree! This Personal Space Features Classic Victorian Architecture And Design And Also Features Built-in Decorating Options Which Allow You To Create A Festive Atmosphere Without Taking Up Any Furniture Slots! Includes Customizable Wallpaper, A Snowball Fight Minigame And Much More!|Scene/Entitlement|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.82.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
470001DE-5DE441E2-92191DB5-AFBE5141|Name|Desc|Palace Of The Seven Winds|Reign Over Your Own Celestial Paradise With The Palace Of The Seven Winds! Exert Your Influence Over The Heavens Themselves To Alter Time, Break Free Of Your Earthly Shackles And Take To The Skies, Lounge In Your Own Personal Harem-style Apartments, Have Wishes Granted By Your Personal Genie, Unlock Rewards And Much More!|Scene/Entitlement|Juggernaut|HDK_1.65.0.139.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
474309D0-D3274C92-851B8E91-C6E5FD29|Name|Desc|Mount Olympus|Lounge Like The Gods As You Sit Atop The Clouds In Your Very Own Mt. Olympus. Take Your Rightful Place On The Throne, Overlooking Your Impluvium (a Water Basin For You Mortals). Take A Stroll Out Back In Your Peristylium To Catch Some Sun. Make Sure To Have One Of Your Worshippers Pull Up Your Chariot For You When You Leave. Reward Your Guests With A Mount Olympus Bolts (Male Or Female), Exclusive To The Mount Olympus Personal Space.|Scene/Entitlement|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.66.0.144.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
478A6CF0-279E44FC-984B04FB-9E9DDB3E|Name|Desc|GZ Burger|GZ Burger, A Hamburger Shop Neighboring A Large Lake, Is All Yours. The Interior Layout Of The Tables, Chairs, Etc. Is Up To Your Imagination. Create Your Own Unique Restaurant And Invite Your Friends!|Scene/Entitlement|Granzella|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
480ACF30-D0A942A4-9BEA4AFB-D2FD9E96|kName|kDesc|Edo Nagaya|This Personal Space Recreates A Backstreet Housing Complex In Edo, A Town Full Of Humanity. If You Have This Personal Space, You Can Use The Tenement House In The Lounge Oedo: Exterminating Mononoke As A Recovery Base.|Scene/Entitlement|Granzella Inc.|HDK_1.52.0.2.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
48729594-8B3749E5-94E10B2B-D7F5FC82|kName|kDesc|Underwater Apartment|It's Wet Out There.|Scene/Entitlement|VEEMEE|HDK_1.52.0.2.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
4A2E9254-A6A74697-99DFB6C0-8AE9B8F4|kName|kDesc|The Sky Temple Of Fratos|Hail Fratos, May His Spirit Forever Soar As Freely As His Temple In The Sky.|Scene/Entitlement|MakerXX|HDK_1.82.0.17.PUB|AUTO-REWARD|Res:0
4C5B6800-53784D29-82E97926-81326791|kName|kDesc|The Complex 2|This FREE Apartment Is Brought To You By NDreams. Expand Your Complex By Getting Any Or All Of The Additional Rooms. In Doing So, You Won't Only Impress Your Friends With A Great Apartment But You Will Be Rewarded For Your Efforts.|Scene/Entitlement|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|AUTO-REWARD|Res:0
4C747EEE-95E943A7-805DE380-192A19BC|kName|kDesc|The Lost Dam Hideout|Miles From Civilisation And Hidden Deep In A Gorge, This Long-lost Dam Is The Perfect Hideout For Every Aspiring Evil Overlord. The Dark Interior And Bare Rock Set The Mood And The Piranha Pool Adds A Suitable Finishing Touch.|Scene/Entitlement|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_XX|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
4D98A4B0-C2764E1C-ACFE4AC0-A6EEF079|Name|Desc|Savage Manor|Enter If You Dare! This Tormented Manor Is Steeped In Grim History, History That Will Not Remain In The Past. Explore This Mysterious Apartment, But Beware Of The Dangers That Lurk Within. Can You Solve The Cryptic Riddles And Learn The Horrible Truths Ingrained Within The Structure's Living, Breathing Walls?|Scene/Entitlement|NDreams|HDK_1.65.0.139.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
4DC44A96-5F144552-AAE14084-DCADF52C|kName|kDesc|Glittering Sands Secluded Retreat|Spend Your Holiday On A Luxurious Private Beach. The Clear Blue Sea, The White Sandy Beach, And The Cottage On The Ocean Are All Yours. With A Friend, Or With That Special Someone. Your Holiday Has Just Begun.|Scene/Entitlement|Granzella Inc.|HDK_1.60.0.450.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
4E6D5E1C-63344770-9F8DA724-787852C1|kName|kDesc|Tearoom, Silver Monastery|The Luxurious And Gorgeous Silver Tearoom.Among The Trees One Can See A Sparkling Silver Figure, Said To Take Your Breath Away. In This Mountain Region Far Removed From Civilization, You Can Spend Some Time With A Cup Of Tea, Cut Off From Everyday Life. * A Present From GZ Gift|Scene/Entitlement|Granzella Inc.|HDK_1.82.0.17.PUB|LUA-REWARD|Res:0
50AAE898-56A14A4E-9180833A-CC23F684|Name|Desc|Assassins Creed Apartment|Take Time Out And Relax In The Birthplace Of Culture And Art, 15th Century Italy. Place Your Treasured Possessions Within A Luxurious Venice Apartment Overlooking The Famous Canals.|Scene/Entitlement|Ubisoft|HDK_1.3.5.120.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
51C58101-D61F4968-94D63165-6BDF8575|Name|Desc|Carlas Coffee Shop Apartment|Carla's Coffee Shop Is Located In The Heart Of The City And Is The Perfect Place To Catch Up With Old Friends. With Street Areas And The Coffee Shop To Decorate You Can Make This Apartment Your Own.|Scene/Entitlement|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
5239D680-BC764EF7-8190D476-BBF777E3|Name|Desc|Santorini Greece|Make A Virtual Journey To The Cradle Of Western Civilization And Visit The Archipelago Off Greece's Mainland. Here You'll Live In A Lush Apartment With Spectacular Views Of The Ocean And Surrounding City. Ya Ssou!|Scene_Entitlement|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.3.2.27.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
5352EFD2-44474EFE-9228A02B-696E14DE|kName|kDesc|My Secret Villa On A Blue Whale|Take A Trip Through The Ocean On The Back Of A Whale. Visit Tropical Countries, The Mediterranean, And Even The Northern Fjords. Its Up To You Where You Steer The Gentle Giant As You Enjoy This Relaxing Cruise.|Scene/Entitlement|Granzella Inc.|HDK_1.83.0.11.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
5499749F-4C664A88-99EB2E1C-AD8C8682|kName|kDesc|Go Fish Tropical Island|Now You Can Catch Fish All Day With The Go Fish Tropical Island. This Private Island Gives You Access To All The Fishing You Could Ever Want, Along With Your Own Beach To Relax On.|Scene/Entitlement|VEEMEE|HDK_1.52.0.2.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
55499856-FD83450E-BA301881-E78E3511|Name|Desc|Blaster's Paradise - Sodium Personal Space|Blast Your Way To An Epic Score With The Awesome TankTop Shooter In This Stunning Sub-tropical Personal Space. With Spectacular Waterfalls, A Mysterious Abandoned Mill, And The Addictive TankTop Shooter, This Waterside Hang-out Will Be The Envy Of All Your Friends.|Scene/Entitlement|Lockwood Publishing|HDK_1.41.0.37.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
55BA0B8C-00C343C2-A44722EA-7A6276F0|kName|kDesc|The Aurora Chinatown Apartment|Welcome To Chinatown - A Cool New Apartment Space From NDreams! Hang Out In Chinatown Square, Or Shelter From The Rain In The Surrounding Building.|Scene/Entitlement|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|AUTO-REWARD|Res:0
55DAF48F-0E0F4DC8-85FFFDD1-C4B840B0|kName|kDesc|MotorStorm® Monument Valley Camp|Take Time Out From All The Racing And Partying To Enjoy The Festival From Afar In Your Mesa-top Campsite.|Scene/Entitlement|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.3.0.292.CORE|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
57471F09-3E894539-820CB5B7-F79427E5|Name|Desc|French Chateau Apartment|Enjoy The Summer In Your New French Chateau. This Stunning Chateau Has A Giant Foyer And Balcony, Where You Can Bask In The Light From Your Chandelier. But The Real Jewel Is Out Back. Take A Leisurely Stroll In The Courtyard, Complete With Perfectly Manicured Trees And Bushes. All This Natural Beauty May Inspire You To Hang Up Some New Art In Your Not So Humble Abode. Reward Your Guests With A French Chateau Painting, Exclusive To The French Chateau Personal Space.|Scene/Entitlement|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
57C7E33B-09E8429D-AEE20B44-2BB36885|Name|Desc|Novus Prime Officer's Quarters|These Large Private Suites Are Normally Reserved For High-ranking Officers Of The Earth Fleet. Civilians And Pilots Alike May Now Claim Their Own Piece Of The Novus Prime Space Station, At Least Until These Suites Run Out! Space Is Available To Install Your Own Hangar For Your Fighter Ships, Which Allows You To Play Missions With Your Guests! You May Also Install A Zero-gravity Simulation System, Which Allows Occupants To Safely Float About The Quarters.|Scene/Entitlement|Hellfire Games, Inc.|HDK_1.41.0.37.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
5906DD8F-737A47DE-B802C96A-6DF7C91F|kName|kDesc|GZ Burger|GZ Burger, A Hamburger Shop Neighbouring A Large Lake, Is All Yours. The Interior Layout Of The Tables, Chairs, Etc. Is Up To Your Imagination. Create Your Own Unique Restaurant And Invite Your Friends!|Scene/Entitlement|Granzella Inc.|HDK_1.60.0.450.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
5A0A211B-BCF140BC-95B299C9-63E272A1|Name|Desc|Hollywood Hills House Daytime Estate (with Home Theatre)|Live Like A Celebrity With A Mansion In The Hollywood Hills, Set Above The LA Skyline. Invite Your Friends Into Your Home Theatre For A Social Viewing Experience With Videos, Trailers And Exclusive Content From Sony Pictures! Features Include: • Built-in Entertainment On Demand Theatre System; • A Swimming Feature For The Infinity Pool! THIS Is The Estate To Own If You Want To Relax In The Lap Of Luxury With Your Friends. Purchase Of This Estate Comes Bundled With The LOOT™ Active Camera And Active Light, So You Can Film Your Parties And Upload Them To YouTube At No Extra Cost! PLEASE READ: Due To Contractual And Rights Agreements, All Content May Not Be Available In All Countries. Content Availability Is Dependent On The Geolocation Of The Device. CRACKLE Content Is Only Available In US, CA, UK, And AU. RADIOIO Is Only Available In US And CA. Only One LOOT™ TV Or LOOT™ Radio Can Be Active At A Time.|Scene/Entitlement|© LOOT™|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
5A752F63-4E594ABD-92198D9F-B9B76D95|Name|Desc|Iron Fusion Vault (Female)|Hidden In A Top Secret Location, This Vault Is Filled With A Collection Of New Suits From Iron Fusion, Each With Their Own Individual Mechanics. The Iron Fusion Vault Holds The Secrets To Metering Out Swift Justice In PlayStation®Home. Upon Entering The Iron Fusion Vault, The Owner Will Be Awarded Mechjet – Glory Plus Four Special Suits: Panthabot – Teigra, Mechjet – Ferruma, Mechjet – Ragnara And Mechsuit-Pilot – Necra.|Scene/Entitlement|Lockwood Publishing|HDK_1.82.0.17.PUB|LUA-REWARD|Res:0
5B2EF559-E8374AF5-87026629-DFFF71E8|kName|kDesc|Rock Reveller – Tour Bus|The Time Has Come To Hit The Road And Party. Take Full Advantage Of The Freedoms A Virtual World Provides, Slip The Bus Into Cruise Control And Join The Party At Full Speed! Just Remember… What Goes On Tour, Stays On Tour!|Scene/Entitlement|JAM Games Ltd|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
5B781C33-66164355-9B739FB6-1CCF9935|kName|kDesc|Yutakanapa-sonaruteien|Additional Personal Gardens In The Palais Region. More Gardening Plans Are Available, Giving You More Freedom To Plant Your Planters. The Images Are Gardening Examples.|Scene/Entitlement|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.66.0.144.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
5BA0F3EF-B5544C37-8EF92B93-D88104A6|kName|kDesc|Relaxing Edo Bathhouse|A Relaxing Atmosphere For Body And Soul. Invite A Friend, Take A Soak Together In The Soothing Waters, And Watch The Days Fatigue Melt Away.|Scene/Entitlement|Granzella Inc.|HDK_1.83.0.11.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
5BB02C61-61E4416D-80139E4E-CC304332|Name|Desc|My Private Hideaway|Washed Ashore On A Solitary Island In The South Seas. The Blazing Sun, The Quiet Ocean, The Refreshing Breeze, Crap! I Built A House On Top Of A Cliff And Even Forgot To Go Home. You Are Now Able To Go To The Southern Island Hideaway Lounge From The Back Door Of The Loghouse. Also, There Are Plans To Add Many Different Things To This Personal Space In The Future.|Scene/Entitlement|Granzella|HDK_1.55.0.155.BETA2|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
5D57E32E-08D0452A-92DC2D8E-BDFB2BB8|NAME|DESC|Example|Some Awesome Example Object|Scene/Entitlement|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_XX|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
5D82E79C-0CCB4E90-B54CCF32-46A9ED3C|kName|kDesc|Onlong Apartment No.2 Sukimasou|Quadruple Room, No Bath, Shared Toilet. The Property Is Conveniently Located Near The Downtown Area.|Scene/Entitlement|Granzella Inc.|HDK_1.55.0.155.BETA2|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
5E6B7DED-B70F4833-B3F67A2B-FB94509E|kName|kDesc|SFRGBT!! Tropical Island|Enjoy A Penalty Shoot-out Against The Worlds Greatest Robot Goalkeeper On Your Very Own Tropical Island At Dusk. Comes Complete With Beach Shelter, Roaring Fire And A Boat To Take You Home Again.|Scene/Entitlement|Sony Computer Entertainment Europe|HDK_1.3.6.22.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
5FC308F5-5D544E46-9287847C-4A0078A6|kName|kDesc|Acorn Meadows Park Apartment - Dusk|Your Own Little Private Slice Of Acorn Meadows Park, This Lakeside Garden Apartment Provides The Perfect Place To Relax And Take Time Away From The Main Park Without Leaving The Acorn Meadows Environment.|Scene/Entitlement|VEEMEE|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
60DFBAF1-2723455C-A8E4012C-39622F1A|Name|Desc|Bonk Living Space|A Personal Space Built In The Primitive Age Of Bonk! Light Up The Room With Primitive Light, And Liven Things Up With Primitive Furniture Like What Can Be Found In The River.* Primitive Furniture Can Only Be Used In This Personal Space.|Scene/Entitlement|Hudson Entertainment, Inc.|HDK_1.41.0.37.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
612B9AF4-41DF4DF4-91D43911-5BC43776|kName|kDesc|Gnome Curling Secret Garden|Enjoy Gnome Curling In The Privacy Of Your Own Secret Garden. Comes Complete With A Gazebo, Beautiful Floral Displays And A Magical Door To Take You Back Home Again.|Scene/Entitlement|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.52.0.2.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
6130BCEB-DF5E4516-B8C75022-9FB2A72D|Name|Desc|The Space Station Clubhouse|The Space Station Needs A Crew, And You've Been Selected To Take Part In An All New Out-of-this-world Experience. Your Space Station Adventure Will Have You Defending Your New Home Against Incoming Asteroids In The Fully Interactive Station Defense Turret Center. On Top Of Defending The Station Your Tasks Will Also Include Lowering And Raising The External Shutters So You Don't Get Blinded By The Sun And You'll Even Have To Evacuate The Garbage You Produce In To The Vaccum Of Space. Your Shuttle Is Cleared For Arrival. The Space Station Space Is A Clubhouse Where Everyone Is Invited To Join.|Scene/Entitlement|Digital Leisure|HDK_1.65.0.139.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
613EE2EA-13614183-84BE1DC4-C28E08E9|kName|kDesc|Castle Strakh|For Centuries, Castle Strakh Has Been The Subject Of Tales And Superstition Amongst The Local People. Some Say The Castle Is Haunted By The Ghostly Bride Of Count Strakh, Others That It Hides A Secret Lab Used For Horrific Experiments. Do You Dare Seek Out The Truth? Contains 11 Ghastly Rewards And LKWD Life XP.|Scene/Entitlement|Lockwood|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
62BFAA70-6F5E4CA3-A72CA190-9EEEE57A|Name|Desc|Creek Falls|Hidden Deep Within The Forest, Creek Falls Sits Neatly Atop A Stunning Waterfall. The Home Is Built Like A Modern Day Studio With A Living Room, Bedroom, And Kitchen Space All Packed Into One Large Open Space. You Can Even Hang Out With Friends In Your Outdoor Patio And Breathe In The Soft Chilly Wind Of The Autumn Air.|Scene/Entitlement|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
62D9786D-6F71409E-BA150B8F-E6193FD1|kName|kDesc|Luxury Lighthouse Apartment|The NDreams Luxury Lighthouse Apartment Is Spread Across Multiple Floors And Comes Complete With Authentic Rotating Light Effect. Situated On A Picturesque Cliffside This Is The Perfect Get Away.|Scene/Entitlement|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.82.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
63801336-05774A92-8A828112-F6C27832|kName|kDesc|Mystery Key - (#3 Of 3)|This Mystery Key Is Only For The Most Sophisticated Home User. Collect All Three.|Scene_Entitlement|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.65.0.139.BETA|AUTO-REWARD|Res:0
63CF2B03-EA0C4269-8E71A6C9-05740A62|Name|Desc|Tycoon Penthouse|Take Your Living Experience To New Heights With The Tycoon Penthouse, Perched High Above The City Sky. The Window-walled Space Comes With Your Own Private Helipad, An Aquarium That Reaches From Floor To Ceiling, And A Spiralling Staircase That Gives The Space Its Modern Design. Dare To Defy Gravity And Add This Little Slice Of Heaven To Your Collection Today.|Scene/Entitlement|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.52.0.2.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
63F65BB0-4AE342F7-A594A4C8-1D9BCD37|kName|kDesc|Castle Greywold: Apartment|In This New Apartment, You Can Take Up Arms In The Training Yard, Entertain Guests In The Audience Chamber, Or Survey Your Surroundings From The Castle Ramparts.|Scene/Entitlement|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
647239EE-F62E4308-8ED120B5-0889812F|Name|Desc|Zombie DeadQuarters|If We Zombies Have Offended, Think But This, And All Is Mended, That You Have But Slumber'd Here, While These Corpses Did Appear.|Scene_Entitlement|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.3.0.125.BETA1|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
6480F726-67B14578-B068C0B6-977AF7E0|Name|Desc|The Nightmare Yacht|The Dream Has Become A Nightmare. This Once Opulent Yacht Has Gone To Wrack And Ruin. Experience The Eerie Surroundings For Yourself And Discover Some Wicked Rewards. Board This Cursed Vessel At Your Own Peril, You Have Been Warned…|Scene/Entitlement|Lockwood Publishing|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
654FC63A-E0D4425A-9E024BDF-6244588C|kName|kDesc|Snow Globe Clubhouse|Ever Shook A Snow Globe And Gazed Inside Wanting To Be A Part Of That Magical, Miniature World? Now This Can Be A Virtual Reality With Our Snow Globe Clubhouse, Set On A Table Inside The Jam Jar, The Outside World Is Visible And Giant! Live The Magic And Feel The Snow Because After All….. Theres Snow Place Like PlayStation®Home!|Scene/Entitlement|JAM Games Ltd|HDK_1.82.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
65658D4A-1D7D46CD-9B99B056-639DB504|Name|Desc|Dream Hideaway|Gift This And Let Them Rest And Relax In The Luxury They Have Become Accustomed To.|Scene/Entitlement|Lockwood Publishing|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|LUA-REWARD|Res:0
6631DA43-A58649DE-946D0FDB-771559A7|kName|kDesc|The Haven Of The Skies Clubhouse|The Haven Of The Skies Clubhouse Is A Breathtaking Twilit Environment Full Of Secrets, Intrigue And Adventure. Taking To The Skies On Your Magic Carpet, Collect The Gems That Your Genie Demands So That He May Grant Your Wishes.|Scene/Entitlement|Lockwood|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
66668980-84934292-B08BDFA2-ED15A0ED|kName|kDesc|LKWDvenue|The Perfect Location For Social Events! Create The Ultimate Event At LKWD Venues! Interactive Points Of Interest With Unique Animations, Options To Customize The Venues, And Mini-games To Play.|Scene/Entitlement|Lockwood|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
67C5004E-BDB44973-8F939FCC-736ACA6A|Name|Desc|Hollywood Hills House Nighttime Clubhouse (with Home Theatre)|Entertain Like An Industry Mogul In This Ultimate Clubhouse, Set In The Hollywood Hills Above The LA Skyline! Invite Your Friends Into Your Home Theater For A Social Viewing Experience With Videos, Trailers And Exclusive Content From Sony Pictures! Features Include: • Built-in Entertainment On Demand Theater System; • A Swimming Feature For The Infinity Pool! THIS Is Where The Party Is For You And Your Club. Purchase Of This Clubhouse Comes Bundled With The LOOT™ Active Camera And Active Light, So You Can Film Your Parties And Upload Them To YouTube At No Extra Cost! PLEASE READ: Due To Contractual And Rights Agreements, All Content May Not Be Available In All Countries. Content Availability Is Dependent On The Geolocation Of The Device. CRACKLE Content Is Only Available In US, CA, UK, And AU. RADIOIO Is Only Available In US And CA. Only One LOOT™ TV Or LOOT™ Radio Can Be Active At A Time.|Scene/Entitlement|© LOOT™|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
6824D17D-B8914335-B4DB951B-9E9ED17A|kName|kDesc|All Spaces SeaClyff|You Save Big By Getting Both The Retreat And The Clubhouse For One Price. * SeaClyff Retreat * SeaClyff Clubhouse * Pulp Music Radio|Scene_Entitlement|Game Mechanics|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
690AF86B-98B54E59-8418C715-1967C200|kName|kDesc|Musicality Club House|A Unique Live Music Venue Perfect For Hosting Club Gatherings. Up To Four Players Can Grab An Instrument And Jam/compete Against Other Club Members. Comes Complete With All Music Packs - Dance, Rock And RnB. Please Note, In Order To Access This Club House You Will Need To Have Purchased The Club House Slot From Either The Estates Store Or The Clubs Menu (available In Options).|Scene/Entitlement|NDreams|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
69845EF2-D5D04D79-9A966CC3-3F250217|kName|kDesc|921 Acacia Drive|Live The Suburban Dream At 921 Acacia Drive! With A Range Of Rooms For You To Decorate To Suit Your Tastes, Along With 8 Daily Reward Items That Give You The Essential Furniture Items, This Personal Space Is A Bonafide Slice Of Americana!|Scene/Entitlement|Lockwood|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
69A74FBA-B57F4C85-9DC55CC4-4A638116|kName|kDesc|Dolphy Room|A Private Space Floating In Virtual Space. It Is Equipped With A Function For Raising A Virtual Pet Dolphy. Spend A Healing Time With Dolphy.|Scene/Entitlement|Hudson Soft Co. Ltd.|HDK_1.3.6.22.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
6BCDE1C1-8F5F443F-8037F3DE-884DB7E5|kName|kDesc|Mystery Key - (#1 Of 3)|This Mystery Key Will Help Complete Your Luxury Mansion. Collect All Three.|Scene_Entitlement|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.65.0.139.BETA|AUTO-REWARD|Res:0
6C0884FA-6926419B-ABD4F676-9B4BBEF8|Name|Desc|Playstation®Home Mansion - Infinity Pool|Boasting A Generous Outdoor Patio, This Lavish Waterfront Backyard Comes Complete With Two Fireplaces, A Marble Bar, And Gold Statues Overlooking Your Own Private Wishing Fountain. Combine This With A Large, Glass-walled, Infinity Pool That Looks Out Into The Oceans Horizon And You Have The Perfect Backyard For Any Social Get-together Or Simply A Relaxing Afternoon.|Scene/Entitlement|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.55.0.155.BETA2|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
6D1C1ADC-76F74336-AD27C552-37741553|kName|kDesc|Rooftop Terrace - Apartment|What Better Place Than A Rooftop Terrace To Host A Social Gathering. Impress Your Friends With The Beautiful View Of A Bustling City At Night.|Scene/Entitlement|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
6E24A0D3-8E8F445C-AC1A6EC3-4CEB8C5E|kName|kDesc|Snow Globe Apartment|Ever Shook A Snow Globe And Gazed Inside Wanting To Be A Part Of That Magical, Miniature World? Now This Can Be A Virtual Reality With Our Snow Globe Apartment, Set On A Table Inside The Jam Jar, The Outside World Is Visible And Giant! Live The Magic And Feel The Snow Because After All….. Theres Snow Place Like PlayStation®Home!|Scene/Entitlement|JAM Games Ltd|HDK_1.82.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
6E647276-545E4D28-AAAA9E6F-1A1CB609|kName|kDesc|Fossil Museum|In This Personal Space, The Fossils That You Found In The Southern Island Hideaway Lounge Are Exhibited.|Scene/Entitlement|Granzella Inc.|HDK_1.60.0.450.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
718EF515-7FC74C5E-875D9570-DF8ED2E1|kName|kDesc|The Irish Pub|A Special St. Patrick's Day Themed Version Of The London Pub, Complete With Darts Game, So You Can Enjoy Good Times And Great Craic With Your Friends.|Scene/Entitlement|VEEMEE|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
722A16BB-D0E94623-B85F5D92-6D95FBC6|Name|Desc|Island Bungalow Clubhouse|Nestled On The Edge Of A Tropical Paradise, This Exquisite Island Bungalow Is Hidden Somewhere On An Uncharted Coastline. Be The First To Explore This Mysterious Paradise. The Island Bungalow Space Is A Clubhouse Where Everyone Is Invited To Join.|Scene/Entitlement|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.55.0.155.BETA2|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
727DCA6F-16284020-B63B3206-3DD44797|kName|kDesc|Pirate Galleon Apartment|Moored By A Tropical Island, This Ship Comes Complete With Playable Cannon Mini-game And Four Pirate Themed Furniture Rewards. A Very Desirable Residence That Has Suddenly Become Available, Due To The Imprisonment Of The Previous Owner.|Scene/Entitlement|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.3.6.22.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
7308A166-0FDF49B6-902932EB-98F72101|kName|kDesc|Stately Home Clubhouse (Gothic)|The Stately Home (Gothic) Is The Perfect Clubhouse For Those People Who Like The Finer Things In Life With A Slightly Darker Twist. With Its Large And Beautiful Grounds And A Direct Link Through To The Masquerade Ball - The Ballroom (Gothic) Clubhouse, This Space Is A Must-have. Also Comes With Five Free Rewards.|Scene/Entitlement|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.82.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
73C463E7-CF9D4F10-8CE45CD6-5B0B6876|Name|Desc|Raven Barracks|Located In An Equatorial Rain Forest, The Raven Barracks Is Your Little Slice Of Paradise. Youll Enjoy The Ancient Ruins, Native Birds, And Beautiful Flora Fortified By Composite Fiber Barricades, A Seismic Sensor Grid And Your Elite Raven Sentry Detachment.|Scene/Entitlement|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.3.6.22.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
7471B411-654D49D4-BD5114B7-FD3AC461|Name|Desc|Sunlit Meadow|This Dappled Glade Is The Ultimate Chilled Out Place To Relax And Unwind Surrounded By Nature. It's The Gift Of Tranquility.|Scene/Entitlement|MakerXX|HDK_1.65.0.139.BETA|LUA-REWARD|Res:0
74A41EF1-34A34069-A61827E4-6E81B49B|kName|kDesc|Audi S1 Sledge Multiplayer|Jump Onto An Audi S1 Sledge And Race Down The Mountainside Against Up To 5 Other Players, With A Chance To Win Rewards.|Scene/Entitlement|MakerXX|HDK_1.41.0.37.PUB|AUTO-REWARD|Res:0
7567599C-D61943AC-85484641-4E0BAD41|Name|Desc|The Casino: Keys To The VIP|Please Enjoy Your Stay At Paradise Springs. Compliments Of The Manager.|Scene/Entitlement|Digital Leisure, Inc.|HDK_1.51.0.60.PUB|AUTO-REWARD|Res:0
75783053-9111436E-8392BF8D-08261140|kName|kDesc|Twingate Castle - Clubhouse|Every Story Has Two Sides, Every Day Has It's Night And Every Soul Has It's Dark Side. What Would Happen If These Two Sides Were Ever Parted, If Magic Entered The Roots Of Your Soul And Divided It Into Two? The Curse Hung In The Air Filling Every Corner Of The Castle. The Splitting Of A Soul In Two, One Side To Hold All That Was Good, Great And Beautiful, The Other Half To Be Filled With The Darkness Of Evil, Bitterness And Hatred. Here Everything Is Light, The Feeling Of Hope And Happiness Is Palpable. But This Is Twingate Castle...|Scene/Entitlement|JAM Games Ltd|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
75888605-DB6B48E5-A7C40AD2-FDB82BED|kName|kDesc|The Jam Jar Apartment|The Jam Jar Was Established In The 1940s As THE Place To Go. Discover The Opulence And Grandeur Of This By Gone Era In A Building Rescued And Restored To Its Rightful Glory! Whether You Decide To Return It To It's Full Boutique Status, Use It's Exquisite Detail As A Backdrop For A Gallery Or As The Venue Of The Latest Fashion Event, The Jam Jar Will Still Prove To Be THE Place To Be Seen!|Scene/Entitlement|JAM Games Ltd|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
75E617D1-009C43FC-9AB56ADD-D7576B29|kName|kDesc|The War Room Clubhouse|The War Room - Perfect For Clan Meetings, Socialising And Plotting World Domination. You And Your Fellow Warmongerers Can Have Your Face And Commands Displayed On Large Screens Throughout This High Tech Facility.|Scene/Entitlement|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
761FD538-4E7E4375-A790B998-DB54D141|kName|kDesc|Edo Row Houses|This Personal Space Re-creates The Collective Residences On The Back Streets In The Humantiy-overflowing Edo Period. If You Own This Personal Space, You Can Use Operation: Defend Edo Row Houses As A Recovery Spot.|Scene/Entitlement|Granzella Inc.|HDK_1.60.0.450.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
76E14D67-7A954149-8BB56D4D-7107138D|kName|kDesc|Go Fish Tropical Island|Now You Can Catch Fish All Day With The Go Fish Tropical Island. This Private Island Gives You Access To All The Fishing You Could Ever Want, Along With Your Own Beach To Relax On.|Scene/Entitlement|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.52.0.2.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
76FD6E8D-2CC74DE1-B944B36A-36BF7B7E|Name|Desc|Cutteridge Estate - Clubhouse|Unlock The Mysteries Of Cutteridge Estate. This Elegant Victorian Estate Is Rumored To Be The Final Resting Place Of Many Dark And Depraved Souls. Do You Dare To Venture Into These Forsaken Halls In Search Of The Secrets Which Lie Within?|Scene/Entitlement|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.65.0.139.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
77621C8B-82D14C82-AD9C0A61-65058B25|kName|kDesc|Xi: Continuum - Standalone Vertigo Apartment|This Massive And Fantastical Outdoor Apartment, Situated On The Side Of A Skyscraper Overlooking A Futuristic City, Defies Belief. Note: For Only A Small Amount Extra, Purchase The Xi: Continuum - Axiom Agent Pack In The NDreams Shop And Obtain The Game Version Of This Apartment And Access To Xi: Continuum, The Exciting PlayStation®Home Adventure Game Featuring An Evolving Story, Playable Missions, And Rewards.|Scene/Entitlement|NDreams|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
777FFBC0-7DC641E1-B9B910A4-EB7E2C19|Name|Desc|LOOT™'s Sunset Yacht (With Home Theater)|Watch Live Events, Videos, Podcasts And Exclusive Content In Your Luxurious On-board Theater While Cruising Along In A Beautiful Tropical Lagoon. In Addition, This Upgraded Amaterasu Yacht Now Offers The Ability To Set The Mood Of Your Cruise. Sunrise, Sunset, Day, Night? It's Your Choice! Thrill To Breathtaking Views And Host Exclusive Parties, Or Sit Back And Count The Stars Under The Romantic Moonlight.|Scene/Entitlement|Loot|HDK_1.41.0.37.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
77D9E3EF-02A74DA9-BD77FBBD-91407A88|kName|kDesc|Lakeside Log Cabin|Admire The Stunning Sunset Across A Mountain Lake From This Modern Log Cabin. The Residence Provides Two Large Living Areas With Beautiful Fire Places In Each And Exquisite Lighting Throughout. These Are Elegantly Joined By A Large Decked Area That Takes You Right Up To The Lake Side. Simply Spectacular.|Scene/Entitlement|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_XX|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
784FF69C-35D94E19-A8B4C8A7-9860E27C|Visari Throne Room|Personal apartment using the interior design of the throne room in Visaris palace.|Visari Throne Room|Personal Apartment Using The Interior Design Of The Throne Room In Visaris Palace.|Scene_Entitlement|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_XX|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
78B67FCF-C9B04B9F-8C65591C-6DE4D7F5|Name|Desc|Discotheque Club-house|Dance The Night Away In This Stylish Discotheque! Featuring Animated Disco Balls, Spotlights And Lasers, This Vast Underground Night-club Even Contains A Rythm-action Dance Mini-game, With A High-score Leaderboard! Getting A High Score Will Give You An Exclusive Reward... Whether You Prefer To Challenge Your Friends At The Mini-game, Party On The Animated Illuminated Dance Floor, Sit On The Stools At The Bar, Or Relax On The Comfy Armchairs, This Is The Perfect Place To Invite Your Friends!|Scene/Entitlement|Atom Republic|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
79B5B7FA-84CE4D07-9D5E93A4-4AE7466B|kName|kDesc|LittleBigPlanet™ Pod Penthouse|Your Very Own LittleBigPlanet™ Pod Penthouse. Pod Is Crafted From The Finest Cardboard And The View Is Simply Out Of This World!|Scene_Entitlement|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.3.5.121.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
7AFA88BE-45314740-8A54933B-C3AF08D7|Name|Desc|Las Vegas Suite|This Luxurious Multilevel Suite Overlooks The Endless Hustle And Bustle Of The Las Vegas Strip. From Million Dollar Views Of Sin City's Sprawling Lights To Extravagant Amenities Like The Romantic Rooftop Hot Tub, This Magnificent Residence Is A Must-have Property For PlayStation®Home High-rollers.|Scene/Entitlement|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.65.0.139.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
7B307B85-C2BA4A74-AB35525D-953C473B|kName|kDesc|Ajagara's Peak|Nestled Atop A Steep And Perilous Mountain; Ajagara's Peak Is Only Accessible To A Select Few - Those Known As The Dragon Scouts. A Place For Diligent Training, Scholarly Pursuits And Deep Meditation; The Monastery At Ajagara's Peak Was Founded To Train An Elite Band Of Soldiers Who Keep Watch Over The Kingdom Of Ajagara. With 7 Daily Rewards And The Chance To Catch A Glimpse Of A Tame Dragon, This Truly Is A Unique Personal Space.|Scene/Entitlement|Lockwood|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
7EFFA7A5-52994544-96C5F6F1-E6F4973D|kName|kDesc|Moon Hermitage|Peakvox Ninja This Personal Space Is Based On A Japanese Style Lounge. Owners Of This Hermitage Will Always Receive A 50% Increase In Login Bonuses In This Lounge. Placing The Following Furniture Sets (or Just Possessing Them) Will Further Increase The Login Bonus 25% Additional...Purchasers Of Decorative Japanese Furniture Sets 25% Additional...Purchasers Of Partition Japanese Furniture Sets 20% Additional...Purchasers Of Garden Set (pine) 20% Additional...Purchasers Of Garden Set (bamboo) 30% Additional ...10% Additional For Purchasers Of Garden Stone Sets...10% Additional For Purchasers Of Coolness Set 1...10% Additional For Purchasers Of Coolness Set 2...10% Additional For Purchasers Of Coolness Set 3 Visits To The Peakvox Ninja Lounge And The Benefits Of The Benefits Are Available To Those Who Are 17 Years Of Age Or Older. This Personal Space Can Be Used As A Regular Personal Space By Those Under 17 Years Old.|Scene/Entitlement|O-Two Inc.|HDK_1.66.0.144.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
7F278311-1436452B-8C3EEFC5-5E385977|kName|kDesc|Avalon Keep: Clubhouse|The Wonderous Avalon Keep Is Now An Expansive Clubhouse! Invite Your Friends To Enjoy This Space With All The Same Features As The Personal Space. Any Upgrades You Purchase For The Avalon Keep Will Also Be Reflected In The Clubhouse And Vice Versa. The Avalon Keep Is An Impregnable Fortress On Your Very Own Floating Island. The Magical Crystals Of Avalon Allow The Landmass To Stay Afloat And Power All The New Technological Advances That Have Swept The World Of Avalon. Your Keep Sets You Apart As One Of The Nobility That Have Taken Residence In The Skies Around Avalon. Master All The Mini-games And Share The Wealth With The Latest In Gift Machine Technology. Can You Unlock All The Secrets Of Your Keep? 			- Dragonfly Automaton 			- Gift Machine For Owners And Guests 			- Scavenger Hunts For Owners And Guests 			- Interactive NPCs 			- Crystal Hunter Mini-game 			- Diurnal Controls|Scene_Entitlement|Heavy Water|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
7F30B22F-8E3A43BD-9648EB96-D5514142|kName|kDesc|Loco Island|This Personal Space Is Your Very Own Tropical Island Inhabited By LocoRoco™ Characters. The Tropical Retreat Is Full Of Exciting Activities. Collect Berries That Fall From The Trees, And Communicate With Islanders To Expand The Facilities. Enjoy The Swing, Slide, Jukebox, And Games For Two Players! And The More Time You Spend On Loco Island, The More Vibrant And Exciting The Paradise Becomes! Treat Yourself To This Fun-filled Personal Space!|Scene/Entitlement|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.3.2.27.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
7F332BE1-9450430B-9C153933-9C832F4C|kName|kDesc|Joe's Boxing Gym Apartment|Joe's Boxing Gym Is The Perfect Place To Hang Out If You Want To Work On Your Moves And Learn How To Spit Sawdust.|Scene/Entitlement|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
7FC9B6B1-596D4F72-A590CBA2-F03AE542|Name|Desc|Bramblenook Farm|Relax And Get Back To Nature In This Charming Country Farm. In This Space You Can Raise Plants And Animals To Improve Your Farming Skills. As You Gain Experience, You Will Be Able To Plant New Crops And Raise New Animals. Chop Wood And Level Your Woodworking Skills To Create Furnishings For Yourself Or To Gift To A Guest. Place Crafted Furniture Items In Bramblenook Farm For No Furniture Cost!|Scene/Entitlement|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
809B9144-05674E92-BD6D5478-B199C342|kName|kDesc|Japanese Garden Apartment|Japanese Garden Apartment|Scene/Entitlement|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.82.0.17.PUB|AUTO-REWARD|Res:0
818AA160-AB284BBF-A5286639-9F0635AD|kName|kDesc|Virtua Tennis 4 – Baseline Battle|A Virtua Tennis Court Game. Stop The Robots!|Scene/Entitlement|MakerXX|HDK_1.52.0.2.PUB|LUA-REWARD|Res:0
82B17718-D49A44B2-BD2E5660-0DB9CF49|Name|Desc|The Midnight Glade|A Secluded Glade Under A Moonlit Starry Sky. Gather Around The Solitary Tree And Warm Yourself By The Glow Of The Fire. It's The Perfect Place For A Fireworks Party.|Scene/Entitlement|Lockwood Publishing|HDK_1.55.0.155.BETA2|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
83109FAC-5CAA4F28-8479420A-F44167F8|kName|kDesc|Halloween Tour Bus|The Time Has Come To Hit The Road And Party. Take Full Advantage Of The Freedoms A Virtual World Provides, Slip The Bus Into Cruise Control And Join The Party At Full Speed! Just Remember… What Goes On Tour, Stays On Tour!|Scene/Entitlement|JAM Games Ltd|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
8350F4C2-A07F4B1D-960F693C-4D3DFE72|kName|kDesc|Dream Forest Paradise|Your Dreams Come True With This Breathtaking Deluxe Home Amongst The Trees, A Luxurious Treehouse If You Will. Traverse The Treetop Bridges, Swim In The Lagoon, And Explore Your Lush Surroundings To Obtain Rewards. With A Magnificent View From Every Angle You'll Never Want To Leave The Dream Forest Paradise From Figment. Live The Dream!|Scene/Entitlement|Lockwood|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
83A5ADB5-0D054C1C-B13B25DF-2922892D|kName|kDesc|Acorn Meadows Park Apartment - Rainy Day|Your Own Little Private Slice Of Acorn Meadows Park, This Lakeside Garden Apartment Provides The Perfect Place To Relax And Take Time Away From The Main Park Without Leaving The Acorn Meadows Environment.|Scene/Entitlement|VEEMEE|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
84A3A0AD-E1294E08-9CB56FCA-629625EC|Name|Desc|LKWD Venue|The Perfect Location For All Your Social Events, The Venue Includes: • Interaction Points Allowing You And Your Friends To Utilise Unique Animations • In Depth Customization Options Including Optional Features Like The Stage And The Catwalk • A Voting Minigame • Your Own Personal LKWD Store • An Integrated Lockwood Gift Machine • LKWD Venue Customisation Pack - Lockwood • LKWD Venue Customisation Pack - Hive Be The Ultimate Host With The LKWD Venue.|Scene/Entitlement|Lockwood|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
84C5D818-FA6747DA-ABED498F-2D31FD34|Name|Desc|Seasons-themed Room|A Personal Space To Enjoy The Changing Seasons.|Scene/Entitlement|O-Two Inc.|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
85A014B8-4CAF4A08-B1D163CA-C3CCC6EC|kName|kDesc|Enterprise-D Main Bridge With Attached Captain's Ready Room|Hey Trekkers, The Star Trek Enterprise-D Has Come To PlayStation®Home! You Can Now Get Yourself The Official Main Bridge With The Attached Captain's Ready Room. TM & © 2013 CBS Studios Inc. STAR TREK And All Related Marks And Logos Are Trademarks Of CBS Studios Inc. All Rights Reserved.|Scene/Entitlement|Flashman Studios LLC.|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
865345B3-D99F41D6-8C2E011C-D38E78F1|Name|Desc|Desert Haven|Take A Minute And Unwind At The Charming Desert Haven Clubhouse. Catch A Couple Sun-rays Poolside While Socialising With Friends Or Meeting New Ones. Take A Nap Beneath The Cabanas Or Even Catch A Fireside Chat Next To The Bonfires. The Desert Haven Space Is A Clubhouse Where Everyone Is Invited To Join.|Scene/Entitlement|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.66.0.144.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
86C2621A-CD2949D8-894457FD-13EA3A44|Name|Desc|Andy's Room|Experience Life At A Toys Eye View In Andys Room From Disney/Pixars Toy Story 3.|Scene/Entitlement|Disney|HDK_1.3.6.22.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
86C5657F-0FA8424F-92CEE518-5CE2365F|NAME|DESC|Living Room Stage Set From Loot™|The Living Room Stage Set Provides Home Users The Opportunity To Shout lights, Camera, Action! While Collaborating With Their Friends To Bring Their Own Movies And Television Shows To Life. The Product Comes With Working Lights And Cameras, As Well As Props And Backdrops. Additionally, The Owner Has The Option To Use Any Items That They Already Have Purchased In Home While In The Stage Set. The Living Room Stage Set Is The First Of Many Stage Sets Coming From Your Friends At Loot™.|Scene/Entitlement|Sony Pictures Entertainment|HDK_XX|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
885D7593-F2F74EF9-A83F6DA4-DD68C311|kName|kDesc|The Drey VIP Room (For Male)|You Have Been Cordially Invited To Be A Member Of The Drey VIP Room. Take An Exclusive Look Into The Inspired Fashions Of Drey's Celebrated Designers. The Drey VIP Room Features A Stunning Collection Of Old And New - Everything To Satisfy The Hunger Of The Fashion Elite Worldwide. This Includes 20 Existing Gift Machine Clothing Items And 9 Exclusive New Clothing Items.|Scene/Entitlement|Lockwood|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|LUA-REWARD|Res:0
887D49F8-F15C457E-A8F5EDF2-E542C812|kName|kDesc|Moonlight Space|This Is The Peakvox Ninja Personal Space, Japanese Lounge.|Scene/Entitlement|Otwo|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
88F08C7E-F01C4196-BE2C3F2B-B827C264|Name|Desc|Wizard's Den|Step Into The Wizard's Den Where The Magic And Wonderment Of An Age Long Past Still Remains. Be Mindful Of The Dragons!|Scene_Entitlement|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_XX|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
891B8300-489241A4-BF477018-71451A4A|Name|Desc|Hillside Apartment|Built With A View In Mind, The Hillside Apartment Is The Place To Get Away From The Confines Of A Concrete Jungle And Bask In The Luxury Of A Home Away From Home.|Scene/Entitlement|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.55.0.155.BETA2|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
89DA2EA0-04514A09-B032A631-821B7B4F|Name|Desc|UFC Personal Space|In The UFC Personal Space You Get Your Own Home Gym. Earn Points To Spend In The UFC Octagon To Win Prizes.|Scene/Entitlement|THQ|HDK_1.41.0.37.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
8A790D6D-A195483B-9FEF7FDA-028ED101|Name|Desc|Club Luminosity - Club House|This Is The Ultimate Place To Share Your Love Of Neon. If You Love Things That Glow, Then This Place Is For You!|Scene/Entitlement|Konami Digital Entertainment|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
8ACB24CC-1B7347DD-BD075B7D-28253663|Name|Desc|Secret Peacekeeping Base, Yuma Café|At A Glance It Appears To Be A Tasteful Coffee Shop, But Behind A Door In The Rear Is A Secret Base For Heroes That Utilize The Most Advanced Science To Battle Evil. Well Then, Let's Defend Our Tranquil Planet Earth From The Clutches Of Evil!|Scene/Entitlement|Granzella|HDK_1.82.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
8B3267C9-23514B69-89F32A80-33166AD6|kName|kDesc|Park Clubhouse|Whether You Prefer To Chill Out By The Fountain, Or Dance With Your Friends In The Music Pavilion, There Is Always A Good Reason To Come And Visit This Peaceful Art-déco Public Park! Contains A Go-kart Racing Game, A Rythm-action Game, And The Space Crash Arcade Cabinet. Playing The Games Will Get You Rewards!|Scene/Entitlement|Atom Republic|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
8C481875-B0104DC7-B66A49F3-AA16E177|kName|kDesc|Twilight Lounge|The Luxurious Twilight Lounge Is The Hangout Of The Elite. With Designer Seating, Chic Lighting, A Funky Bar, And Even A Hot Tub This Is The Place To Be Seen!|Scene/Entitlement|Lockwood|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|LUA-REWARD|Res:0
8C92650F-B74C49C9-9D8392D2-F7567CDE|Name|Desc|Cutthroats Hideaway Apartment|The Best Spot From Which To Embark Upon Your Next Swashbuckling Adventure!! No Matter The Plunders You Seek, You And Your Friends Will Have The Time Of Your Life. Check Out The Pirate Ship, Walk The Plank, Shadow Dancing, Play Checkers, Best Your Mateys At Liar's Dice, Or Furnish Your Space With All Your Ill-begotten Gains. All This And An Ocean View. Thee Place To Assemble Before Going Off To Play Cutthroats: Battle For Black Powder Cove.|Scene/Entitlement|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
8D2C0A43-D2F54E94-B0D6C424-63D81900|Name|Desc|The Dream Yacht: Arctic Voyage|Treat Them To The Sights Of Breathtaking Glaciers, Giant Ice Formations And Crystal Blue Waters With The Dream Yacht: Arctic Voyage. Explore Three Decks, Chill Out On The Private Ice Shelf And Collect 20 Unique Rewards. Live The Dream!|Scene/Entitlement|Lockwood Publishing|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|LUA-REWARD|Res:0
8EB870C4-5502489A-B4906B84-6AE35F01|Name|Desc|Luxury Weekend Lake House|Enjoy A Bit Of Rest And Relaxation In This Modern Two-story Lake House Complete With A Kitchen, Bedroom, And Dock With Your Very Own Rowboat. The Stunning Backdrop For The Perfect Weekend Getaway Is Set On The Edge Of A Tantalizing Lake And Mystically Docile Forestry. In Addition To That, The Serene Life-like Atmosphere Of Dancing Fire-flies And Migrating Birds Will Surely Erase Any Motivation Of Returning To The Busy City Streets.|Scene/Entitlement|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.41.0.37.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
8EBCCB06-3F964F1F-B2FB4FB0-33F909C7|Name|Desc|Gothic Cathedral - Clubhouse|This Ancient Abandoned Cathedral On The Cliff Is A Sanctuary And A Place You Call Home.  From The Majestic Room, Moonlit Courtyard, To The Massive Candlelit Hall, You Can Be The Ruler Of The Night.|Scene/Entitlement|Konami|HDK_1.65.0.139.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
905C3B4F-B8124007-AC386DE9-F9F41893|kName|kDesc|SeaClyff Night Clubhouse|A Radical Nightclub Space With All The Essentials. Food In The Fridge, Tunes In The Stereo And Lots Of Space For Multi-level Dance Floor Action. State Of The Art Everything. The Doors Are Automatic, The Appliances Are Interactive, Even The Shower And Toilet Work (an Essential At Any Party). Four Floors Of Fun In A Hi-tech Heaven That Would Make Even The Great Gatsby Jealous. If Lavish Is Your Lifestyle, Then This Is Your New Party Pad.|Scene/Entitlement|Game Mechanics|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
905DB9DE-0ABC4191-85CA28D8-AB6343C0|kName|kDesc|LKWD Life Paradise Marina|An Idyllic Marina Apartment Perfect For Spending The Night Before Your Next Big Adventure. Luxuriate In Stylish Surroundings With A Stunning Tropical Sunset View, Exotic Wildlife And Magnificent Craft Around You.|Scene/Entitlement|Lockwood|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|LUA-REWARD|Res:0
905EC5DC-E699444D-B9610103-680F1020|kName|kDesc|Neotopia Hub Apartment|Take Up Residence In The Neotopia Hub Apartment. Www.neotopia.co|Scene/Entitlement|Madmunki|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
90A027DE-4B2E4AB6-A5197ECB-1246267F|Name|Desc|Old West Saloon Clubhouse|Take Pride As The New Owner Of The Old West Saloon Today! You've Worked Hard Moving Westward To Explore The New Frontier, And It's Time To Take Pride In Your Latest Acquisition. The Saloon Is The Perfect Place To Host Friends With Included Games Of Blackjack, Liar's Dice And Even Darts. But No New Piece Of Real Estate Would Be Complete Without A Wardrobe So Included Is Old West Attire And Furniture To Truly Give Your New Home An Authentic Look And Feel. This Saloon Is So Jammed Packed With Items And Minigames You'll Be The Talk Of The Town! The Old West Saloon Space Is A Clubhouse Where Everyone Is Invited To Join.|Scene/Entitlement|Digital Leisure|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
91FD9A80-0E30427D-9EE089E3-1FED7372|kName|kDesc|Gothic Cathedral|This Ancient Abandoned Cathedral On The Cliff Is A Sanctuary And A Place You Call Home.  From The Majestic Room, Moonlit Courtyard, To The Massive Candlelit Hall, You Can Be The Ruler Of The Night.|Scene/Entitlement|Konami|HDK_1.60.0.450.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
92066043-7BD4466F-8616C358-34E1E4FD|kName|kDesc|SeaClyff Clubhouse|A Radical Club Space With All The Essentials. Food In The Fridge, Tunes In The Stereo And Lots Of Space For Multi-level Dance Floor Action. State Of The Art Everything. The Doors Are Automatic, The Appliances Are Interactive, Even The Shower And Toilet Work (an Essential At Any Party). Four Floors Of Fun In A Hi-tech Heaven That Would Make Even The Great Gatsby Jealous. If Lavish Is Your Lifestyle, Then This Is Your New Party Pad.|Scene/Entitlement|Game Mechanics|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
92E73C12-F52A416E-B2DE84D5-3A1F6756|Name|Desc|Oscar's Lobster Mania Island|Feed Oscar Those Lobsters Till You Drop, Or Just Wander The Sandy Beach In The Midday Sun.|Scene/Entitlement|VEEMEE|HDK_1.55.0.155.BETA2|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
9314F7BE-C70D46D0-91301D6F-58A24735|Name|Name|Batman Object Unlocker|Batman Object Unlocker|Scene/Entitlement|MakerXX|HDK_XX|AUTO-REWARD|Res:0
93C188A6-4422482D-93D97D39-67A924FA|kName|kDesc|RaceOn Garage|This Garage Is Not Just For Cars, It's The Pinnacle Of Cool When It Comes To A Meeting Place For People In PlayStation®Home. Be One Of The Edgy First To Own This Stunning Space And Decide What You Want To Use It For! Organize An Underground Party Or Convert It Into The Most Modern Of Living Space Or Keep It As A Working Space, The Choices Are Endless!|Scene/Entitlement|JAM Games Ltd|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
93DA1344-F63F4007-9B69AA40-97CE99B6|kName|kDesc|Hot Sandy Beach Just For Two|Vacation On A Luxurious Private Beach. The Clear Blue Ocean, The Wide Sandy Beach, And The Cottages On The Sea Are All Yours. With Your Friends, With Your Lover. Your Vacation Has Just Begun.|Scene/Entitlement|Granzella Inc.|HDK_1.65.0.139.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
93F47868-BF7341D3-BFF67F23-EA3B3813|kName|kDesc|The Greenhouse|Enjoy The Wonderful Atmosphere And Gardens Around This Victorian Style Greenhouse. This Newly Restored Piece Of Architecture Retains The Charm And The Beauty Of The Old Days. Surrounded By A Lake And Luscious Green Areas, It Is The Perfect Place To Hang Around Alone Or With Friends.|Scene/Entitlement|KOVOK LTD|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
93F58E4E-A55046CE-94781030-4B2BC4E5|kName|kDesc|The Secret Party Garden: Clubhouse|Host Your Own Secret Party Within The Secluded Walls Of This Luscious Garden. Chill Out By The Lily Pond, Or Put Your Feet Up On The Patio And Take In The Tranquil Surroundings.|Scene/Entitlement|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
94F8553E-D3C8445B-9729700A-7C9AE28A|Name|Desc|Aurora Showcase Apartment|The Perfect Apartment For Showcasing Your Rewards And Purchases.|Scene/Entitlement|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|AUTO-REWARD|Res:0
94FEA9FC-C05D409B-AF9401A3-A2B40AF0|Name|Desc|RaceOn Garage|This Garage Is Not Just For Cars, It's The Pinnacle Of Cool When It Comes To A Meeting Place For People In PlayStation®HOME. Be One Of The Edgy First To Own This Stunning Space And Decide What You Want To Use It For! Organize An Underground Party Or Convert It Into The Most Modern Of Living Space Or Keep It As A Working Space, The Choices Are Endless!|Scene/Entitlement|Jam Games LTD|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
95761C1E-0D27494F-AE8020AA-C31E0536|Name|Desc|Emo's Garage Loft|Your Very Own Emo Ray Garage Loft. A Great Place To Relax After Saving The World From Intergalactic Teddy Bears! This Apartment Connects Directly Into The Public And Game Spaces For Emo Ray Vs. Intergalactic Teddy Bears!|Scene/Entitlement|Heavy Water|HDK_1.65.0.139.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
991413A1-9B9644B0-8DDBB3F3-D478AC60|kName|kDesc|Mystery Key - (#2 Of 3)|This Mystery Key Will Fast Become Your Favorite. Collect All Three.|Scene_Entitlement|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.65.0.139.BETA|AUTO-REWARD|Res:0
99976F79-27C0475E-95348420-406AF70A|Name|Desc|Men In Black™ Headquarters - Clubhouse|Youll Have An All-access Pass When You Own The Men In Black™ Headquarters As Your Own Club House!  Hold Your Meetings In The MIB Offices, Shop In The Armory And Relax In The Break Room! The MIB™ HQ Is The Perfect Set-up For Your Secret, Underground Organization. So Suit Up And Get Ready For The Explosive Return Of Agents Kay And Jay In Men In Black™ III And The Epic New Video Game Men In Black: Alien Crisis™!|Scene/Entitlement|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.65.0.139.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
9C44BA1A-9DD847FE-BDDA1B92-9F782D90|Name|Desc|Gothic Manor|Welcome To The Gothic Manor, Where Its Always Midnight And The Moon Is Constantly Hovering In The Starry Night Sky. Youll Enjoy The Manor's Dark Victorian Style Themes Such As The Grand Ballroom On The Grand Floor, And A First Story Balcony That Overlooks An Outside Courtyard, Complete With Its Own Man-made Pond. Reward Your Guests With A Gothic Manor Goblet Item, Exclusive To Gothic Manor Personal Space.|Scene/Entitlement|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.66.0.144.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
9CBB7537-6FCB4B1C-A362DD65-B64DD6DA|kName|kDesc|The House - Clubhouse|The LIVING Collection - The House! Remember... Fashion Passes, Style Remains, LIVING Is The Key!|Scene/Entitlement|JAM Games Ltd|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
9D455EFB-BCFF45CA-B6E18FF7-F460EE91|Name|Desc|City Of Flowers Penthouse Window To The World|Make This Apartment Penthouse In Downtown Paris Yours, Between The Eiffel Tower And The Arc De Triomphe. Your Life In The City Of Flowers, Paris, Begins Here.|Scene/Entitlement|Granzella|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
9D6282BB-46224ED8-BA541CF4-D2BEB11A|Name|Desc|Valor Barracks|Valor Barracks - For Valor Employees, The Barracks Are Your Home Away From Home. This Apartment Has All The Amenities A Soldier Should Ever Need. There's Fresh Mountain Air, Tall Evergreen Trees And A Heavily Armed Chopper Just Around The Corner.|Scene/Entitlement|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.3.5.120.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
9E680C54-57E64C05-824C5D9E-85192126|Name|Desc|PlayStation®Home Mansion - First Floor|Step Onto The Second-story Floor Of The Playstation®Home Mansion And Experience The Frills Of A Life Lived In Luxury. Indulge Yourself In A Classic Game Of Pool Or The Darts Mini-game That Comes Included In Your New Game Lounge. Couple That With A Sleek Juice Bar, A Library Fit For A Greek Scholar, And A Lavishly Decorated Bedroom And Youre Living Life Like A King. As An Added Bonus, Each Section Of The Playstation®Home Mansion Includes Up To 5 Unique Gold Rewards For You And Your Guests.|Scene/Entitlement|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.65.0.139.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
9EF9E187-08A84555-A767F27D-97B497BA|kName|kDesc|Xi Vertigo Apartment|This Massive And Fantastical Outdoor Apartment, Situated On The Side Of A Skyscraper Overlooking A Futuristic City, Defies Belief.|Scene/Entitlement|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
A0266F81-7FFA4165-ABCF8780-B4F71E5B|kName|kDesc|Audi Apartment|The Audi Apartment Is Your Reward For Reaching The Skies In The Audi Vertical Run Game. Enjoy The View Of The City Below Or Relax While Watching Selected Audi Content.|Scene/Entitlement|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_XX|LUA-REWARD|Res:0
A02FA240-BA2E4816-88BAB4F3-A120FD4E|Name|Desc|Playground Apartment|This Apartment Boasts Beautiful Views Of The Playground, The Buser Bridge, And The Quevedo River. It Is Furnished With The Latest In Parquet Flooring, Lighting Fixtures, And Radiator Heating.|Scene/Entitlement|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.3.6.22.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
A07DDAB2-42B34B78-BFC2B33C-4C822F65|kName|kDesc|The Secret Party Garden: Apartment|Host Your Own Secret Party Within The Secluded Walls Of This Luscious Garden. Chill Out By The Lily Pond, Or Put Your Feet Up On The Patio And Take In The Tranquil Surroundings.|Scene/Entitlement|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
A15FB2B4-B4684AE9-8DC2B6C7-49D7857D|Name|Desc|The Painted Bare Studio|The Painted Bare Studio Is The Ideal Place To Let Your Artistic Imagination Run Wild! So Unpack Your Artist Equipment And Get Settled In. But What Will You Use This Loft Apartment For, A Workspace, A Living Space, A Gallery Or As The Perfect Backdrop To A Social Event? The Choice Is Yours With This Versatile Apartment!|Scene/Entitlement|JAM Games Ltd.|HDK_1.82.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
A3BAF598-82314A5E-9454EBA1-8A16E388|Name|Desc|Lock-a-doodle Studio (Clubhouse)|The Perfect Setting For All Your Doodling! The Lock-a-doodle Studio Includes A Built In Lock-a-doodle Mini-game Plus A Gallery To Display All Your Finest Doodles Created In-game!|Scene/Entitlement|Lockwood Publishing|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
A3C73E02-C31C4F5E-8138013E-10A2F9ED|kName|kDesc|The Dressing Room|This Environment Is Undoubtedly The Most Distinguished And Elegant On PlayStation®Home. Characterised By Its Spaciousness, Light And Class, It Has Been Specially Created For Those Who Appreciate Quality And Good Taste. The Dressing Room Is Not Only A Masterpiece Of Architecture, But Also A Work Of Art.|Scene/Entitlement|KOVOK LTD|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
A3D7AFFC-BCB34795-933F7E60-4457C7C8|Name|Desc|Ansada Fone Apartment (Night)|This Is A Special Version Of The Ansada Fone Apartment That Was Won From Playing The OMG Trap-O-Matic In Aurora. Don't Forget To Check Out The Other Cool Apartments And Clubhouses From NDreams.|Scene/Entitlement|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.55.0.155.BETA2|AUTO-REWARD|Res:0
A3D87992-4DEE4CEA-AFFCE378-B253E597|kName|kDesc|A School Life Full Of Memories|One Floor Of The School Building Is Yours, Including Two Classrooms, The Purchasing Department And The Hallway. The Layout Is Up To You, Including Desks And Chairs. Create Your Own Classroom And Enjoy School Life With Your Friends! However, Don't Stay At School Until Late At Night. You Never Know What Might Happen...|Scene/Entitlement|Granzella Inc.|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
A44E02A6-EFD24108-9ECED0D1-258314AE|kName|kDesc|Xi Party House|A Nighttime Party Apartment With Pumping Electronic Dance Music. What's In The Safe And How Do You Open It?|Scene/Entitlement|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
A44F7325-E04D4C0E-AC65DF04-146F6610|Name|Desc|Cutteridge Estate|Unlock The Mysteries Of Cutteridge Estate. This Elegant Victorian Estate Is Rumored To Be The Final Resting Place Of Many Dark And Depraved Souls. Do You Dare To Venture Into These Forsaken Halls In Search Of The Secrets Which Lie Within?|Scene/Entitlement|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.55.0.155.BETA2|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
A476D518-FD714AD6-B8298458-580C5658|Name|Desc|Nebula Air Ship|Take To The Skies As A Nautical Air Pilot As You Maneuver Your Air Ship Through The Soft Billowy Clouds. From Atop Your Sky Deck You Will Truly Have A Birds Eye View Of The Land Down Below. You Might Even Catch A Glimpse Of Other Air Ships Flying In The Distance. Reward Your Guests With A Miniature Airship Item, Exclusive To Nebula Air Ship Personal Space.|Scene/Entitlement|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.55.0.155.BETA2|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
A47FB9E6-D69E4907-B9272EB7-3BFC2E63|Name|Desc|The Pearl Diver Apartment|Spend Some Time Beneath The Waves In Your Own Submarine, The Pearl Diver. Designed For Combing Through The Sea Floor, This Underwater Vessel Is Enclosed By Glass To Allow You To Fully Enjoy The Aquatic Sea Life. Reward You And Your Friends With The Exclusive Pearl Diver Mini-Fish Tank Furniture Item, Only Available In The Pearl Diver Apartment.|Scene/Entitlement|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
A50BAAE7-B5194401-B7E9FEE4-159DD198|kName|kDesc|A Tranquil Personal Garden|Your Own Garden, Received From The Kingdom Of Planta. Create Your Own Beautiful Garden By Planting Plantas And Arranging Furniture.|Scene/Entitlement|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.66.0.144.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
A54359B4-41EF4F5C-8B5C821A-EA0D5A87|Name|Desc|Fossil Museum|In This Personal Space, The Fossils That You Found In The Southern Island Hideaway Lounge Are Exhibited.|Scene/Entitlement|Granzella|HDK_1.65.0.139.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
A5BFD1B4-36344DBC-973DAF29-DFCF1225|Name|Desc|The Jewel Of The Skies|The Jewel Of The Skies Was Once A Flourishing Village In The Clouds, Each Palace And Dwelling Accessible Only By Flying Carpet. Long Ago This Magical Knowledge Was Lost And The Towers And Spires Gradually Fell Into Disrepair Until Only A Few Remained. Awaken The Genie, Unleash His Magic And Reap The Rewards! • Flying Carpet Gem Collection Mini-game • Interactive Genie • Unlockable Rewards And Apartment Customisations|Scene/Entitlement|Lockwood Publishing Ltd.|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
A61C6C54-D6544E90-9F5B66EA-7247A79D|Name|Desc|PlayStation®Home Mansion - Garage|A Mansion Isnt A Really A Mansion Without An Expensive Place To Keep Your Rides. Thats Why We Created An Over-sized Four-door Garage To Accompany The Playstation®Home Mansion. Your Showroom Comes Equipped With Overhead Lights To Help Show Off Your Prized Trophies. There Is More To This Fancy Showroom That Meets The Eye; Can You Find The Missing Pieces? As An Added Bonus, Each Section Of The Playstation®Home Mansion Includes Up To 5 Unique Gold Rewards For You And Your Guests.|Scene/Entitlement|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.55.0.155.BETA2|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
A7EFDE03-BCC94C49-BB234441-B1576B24|Name|Desc|Island Bungalow Apartment|Nestled On The Edge Of A Tropical Paradise, This Exquisite Island Bungalow Is Hidden Somewhere On An Uncharted Coastline. Be The First To Explore This Mysterious Paradise.|Scene/Entitlement|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.55.0.155.BETA2|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
A7FF6B1E-5D814693-B3E38620-757B6798|Name|Desc|The Campsite|Hitch Up Your Horse, And Put Some Beans On The Fire. This Is Your Very Own Campsite. It May Not Be Much, But At Least You've Got Something To Protect You From The Elements.|Scene/Entitlement|Digital Leisure Inc.|HDK_1.82.0.17.PUB|AUTO-REWARD|Res:0
A8CC1808-E02D4E59-95A2B6F2-AE08803A|kName|kDesc|Acorn Meadows Park Apartment - Autumn|Your Own Little Private Slice Of Acorn Meadows Park, This Lakeside Garden Apartment Provides The Perfect Place To Relax And Take Time Away From The Main Park Without Leaving The Acorn Meadows Environment.|Scene/Entitlement|VEEMEE|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
AA8D55A0-CAF74861-8C6DCCFE-ABCAE5B9|Name|Desc|Winter Vacation Villa|Experience The Frills And Chills Of This Ski Chalet Winter Wonderland Overlooked By An Icy Cascading Waterfall And Nestled Neatly In Between A Snowy Cliff And Snow-dressed Forest. Complete With Its Own Outdoor Jacuzzi, Indoor Fireplace, And Veranda Bedroom, This Is How The Winter Holiday Was Meant To Be Spent.|Scene/Entitlement|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
ABDED858-8E3B49BC-BAA4392D-9FDB5A63|kName|kDesc|SeaClyff Night Retreat|A Night Version Of One Of The Most Alive Spaces You Will Ever Spend Time In. It Has All The Best Parts Of The Day Space And Dynamic Outdoor Lighting That Can Be Turned On And Off. Even The Hot Tub Has Its Own Lighting. There Are A Few Enhancements Including All New Music. A Must Have For People Who Like The Best Of Everything.|Scene/Entitlement|Game Mechanics|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
ADB7291D-6C2346EE-A5D098CA-F8BA776D|kName|kDesc|Prehistoric Canyon|Enjoy Panoramic Views Of Dramatic Waterfalls And Lush Grassland From Your Bamboo Hut Perched High Above Prehistoric Canyon. Dinosaurs And Prehistoric Mammals Roam The Surroundings, From Peaceful Mammoth Families To Ferocious T-Rex. Play The Dinosaur Spotting Mini Game To Record The Prehistoric Creatures That Visit Every Day And Earn Rewards – Guests Can Play Too!|Scene/Entitlement|Lockwood|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
B01602C3-3B4F4DE0-94C4BE5F-E2A92D2C|kName|kDesc|Underwater Apartment|It's Wet Out There.|Scene/Entitlement|VEEMEE|HDK_1.60.0.451.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
B0A3D79D-EC6B483F-840ADF5A-03AD2FEA|Name|Desc|Tuscan Villa Clubhouse|Enjoy A Day In The Countryside At Your Elaborate Tuscan Villa. This Two-room Lodging Has A Swanky Living Room Connected To An Outdoor Porch And Patio. To Make Things Better, Weve Added An Indoor Swimming Pool In The Very Next Room. This Is The Perfect Place To Lay Out And Get To Know Your Guests Better. The Tuscan Villa Space Is A Clubhouse Where Everyone Is Invited To Join.|Scene/Entitlement|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
B0DDE58E-6BF54E3D-90C2C402-4A3EFC64|Name|Desc|Frozen Peak Palace|Surround Yourself In The Frosty Splendors Of The Frozen Peak Palace. Made Entirely From Blocks Of Ice, This Frosty Getaway Comes With A Rare Piece Of Art And An Inglenook With A Glacial Blue Flame. Reward Your Guests With A Frozen Peak Palace Throne Item, Exclusive To Frozen Peak Palace Personal Space.|Scene/Entitlement|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
B1512A75-9FA14B81-A67E24A9-F166313D|kName|kDesc|Relaxing Edo Bathhouse|A Relaxing Atmosphere For Body And Soul. Invite A Friend, Take A Soak Together In The Soothing Waters, And Watch The Days Fatigue Melt Away.|Scene/Entitlement|Granzella Inc.|HDK_1.83.0.11.PUB|LUA-REWARD|Res:0
B16B70B1-DC7F4315-BEEFE237-5731DB92|Name|Desc|Summer With Sunflowers Blooming|A Personal Space Where You Can Enjoy The Good Old Japanese Summer.|Scene/Entitlement|O-Two Inc.|HDK_1.82.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
B3716013-FE0F4926-8DD0A81F-99966076|Name|Desc|The Casino: Penthouse Suite|Welcome To Our Exclusive Penthouse Suite Strictly Reserved For Those In Our Millionaire's Club. The Concierge Is On Standby 24 Hours A Day To Manage Any Of Your Needs. Enjoy Your Stay At The Paradise Hotel And Casino.|Scene/Entitlement|Digital Leisure|HDK_1.65.0.139.BETA|AUTO-REWARD|Res:0
B385B2B4-EEE64B9C-A816C430-FE9837AF|kName|kDesc|The Hangar Skatepark|This Skatepark Is Housed Within A Huge Repurposed Aircraft Hangar! It's Open, It's Spacious, It's Everything An Avid Skater Ever Dreamed Of! With Ramps, Bowls, Grind Rails And Half Pipes, Its Time To Get On Your Deck And Skate Around This Large Skatepark!|Scene/Entitlement|VEEMEE|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
B3891E70-370F41CB-A2C11EEF-2FD1BFC8|kName|kDesc|The Midnight Glade|A Secluded Glade Under A Moonlit Starry Sky. Gather Around The Solitary Tree And Warm Yourself By The Glow Of The Fire. It's The Perfect Place For A Fireworks Party.|Scene/Entitlement|Lockwood|HDK_1.55.0.155.BETA2|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
B4D67F63-0CCE41A9-992A1E66-8083A5EF|Name|Desc|Ratchet & Clank: Home Sweet Home™|Enjoy The Space View From Your Ratchet & Clank Apartment!|Scene_Entitlement|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.3.0.125.BETA1|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
B6326429-CF304E26-959BC425-9E603A2E|Name|Desc|The Casino: Budget Room|We Hope You Enjoyed Playing At The Casino. As A First Time Player We've Managed To Find A Spare Room In Section B3 In Our Former Hotel Space. We're Happy To Offer One Of Our VIP Suites As Soon As You've Shown The True Card Shark You Are. Good Luck!|Scene/Entitlement|Digital Leisure, Inc.|HDK_1.51.0.60.PUB|AUTO-REWARD|Res:0
B635FDBE-95504AF9-A08B8A22-EFD7F768|Name|Desc|Warhawk™ Apartment|Your Personal Flying Fortress Will Keep You Safe While You And Your Friends Plan Your Next Attack With The Warhawk™ Sand Table. Jump Back Into The Fight With A Friend In The Co-operative 2-player Warhawk™ Turret Shooter, Competing For The High Score On Your Personal Leaderboard.|Scene_Entitlement|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.3.5.113.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
B63D963B-656D4EFD-BAEE6A5C-83EE30C7|kName|kDesc|City By The Bay Loft Window To The World|A Large Loft In Central San Francisco Along The Cable Car Line. You Can Live There Or Open Up A Shop. It's Up To You! Starting Today, You Too Are A Member Of The City By The Bay.|Scene/Entitlement|Granzella Inc.|HDK_1.82.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
B694C29F-794E4DCF-9F929370-353BBD5A|kName|kDesc|Xi Party House|Your Very Own Slice Of Xi - The Perfect Nighttime Party Palace.|Scene/Entitlement|MakerXX|HDK_1.3.6.22.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
B7731739-9BBA4627-B4C997CE-EFE4D183|Name|Desc|Aurora Island|Your Very Own Slice Of Aurora - It Is A Place To Relax And Contemplate. Well, When Aurora Isn't Under Attack!|Scene/Entitlement|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.41.0.37.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
B7812196-ED194EDA-8BE0D65C-8C898CCF|kName|kDesc|Luxurious Tropical Paradise Beach Crib|Some Would Call It Heaven, Some A Palace, In Europe They Call It A Villa, Some Americans A Mansion, But Most Just Call It A Hut. This Modern 21st Century Building In The sticks And Straw Style Has An Advanced Virtual Room System That Is Impossible To Find. It Has A Large Private Area With A Domed Games Room. Although It Has A Classic Flavour, The Home Has A Few Unique Qualities. Its Also An Amazing Place For Parties.|Scene_Entitlement|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.52.0.2.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
B7B8593F-4C614B69-84B7A3B9-1CC7243D|kName|kDesc|The Boutique Apartment|This FREE Apartment From NDreams Is The Perfect Place For The Suave And Sexy Socialites Of PlayStation®Home! Show Off Your Social Status By Purchasing The Additional Rooms. Unlock All Of The Rooms For A Collection Of Prestigious Reward Items!|Scene/Entitlement|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|AUTO-REWARD|Res:0
B873C179-25334865-881741CF-1DC21591|kName|kDesc|Masquerade Ball - The Ballroom Club House (Gothic)|The Perfect Club House To Host A Lavish Gothic Themed Masquerade Ball. Entertain Your Guests In This Beautiful Ballroom. Deck Out Your Ballroom With The Gothic Masquerade Ball Furniture Range For Extra Authenticity. Please Note, In Order To Access This Club House You Will Need To Have Purchased The Club House Slot From Either The Estates Store Or The Clubs Menu (available In Options).|Scene/Entitlement|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
B9165C00-4C514A88-BF835680-0624C0E6|kName|kDesc|Low Tide Lounge|Low Tide Lounge|Scene/Entitlement|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.3.0.292.CORE|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
B9867B6D-98174DB2-A27DA8F7-32C51251|kName|kDesc|Tree House Personal Apartment|A Stunning Circular Treehouse Built Around The Trunk Of An Ancient Tree High Up In The Mountains. Made Of Wood And Circular In Design, There Are Two Levels Each Offering Spectacular Views Of The Waterfalls And Mountains Outside.|Scene_Entitlement|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.3.2.16.BETA1|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
BC9D11D7-60694652-B47C27B7-A7207FB0|kName|kDesc|The Imperial Voyager|Traverse The Great Blue Yonder In Professor Sidwells Patented Steampunk Skyship, The Legendary Imperial Voyager.|Scene/Entitlement|MakerXX|HDK_1.83.0.11.PUB|AUTO-REWARD|Res:0
BCAC7233-591E4855-97B68A15-E7ED4A39|kName|kDesc|The 'Country Chic - Tour Bus' - Clubhouse|The Time Has Come To Hit The Road And Party. Take Full Advantage Of The Freedoms A Virtual World Provides, Slip The Bus Into Cruise Control And Join The Party At Full Speed! Just Remember… What Goes On Tour, Stays On Tour!|Scene/Entitlement|JAM Games Ltd|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
BD1511CE-D0C24873-A3F3E420-6D3E54D4|Name|Desc|Hillside Clubhouse|Built With A View In Mind, The Hillside Clubhouse Is The Place To Get Away From The Confines Of A Concrete Jungle And Bask In The Luxury Of A Home Away From Home. The Hillside House Space Is A Clubhouse Where Everyone Is Invited To Join.|Scene/Entitlement|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.55.0.155.BETA2|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
BD8D559F-9E554E7E-9D51A766-62E08C91|kName|kDesc|Rainy Day Apartment|When The Sun Is Setting And It's Wet Outside, There Really Is No Place Like Home...|Scene/Entitlement|MakerXX|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|AUTO-REWARD|Res:0
BEAF71D1-C32643BE-9CBED7EA-7E690F65|kName|kDesc|Penthouse In La Ville-Lumière -From The Window Of The World-|A Penthouse Which Is Located Close To Paris' Urban Area, Eiffel Tower And Triumphal Arch Is Yours. The Life In Paris, La Ville-Lumière, Starts Now.|Scene/Entitlement|Granzella Inc.|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
BF7EA1B6-93C54CAF-80BE273A-36425106|kName|kDesc|Gnome Curling Secret Garden|Enjoy Gnome Curling In The Privacy Of Your Own Secret Garden. Comes Complete With A Gazebo, Beautiful Floral Displays And A Magical Door To Take You Back Home Again. When You Purchase This Apartment You Also Receive: Gnome Curling - Standard Gnome Gnome Curling - Fat Gnome Gnome Curling - Skinny Gnome Gnome Curling - Bouncy Gnome Gnome Curling - Explosive Gnome Gnome Curling - Ninja Gnome Gnome Curling - Stinky Gnome Gnome Curling - Sexy Gnome|Scene/Entitlement|VEEMEE|HDK_1.55.0.155.BETA2|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
BFC699E9-4468434D-8D8A9525-56F6CF8E|Name|Desc|Dolphy Room|A Relaxing Virtual Space Where You Can Raise And Interact With Your Own Dolphy.|Scene/Entitlement|Hudson Soft Co. Ltd.|HDK_1.3.6.22.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
C03F895E-FF47481D-9A8E92EF-337D6A08|Name|Desc|Moon Forest Clubhouse|Camping Will Never Be The Same After You Spend A Night At The Moon Forest Clubhouse. Complete With An Outdoor Fire Pit, This Three Room Exotic Getaway Is A Great Way To Lose Yourself In Nature And Spend Time With Friends. The Moon Forest Clubhouse Is A Space Where Everyone Is Invited To Join.|Scene/Entitlement|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.55.0.155.BETA2|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
C0420793-8689412C-ADCE1531-F4A67DE6|kName|kDesc|City By The Bay Loft Window To The World|A Large Loft In Central San Francisco Along The Cable Car Line. You Can Live There Or Open Up A Shop. It's Up To You! Starting Today, You Too Are A Member Of The City By The Bay.|Scene/Entitlement|Granzella Inc.|HDK_1.82.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
C448493B-36F64B13-8437B3FE-74A67430|Name|Desc|Plum Tree Pavilion Clubhouse|Take A Deep Breath And Inhale The Soft Sweet Aroma Of The Plum Tree Pavilion. Its Gentle Landscaping And Exquisite Architecture Makes This Space Ideal For Anyone Whos A Fan Of Fishponds And Rock Formations. The Plum Tree Pavilion Is A Clubhouse Where Everyone Is Invited To Join.|Scene/Entitlement|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
C5B4CA8C-D0694FEE-B5CE2D0E-72646493|Name|Desc|Palace Of The Seven Winds Clubhouse|Reign Over Your Own Celestial Paradise With The Palace Of The Seven Winds! Exert Your Influence Over The Heavens Themselves To Alter Time, Break Free Of Your Earthly Shackles And Take To The Skies, Lounge In Your Own Personal Harem-style Apartments, Have Wishes Granted By Your Personal Genie, Unlock Rewards And Much More!|Scene/Entitlement|Juggernaut|HDK_1.65.0.139.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
C6144AE1-60314F14-9133163E-3316414B|Name|Desc|Diamond Beach Mansion|Enter The Most Luxurious Personal Space In PlayStation®Home. The Diamond Beach Mansion Is Packed With Special Features Befitting The Rich And Famous – From A Gifting Machine That Lets You Give Your Friends Exclusive Virtual Items (and Rewards Just For The Owner), To Fully-functional Appliances And Fun Interactives Like The User-controlled Weather And Day/night Cycles. The Diamond Beach Mansion Includes Four Extensions: 1st Floor, 2nd Floor, Backyard, And Private Yacht That You Can Buy In Any Order. Collect All Four Areas Of The Diamond Beach Mansion To Unlock A Secret Area!|Scene/Entitlement|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.55.0.155.BETA2|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
C77BDA45-69B74D4F-AB24CDBD-69456462|kName|kDesc|Masquerade Ball - The Ballroom (Gothic)|The Perfect Personal Space To Host A Lavish Gothic Themed Masquerade Ball. Entertain Your Guests In This Beautiful Ballroom. Deck Out Your Ballroom With The Gothic Masquerade Ball Furniture Range For Extra Authenticity.|Scene/Entitlement|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
C7C53218-28284FD9-80B5DA86-5966F6FA|kName|kDesc|Nostalgic University Days|Make The First Floor Of A University Building Yours, Including Two Classrooms, A Shop, And A Hallway. The Layout Of Desks, Chairs, And Other Items Is Up To You. Make Your Own Unique Classroom And Enjoy University Life Along With Your Friends! Be Careful Not To Stay At University Until Late At Night. You Never Know What Might Happen...|Scene/Entitlement|Granzella Inc.|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
C7EB3685-A9344D32-AA40B3D9-246EF583|kName|kDesc|Paradise Health Club: Clubhouse|Relax And Re-energise In The Exotic And Picturesque Grounds Of Paradise Health Club! Chill Out By The Pool, Sunbathe On The Terrace Or Detox In The Sauna!|Scene/Entitlement|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
C8864540-2F1D4F2C-880D4A5F-5156EFB9|Name|Desc|F.U.B.A.R. Apartment (+DOUBLE POINTS)|This Unique Outdoor Apartment Contains A Scaled Copy Of Your Own Amazing Military Base From The FREE Game F.U.B.A.R. (Fight Until Blood And Ruin) And Earns You DOUBLE POINTS In Key Sections Of The Game, Helping You Rank Up Much Faster. Observe Your Master Piece Of War From The Comfort Of Your Own Home And Show It Off To Your Friends.|Scene/Entitlement|NDreams|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
C9B2191B-0122468C-A32A0E37-DF02CA88|Name|Desc|Moon Forest Apartment|Camping Will Never Be The Same After You Spend A Night At The Moon Forest Apartment. Complete With An Outdoor Fire Pit, This Three Room Exotic Getaway Is A Great Way To Lose Yourself In Nature And Spend Time With Friends. Reward Yourself And Your Friends With Exclusive Camping Gear Furniture Item, Only Available In The Moon Forest Apartment.|Scene/Entitlement|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.55.0.155.BETA2|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
C9B58F0B-F45C4D6E-8344DDD9-F09BBA72|kName|kDesc|Acorn Meadows Park Apartment|Your Own Little Private Slice Of Acorn Meadows Park, This Lakeside Garden Apartment Provides The Perfect Place To Relax And Take Time Away From The Main Park Without Leaving The Acorn Meadows Environment.|Scene/Entitlement|VEEMEE|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
CBC81E64-19F643DA-A4E0BB27-0FB943F9|kName|kDesc|City Penthouse|A Luxury Apartment In The Heart Of The City Designed Around A Split Level Layout. Additional Highlights Include Exquisite Water Features, Unique Lighting Solutions And An Incredible View Of The City Skyline.|Scene/Entitlement|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_XX|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
CC17FFC2-E2FA46DD-AAFD5D77-C4E9155C|Name|Desc|The Complex|This FREE Apartment Is Brought To You By NDreams. Expand Your Complex By Getting Any Or All Of The Additional Rooms. On Doing So, You Won't Only Impress Your Friends With A Great Apartment But You Will Be Rewarded For Your Efforts.|Scene/Entitlement|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|AUTO-REWARD|Res:0
CE92A783-C28948E4-B4225D06-E6A87217|Name|Desc|Hollywood Hills House Daytime Clubhouse (with Home Theatre)|Entertain And Meet With Your Club In This Ultra-exclusive Clubhouse, Set In The Hollywood Hills Above The LA Skyline! Features Include: • Built-in Entertainment On Demand Theater System; • A Swimming Feature For The Infinity Pool! THIS Is The Ultra-exclusive Retreat For The Discerning Club Owner. Purchase Of This Clubhouse Comes Bundled With The LOOT™ Active Camera And Active Light, So You Can Film Your Parties And Upload Them To YouTube! PLEASE READ: Due To Contractual And Rights Agreements, All Content May Not Be Available In All Countries. Content Availability Is Dependent On The Geolocation Of The Device. CRACKLE Content Is Only Available In US, CA, UK, And AU. RADIOIO Is Only Available In US And CA. Only One LOOT™ TV Or LOOT™ Radio Can Be Active At A Time.|Scene/Entitlement|© LOOT™|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
CE9F6B73-83F940D8-A536584B-A46EF107|Name|Desc|Sodium Blimp|Step Aboard Your Very Own Dirigible! Sodium Pilots All Need A Way To Travel From One Track To Another And Many Prefer To Go Via Blimp. If You Get Adventurous While On Your Travels, Why Not Stop For A Digging Session, Who Knows What Treasures The Desert Floor Might Yield! Includes: • Flying Minigame • Digging Minigame With 13 Exclusive PlayStation®Home Rewards And The Chance To Earn Sodium Resources • The Ability To Complete New Public And Secret VICKIE Challenges In Return For Sodium Credits|Scene/Entitlement|Lockwood Publishing|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
CFF3AD7D-D4E243D3-AAAC39EE-49C804AB|Name|Desc|Waterfall Terrace|Waterfall Terrace Is The Perfect Secluded Get Away - Fish And Enjoy Nature In All It's Splendor.|Scene_Entitlement|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.3.0.125.BETA1|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
D0652E2F-5FB249FE-BE72633F-49FE7876|kName|kDesc|Underwater Apartment|It's Wet Out There|Scene/Entitlement|MakerXX|HDK_1.55.0.156.PUB|AUTO-REWARD|Res:0
D0719CB2-F255445D-9CFAA4C0-9BDC8728|kName|kDesc|LKWD Life Lakeside Oasis|Enjoy The Subtle Elegance And Modern Asthetic Of This Beautiful Personal Space. A Just Reward For Your Hard Efforts In LKWD Life.|Scene/Entitlement|Lockwood|HDK_1.83.0.11.PUB|LUA-REWARD|Res:0
D0D63971-412B4B58-BB0755B5-FBF20E46|Name|Desc|Tuscan Villa Apartment|Enjoy A Day In The Countryside At Your Elaborate Tuscan Villa. This Two-room Lodging Has A Swanky Living Room Connected To An Outdoor Porch And Patio. To Make Things Better, Weve Added An Indoor Swimming Pool In The Very Next Room. This Is The Perfect Place To Lay Out And Get To Know Your Guests Better. Reward Yourself And Your Friends With An Exclusive Tuscan Villa Pizza Furniture Item, Only Available In The Tuscan Villa Apartment.|Scene/Entitlement|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
D12B4345-24C741A5-BA7BBFA0-33982C3E|Name|Desc|Ansada Fone Apartment|This Truly Unique Apartment Isn't Like Anything You Have Ever Seen Before In PlayStation®Home. A Fantastic Cartoon World Where You Can Play A Frantic 4 Player Mini Game With Your Friends Or Chill Out And Redecorate. Will You Get There In Time To Ansada Fone?|Scene/Entitlement|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.52.0.2.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
D14BEDE1-562F40E7-9E98FCD2-66870B1D|Name|Desc|Edo Row Houses|This Personal Space Re-creates The Collective Residences On The Back Streets In The Humantiy-overflowing Edo Period. If You Own This Personal Space, You Can Use Operation: Defend Edo Row Houses As A Recovery Spot.|Scene/Entitlement|Granzella|HDK_1.55.0.155.BETA2|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
D1556CE2-155E4979-A996991C-76704278|Name|Desc|Infinite Oasis Ranch Apartment|The Perfect Place For A Mid-summer Retreat, The Infinite Oasis Ranch Has It All. From Lively Cacti And Ageless Palm Trees To Panoramic Views Of The Surrounding Mountain Ridge, This Space Packs It All. Reward Yourself And Your Friends With The Exclusive Infinite Oasis Ranch Hay Chair, Only Available In The Infinite Oasis Ranch Apartment.|Scene/Entitlement|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
D173B874-16054E3F-A72DE46A-5E9A8336|Name|Desc|Plum Tree Pavilion Apartment|Take A Deep Breath And Inhale The Soft Sweet Aroma Of The Plum Tree Pavilion. Its Gentle Landscaping And Exquisite Architecture Makes This Space Ideal For Anyone Whos A Fan Of Fishponds And Rock Formations. Reward You And Your Friends With An Exclusive Lantern Furniture Item, Only Available In The Plum Tree Pavilion Apartment..|Scene/Entitlement|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
D1A1DF77-FC8B48B3-B566BFC9-5450EBB9|Name|Desc|MiniBots Training Facility|This Personal Space Allows You To Design And Control A Custom MiniBot In A Fast-paced Multiplayer Third Person Shooter For 2-8 Players. Battle It Out In A Last-bot Standing Free-for-all Brawl Or Group With Friends For Team Arena Mode! Complete Hidden Achievements To Unlock Unique Rewards!|Scene/Entitlement|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.65.0.139.BETA|LUA-REWARD|Res:0
D3108B66-456F4C74-93CB0BE4-D50A6381|Name|Desc|Uncharted Fortune Hunter's Apartment|Being A Fortune Hunter Is Never Easy. It Means Having To Travel To The Ends Of The Earth And Rarely Staying In One Place Too Long. Good Thing You Have An Apartment Like This To Call Home.|Scene/Entitlement|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.3.5.121.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
D41104DA-FD364319-B4EDBA53-0B6353B6|kName|kDesc|Stately Home Clubhouse|The Stately Home Is The Perfect Clubhouse For Those People Who Like The Finer Things In Life. With Its Large And Beautiful Grounds And A Direct Link Through To The Masquerade Ball - The Ballroom Clubhouse, This Space Is A Must-have. Also Comes With Five Free Rewards.|Scene/Entitlement|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.82.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
D4A05C18-F4124DFC-AC30A0DE-F342C412|kName|kDesc|Pink Paradise - Tour Bus|The Time Has Come To Hit The Road And Party. Take Full Advantage Of The Freedoms A Virtual World Provides, Slip The Bus Into Cruise Control And Join The Party At Full Speed! Just Remember… What Goes On Tour, Stays On Tour!|Scene/Entitlement|JAM Games Ltd|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
D52975DC-8EFF47BB-845B640E-D1B2C5A2|kName|kDesc|The Nightclub: Apartment|The Nightclub Is The Perfect Venue For A Fantastic Night Out. Dance To Pumping Music Tracks On The Dance Floor, Sip On Drinks In The Lounge Area, Or Activate The Foam Cannon For An Extra Crazy Night!|Scene/Entitlement|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
D52F0918-A7AC42FE-BD2362D8-1762A02B|Name|Desc|Studio Stage Set From LOOT™|The Modular Stage Set Takes Professional Machinima To The Next Level. It Provides The User With Unprecedented Levels Of Control Over The Floor, Walls, Backdrops, Lights And Camera Systems.  Also Included Are The Portable Camera And Portable Light Active Items, Which Let You Take The LOOT™ Machinima Tools To Any Private Space You Own, Transforming It Into A Perfect Location For Shooting Your Movies And TV Shows. It Is The Ultimate Tool For Having Fun With Your Friends While Bringing New Stories To Life.|Scene/Entitlement|LOOT™|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
D6347D26-64794E71-9EFEDA36-0AB06F57|Name|Desc|Glittering Sands Secluded Retreat|Spend Your Holiday On A Luxurious Private Beach. The Clear Blue Sea, The White Sandy Beach, And The Cottage On The Ocean Are All Yours. With A Friend, Or With That Special Someone. Your Holiday Has Just Begun.|Scene/Entitlement|Granzella|HDK_1.65.0.139.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
D6585313-04764E31-97755D22-7BFA4BE5|kName|kDesc|SeaClyff Retreat|Floor-to-ceiling Windows In Most Rooms Looking Out On An Unobstructed View Of The Ocean. The Four Floors Include A Large Master Bedroom Which Opens Up To A Balcony And A Study With Your Choice Of Wallpaper. An Open Floor Plan With Lots Of Natural Light. A Large Living Room, Dining Room With Fireplace And Finished Basement. Kitchen Recently Upgraded With High End Working Appliances. A Built In Hot Tub And Expansive Deck Areas With Stunning Views. All Doors Are Automatic. Included Is A Built In Sound System, Games, Plus Rewards For The Owner And Guests. It Truly Has More Features Than Can Be Listed Here. It Is A Must See To Believe.|Scene/Entitlement|Game Mechanics|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
D6C195CB-266F4307-A4F408DD-2ACDFBEF|kName|kDesc|Oscar's Lobster Mania Island|Feed Oscar Those Lobsters Till You Drop, Or Just Wander The Sandy Beach In The Midday Sun.|Scene/Entitlement|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.52.0.2.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
D984FB4A-38604E87-8326658C-DB66F643|Name|Desc|Club Luminosity|This Is The Ultimate Place To Share Your Love Of Neon. If You Love Things That Glow, Then This Place Is For You!|Scene/Entitlement|Konami Digital Entertainment|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
D9B1F481-E24143E3-901B74F5-BC1C30BB|Name|Desc|SuperStar - Jetsetter Private Plane|Take A Ride In The Ultra Luxurious Private Plane. This Flying Home Has Everything A Superstar Needs, Including The Best Pilots Around. Show Off Like A Super Star!|Scene/Entitlement|Konami Digital Entertainment, Inc.|HDK_1.55.0.155.BETA2|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
DA7D5905-4C2D43DD-B5CEEF48-D44221C4|Name|Desc|Old West Saloon|Take Pride As The New Owner Of The Old West Saloon Today! You've Worked Hard Moving Westward To Explore The New Frontier, And It's Time To Take Pride In Your Latest Acquisition. The Saloon Is The Perfect Place To Host Friends With Included Games Of Blackjack, Liar's Dice And Even Darts. But No New Piece Of Real Estate Would Be Complete Without A Wardrobe So Included Is Old West Attire And Furniture To Truly Give Your New Home An Authentic Look And Feel. This Saloon Is So Jammed Packed With Items And Minigames You'll Be The Talk Of The Town!|Scene/Entitlement|Digital Leisure|HDK_1.55.0.155.BETA2|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
DB3088E4-7BD14979-8639CE12-350AF649|Name|Desc|Def Jam Rapstar Studio|State Of The Art In-home Recording And Mixing Studio.|Scene/Entitlement|Konami|HDK_1.41.0.37.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
DB5D6D31-96B1454B-82862C18-6BD61D8B|kName|kDesc|PC Primitive Dwelling|An Unusual Personal Space Built In The Primitive World Where PC Primitives Are Set! Light The Rooms With primitive Lamps And Enhance The Dwellings With primitive Furniture That Can Be Obtained From Time To Time At Rivers And Other Places! The Primitive Furniture Is An Exclusive Item For This Personal Space.|Scene/Entitlement|Hudson Soft Co. Ltd.|HDK_1.41.0.37.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
DB7EE97E-8D444839-85571ECC-0302A3A7|Name|Desc|Drop Science Subway|This Derelict Station Was Deserted Long Ago And Is Now The Coolest Party Space, Hidden From The City. Turn The Music Up, Dance, And Socialise Into The Late Hours.|Scene/Entitlement|Lockwood Publishing|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
DEAF2F6C-71A54119-940BE296-9A8E70FE|kName|kDesc|Masquerade Ball - The Ballroom Club House|The Perfect Club House To Host A Lavish Masquerade Ball. Entertain Your Guests In This Beautiful Ballroom. Deck Out Your Ballroom With The Masquerade Ball Furniture Range For Extra Authenticity. Please Note, In Order To Access This Club House You Will Need To Have Purchased The Club House Slot From Either The Estates Store Or The Clubs Menu (available In Options).|Scene/Entitlement|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
DF87D024-CF5C4AE5-9C1E3581-779C2FAE|kName|kDesc|Mahjong Apartment|Looking For A Nice And Tranquil Place To Stay? The Mahjong Apartment Is Just The Place! This Walled Apartment In An Busy Orient City Is An Oasis Of Rest With Blossom Trees And Koi Carps. If You Are Looking For Something More Lively You Can Try The Mahjong Attack Game That Comes With The Apartment. Mahjong Attack Is A Challenging Variant Of Mahjong Solitaire Which Is All About Speed! You Play The Game Alone (single Player), Together With Your Friends (co-op) Or Against Your Friends (multiplayer)!|Scene_Entitlement|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.55.0.155.BETA2|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
DFB03849-CA934A54-88C48B6D-5AAF9905|kName|kDesc|Tearoom, Golden Monastery|The Luxurious And Gorgeous Golden Tearoom. Among The Trees One Can See Its Sparkling Golden Form, Said To Take Your Breath Away. In This Mountain Region Far Removed From Civilization, You Can Spend Some Time With A Cup Of Tea, Cut Off From Everyday Life. * A Gift From GZ Gift|Scene/Entitlement|Granzella Inc.|HDK_1.82.0.17.PUB|LUA-REWARD|Res:0
E238192E-7D914A60-9BBC1F8A-58DE38F7|kName|kDesc|The Dream Yacht: Arctic Voyage Clubhouse|Treat Yourself To The Sights Of Breathtaking Glaciers, Giant Ice Formations And Crystal Blue Waters With The Dream Yacht: Arctic Voyage. Explore Three Decks, Chill Out On The Private Ice Shelf And Collect 8 Unique Rewards. Live The Dream!|Scene/Entitlement|Lockwood|HDK_1.83.0.11.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
E24A306F-515E4D9E-91589004-80616932|kName|kDesc|The Bunker Bar|The Bunker Bar Is The Ultimate Live Music Venue! A Dynamically Lit Stage Dominates One Side Of The Space With An Ultra Cool, Chic Bar And Hangout To The Other Side. Party!|Scene/Entitlement|Lockwood|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|LUA-REWARD|Res:0
E33173CD-17B8405B-8C913D8A-2AB9A529|Name|Desc|Planetland|This Is The Personal Space For The More Adventurous Home Buyer. Space Is Limited, So Act Now!|Scene_Entitlement|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.3.2.27.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
E494E896-9424438D-8E391200-A7271D67|kName|kDesc|Castle Durrant|An Understated Residence For Aspiring Nobility To Call Their Own. A Perfect Place To Relax And Hold Out Against The Siege Of Life.|Scene/Entitlement|MakerXX|HDK_1.82.0.17.PUB|AUTO-REWARD|Res:0
E49D5955-BA314E87-A0E65243-B5D08DFE|Name|Desc|Doctor Who TARDIS - Clubhouse|TARDIS Stands For Time And Relative Dimension In Space. The TARDIS Looks Like A 1950s Wooden Police Phone Box On The Outside, But Is Of Infinite Proportions On The Inside. Amaze Your Friends When They Discover The Wonder Of Time Lord Technology. Doctor Who Logo © 2013 And TM BBC. Licensed By BBC WW Ltd.|Scene/Entitlement|BBC Worldwide Ltd.|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
E4EEA356-28704E7E-970B9191-CB4B1DC5|Name|Desc|Neptune Suite|The Neptune Suite Offers A Virtual Life Of Luxury In This Opulent Underwater Paradise. Enjoy This Action-packed Personal Space Featuring An 8-player Picture Scramble Game, A 4-player Action Game, An Interactive Robotic Pet, And A Sweeping Underwater Glass Wall Vista. Buy Now!|Scene/Entitlement|Mass Media|HDK_1.3.5.120.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
E4F28E56-5AE246B8-82F6A830-5BD80431|kName|kDesc|Paradise Health Club: Apartment|Relax And Re-energise In The Exotic And Picturesque Grounds Of Paradise Health Club! Chill Out By The Pool, Sunbathe On The Terrace Or Detox In The Sauna!|Scene/Entitlement|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
E5946B58-111F4767-A91B0F08-057E339F|kName|kDesc|Mahjong Apartment|Looking For A Nice And Tranquil Place To Stay? The Mahjong Apartment Is Just The Place! This Walled Apartment In An Busy Orient City Is An Oasis Of Rest With Blossom Trees And Koi Carps. If You Are Looking For Something More Lively You Can Try The Mahjong Attack Game That Comes With The Apartment. Mahjong Attack Is A Challenging Variant Of Mahjong Solitaire Which Is All About Speed! You Play The Game Alone (single Player), Together With Your Friends (co-op) Or Against Your Friends (multiplayer)!|Scene/Entitlement|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.66.0.144.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
E5A9148C-92C74351-B7DA822C-8D5E9C52|Name|Desc|Tropical Escape|Warm, Humid, And Exotic. For A Small Fee, You Too Can Own A Piece Of Paradise!|Scene_Entitlement|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.3.5.113.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
E64002D2-6491473C-A798729B-377B81CF|NAME|DESCRIPTION|Basic Clubhouse|The Basic Clubhouse For You To Customise As You Wish!|Scene_Entitlement|Sony Computer Entertainment Europe|HDK_1.52.0.2.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
E67041BA-6A7E4DD6-9A4C0C9D-72DD948B|kName|kDesc|My Secret Villa On A Blue Whale|Take A Trip Through The Ocean On The Back Of A Whale. Visit Tropical Countries, The Mediterranean, And Even The Northern Fjords. Its Up To You Where You Steer The Gentle Giant As You Enjoy This Relaxing Cruise.|Scene/Entitlement|Granzella Inc.|HDK_1.83.0.11.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
E6E84D0B-D51740E0-B95960EB-67DDED9A|kName|kDesc|The House - Apartment|The LIVING Collection - The House! Remember... Fashion Passes, Style Remains, LIVING Is The Key!|Scene/Entitlement|JAM Games Ltd|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
E751A216-DA714C0C-A5AEC618-50D26995|kName|kDesc|Stately Home (Gothic)|The Stately Home (Gothic) Is The Perfect Personal Apartment Space For Those People Who Like The Finer Things In Life With A Slightly Darker Twist. With Its Large And Beautiful Grounds And A Direct Link Through To The Masquerade Ball - The Ballroom (Gothic), This Space Is A Must-have. Also Comes With Five Free Rewards.|Scene/Entitlement|MakerXX|HDK_1.82.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
E753F04A-0CEC47E1-BDC84C10-7BE7C2AF|kName|kDesc|VEEMEE's 50's Diner|Don't Be A Square On Those Summer Nights And Head Down To The VEEMEE 50's Diner To Hand Jive, Grab Some Food And Hang With Friends!|Scene/Entitlement|VEEMEE|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
E79B9C82-3EDE4F26-914219AA-136B9175|Name|Desc|SFRGBT!! Tropical Island|Enjoy A Penalty Shoot-out Against The Worlds Greatest Robot Goalkeeper On Your Very Own Tropical Island At Dusk. In Addition To The SFRGBT!! Minigame, The Island Comes Complete With Beach Shelter, Roaring Fire And A Boat To Take You Home Again. The Minigame Also Includes 4 Unique Reward Items (sand Castle, Bucket And Spade, SFRGBT!! Face Ball And Shark Fin Wearable Accessory) Which Can Only Be Won By Playing Against Robo-goalie In This Exclusive Personal Space.|Scene/Entitlement|VEEMEE|HDK_1.55.0.155.BETA2|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
E7C3EF89-DDBD4D37-BB0CA21C-17A1704C|Name|Desc|Cutteridge Estate|Unlock The Mysteries Of Cutteridge Estate. This Elegant Victorian Estate Is Rumored To Be The Final Resting Place Of Many Dark And Depraved Souls. Do You Dare To Venture Into These Forsaken Halls In Search Of The Secrets Which Lie Within?|Scene/Entitlement|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.55.0.155.BETA2|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
E84D7BA7-84294427-A2BB09EE-65F1483F|Name|Desc|Avalon Keep|The Avalon Keep Is An Impregnable Fortress On Your Very Own Floating Island. The Magical Crystals Of Avalon Allow The Landmass To Stay Afloat And Power All The New Technological Advances That Have Swept The World Of Avalon. Your Keep Sets You Apart As One Of The Nobility That Have Taken Residence In The Skies Around Avalon. Master All The Mini-games And Share The Wealth With The Latest In Gift Machine Technology. Can You Unlock All The Secrets Of Your Keep?|Scene/Entitlement|Heavy Water|HDK_1.65.0.139.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
E984BAEC-72C34918-AEC45F92-9978AF1A|kName|kDesc|Stately Home|The Stately Home Is The Perfect Personal Apartment Space For Those People Who Like The Finer Things In Life. With Its Large And Beautiful Grounds And A Direct Link Through To The Masquerade Ball - The Ballroom, This Space Is A Must-have. Also Comes With Five Free Rewards.|Scene/Entitlement|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.82.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
E9D19674-CADD4C83-A2FC440B-0AAA1528|Name|Desc|S.V.E.R. Barracks|S.V.E.R. Barracks - The S.V.E.R. Barracks Is Your Private Getaway To Remote Central Asia. It Features A Spectacular Sunset View, So You Can Relax On Your Large Balcony, Clean Your Rifle And Watch Strike Fighters Fly Through The Sun Kissed Heavens.|Scene/Entitlement|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.3.5.120.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
EA475EA2-CBE94203-81586432-491FF1D6|Name|Desc|Lock-a-doodle Studio|The Perfect Setting For All Your Doodling! The Lock-a-doodle Studio Includes A Built In Lock-a-doodle Mini-game Plus A Gallery To Display All Your Finest Doodles Created In-game!|Scene/Entitlement|Lockwood Publishing|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
EB5E89C1-83404CCF-80C306ED-C485C998|Name|Desc|Tron Apartment|Experience Life On The Grid In This Apartment From Tron:Evolution.|Scene/Entitlement|Disney Interactive Studios|HDK_1.3.6.22.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
EC15349C-76FA42BD-9143E144-CAC95603|kName|kDesc|LocoIsland|This Is A Personal Space Where You Can Have The South Island Of LocoRoco® Characters All To Yourself. This Island Is Full Of Playfulness! You Can Add Facilities By Collecting Nuts From The Island And Communicating With The Inhabitants. There Are Swings, A Slide, A Jukebox, And Even A Game That Can Be Played By Two People! The More You Play, The More Lively And Fun Loco Island Will Become! Enjoy The Personal Space With A Lot Of Volume!|Scene/Entitlement|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.3.5|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
EFC9404D-DABF46FB-A295753B-B17E3594|Name|Desc|Hollyridge Estate – Clubhouse|The Hollyridge Estate Is The Perfect Setting For An Elegant Winter Soiree! This Personal Space Features Classic Victorian Architecture And Design And Also Features Built-in Decorating Options Which Allow You To Create A Festive Atmosphere Without Taking Up Any Furniture Slots! Includes Customizable Wallpaper, A Snowball Fight Minigame And Much More!|Scene/Entitlement|Juggernaut Games|HDK_1.82.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
F05D8E38-052346FF-9400D26A-94693DB6|kName|kDesc|Martial Art Place|Personal Space Of The Exercise Hall Type Which Trains A Martial Art. Seemingly, The Decoyed Game Is Lived And Attached.|Scene_Entitlement|Will Co.,Ltd.|HDK_1.52.0.2.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
F0C260A5-06C54571-B05E8D49-B32A2938|Name|Desc|Cosmic Corner - Fun Sized Apartment|An Affordable Apartment From NDreams. For Some Reason A Piece Of This Planet Has Broken Away And Is Now Floating Between The Earth And The Moon. With Stunning Views Of Both It Could Be A Perfect Getaway To Chill Out Amongst The Stars.|Scene/Entitlement|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
F1211BB3-F84F4A38-8883E48B-534277EC|kName|kDesc|Musicality Apartment|A Unique Live Music Venue - Up To Four Players Can Grab An Instrument And Jam/compete Against Each Other. Comes Complete With The Dance Music Pack – Additional Packs Are Available To Purchase At The Musicality Shop.|Scene/Entitlement|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.3.6.22.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
F1F7F43D-808C44F5-9353DC9B-7D6DA12F|Name|Desc|Hidden Oak Retreat Clubhouse|Welcome To The Hidden Oak Retreat, A Clubhouse Retreat Tucked Away In The Mountains. Get Away From The Hustle Of City Life And Enjoy One Of The Two Relaxing Fireplaces. Look Up And And You'll Notice The Clubhouse Lit By Chandeliers Made Of Antlers! Head Out To The Deck And Enjoy The Lakefront View While You Roast Some Marshmallows On The Campfire. Now This Is The Great Outdoors! The Hidden Oak Retreat Space Is A Clubhouse Where Everyone Is Invited To Join In.|Scene/Entitlement|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
F2653EE0-993C471A-8E242F55-18AEBABC|kName|kDesc|SFRGBT!! Tropical Island|Enjoy A Penalty Shoot-out Against The Worlds Greatest Robot Goalkeeper On Your Very Own Tropical Island At Dusk. In Addition To The SFRGBT!! Minigame, The Island Comes Complete With Beach Shelter, Roaring Fire And A Boat To Take You Home Again. The Minigame Also Includes 4 Unique Reward Items (sand Castle, Bucket And Spade, Mr. Wilson Face Ball And Shark Fin Wearable Accessory) Which Can Only Be Won By Playing Against Robo-goalie In This Exclusive Personal Space.|Scene/Entitlement|VEEMEE|HDK_1.70.0.93.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
F26F890F-F87149F3-8CE76F09-0FB07B28|Name|Desc|The Space Station|The Space Station Needs A Crew, And You've Been Selected To Take Part In An All New Out-of-this-world Experience. Your Space Station Adventure Will Have You Defending Your New Home Against Incoming Asteroids In The Fully Interactive Station Defense Turret Center. On Top Of Defending The Station Your Tasks Will Also Include Lowering And Raising The External Shutters So You Don't Get Blinded By The Sun And You'll Even Have To Evacuate The Garbage You Produce In To The Vaccum Of Space. Also Included With The Space Station Is A Chair, Sofa, Custom Space Helmet And A Zero Gravity UFO Companion Object To Follow You All Around PlayStation®Home. Your Shuttle Is Cleared For Launch, Awaiting Your Clearance.|Scene/Entitlement|Digital Leisure|HDK_1.65.0.139.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
F3BA0474-E9294766-96F6445D-F9485ABF|kName|kDesc|LocoIsland|This Personal Space Is Your Very Own Tropical Island Inhabited By LocoRoco™ Characters. The Tropical Retreat Is Full Of Exciting Activities. Collect Nuts That Fall From The Trees, And Communicate With Islanders To Expand The Facilities. Enjoy The Swing, Slide, Jukebox, And Games For Two Players! And The More Time You Spend On LocoIsland, The More Vibrant And Exciting The Paradise Becomes! Treat Yourself To This Fun-filled Personal Space!|Scene/Entitlement|Sony Computer Entertainmnet|HDK_1.3.5|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
F4D950BB-AFBA4D07-B5CA783C-12FF1631|kName|kDesc|PIRATE GALLEON APARTMENT|Moored By A Tropical Island, This Ship Comes Complete With Playable Cannon Mini-game. A Very Desirable Residence That Has Suddenly Become Available, Due To The Imprisonment Of The Previous Owner.|Scene/Entitlement|NDreams|HDK_1.3.0.292.CORE|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
F5BDB8BF-A19B457F-97D9B135-3671829F|kName|kDesc|The Drey VIP Room (For Female)|You Have Been Cordially Invited To Be A Member Of The Drey VIP Room. Take An Exclusive Look Into The Inspired Fashions Of Drey's Celebrated Designers. The Drey VIP Room Features A Stunning Collection Of Old And New - Everything To Satisfy The Hunger Of The Fashion Elite Worldwide. This Includes 22 Existing Gift Machine Clothing Items And 12 Exclusive New Clothing Items.|Scene/Entitlement|Lockwood|HDK_1.80.0.53.PUB|LUA-REWARD|Res:0
F676E510-C04644DD-B7CCF224-F4AB3248|Name|Desc|The Pearl Diver Clubhouse|Spend Some Time Beneath The Waves In Your Own Submarine, The Pearl Diver. Designed For Combing Through The Sea Floor, This Underwater Vessel Is Enclosed By Glass To Allow You To Fully Enjoy The Aquatic Sea Life. The Pearl Diver Space Is A Clubhouse Where Everyone Is Invited To Join.|Scene/Entitlement|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
F6854E66-3D944778-8FBA40AC-5EEA954C|kName|kDesc|Studio Stage Set From LOOT™|The Modular Stage Set Takes Professional Machinima To The Next Level. It Provides The User With Unprecedented Levels Of Control Over The Floor, Walls, Backdrops, Lights And Camera Systems.  Also Included Are The Portable Camera And Portable Light Active Items, Which Let You Take The LOOT™ Machinima Tools To Any Private Space You Own, Transforming It Into A Perfect Location For Shooting Your Movies And TV Shows. It Is The Ultimate Tool For Having Fun With Your Friends While Bringing New Stories To Life.|Scene/Entitlement|LOOT™|HDK_1.66.0.144.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
F879374F-CC5A4676-8B86219F-58AFF83E|kName|kDesc|Castle Greywold: Clubhouse|In This New Clubhouse, You Can Take Up Arms In The Training Yard, Entertain Guests In The Audience Chamber, Or Survey Your Surroundings From The Castle Ramparts.|Scene/Entitlement|NDreams Ltd.|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
F8803888-E0EF4EA9-B76F553B-C2E670A0|kName|kDesc|Japanese School Days|Make The First Floor Of A School Building Yours, Including Two Classrooms, A Shop, And A Hallway. The Layout Of Desks, Chairs, And Other Items Is Up To You. Make Your Own Unique Classroom And Enjoy School Life Along With Your Friends! Be Careful Not To Stay At School Until Late At Night. You Never Know What Might Happen...|Scene/Entitlement|Granzella Inc.|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
F97C0E36-3A0249A2-BAC1F6E9-ECF86E3A|Name|Desc|Ghost Pirate Ship|LeChuck's Pirate Ship. Sail The Seven Seas And Even More With The New Underground Lava Transport Hull. Strike Fear In The Hearts Of Sailors And Wannabe Pirates. The Sails May Look Ripped But They Are Still Fully Functional. Avast! And Good Luck!|Scene/Entitlement|LucasArts|HDK_1.3.5.120.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
FB704EA9-BB424031-B23F3F73-5E018A12|kName|kDesc|Polar Rush Tundra Lodge|Jump On Your Snowmobile And Explore The Tundra In This Exciting New Personal Space From Lockwood! From Your Modern Apartment, You'll Be Able To Look Out Onto The Beautiful Arctic Surroundings Before Riding Out To See What You Can Find. Includes Snowmobile Exploration Minigame Which Allows You To Cruise Around The Landscape, Perform Stunts And Find 9 Exclusive PlayStation®Home Rewards.|Scene/Entitlement|Lockwood|HDK_1.83.0.11.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
FBD37FB2-E65C427C-99A31D30-2AA52EA5|Name|Desc|Yacht: Santorini|Docked At Greek's Famous Santorini Harbor, Your Yacht Is Equipped With All The Modern Virtual Conveniences You Would Expect. Step Out On Deck To Take In The Spectacular View Or Stay Inside And Relax With Some Friends.|Scene_Entitlement|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.3.2.27.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
FCF8FF7C-745644AB-B1E47590-B2DD0F10|Name|Desc|The Lost Dam Hideout|Miles From Civilization And Hidden Deep In A Gorge, This Long-lost Dam Is The Perfect Hideout For Every Aspiring Evil Overlord. The Dark Interior And Bare Rock Set The Mood And The Piranha Pool Adds A Suitable Finishing Touch.|Scene/Entitlement|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.3.6.22.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
FD2F25C1-22E94747-8651BA97-9D71106F|kName|kDesc|Park Personal Space|Whether You Prefer To Chill Out By The Fountain, Or Dance With Your Friends In The Music Pavilion, There Is Always A Good Reason To Come And Visit This Peaceful Art-déco Public Park! Contains A Go-kart Racing Game, A Rythm-action Game, And The Space Crash Arcade Cabinet. Playing The Games Will Get You Rewards!|Scene/Entitlement|Atom Republic|HDK_1.86.0.17.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
FE414678-560D430A-9919341A-B85F6BAE|Name|Desc|Prehistoric Valley|Prehistoric Valley Is Your Regular Lush Mountaintop Peaceful Idyll… It Just Happens To Be Around 100 Million Years Ago And Inhabited By Cave People, Dinosaurs, And Giant Mammals!|Scene/Entitlement|Lockwood Publishing|HDK_1.82.0.17.PUB|LUA-REWARD|Res:0
FE63458A-9BD14A06-AB5F7380-3EAF7C26|kName|kDesc|Tearoom, Aqua Monastery|The Luxurious And Gorgeous Aqua Tearoom.Among The Trees One Can See A Sparkling Aqua Figure, Said To Take Your Breath Away. In This Mountain Region Far Removed From Civilization, You Can Spend Some Time With A Cup Of Tea, Cut Off From Everyday Life. * A Present From GZ Gift|Scene/Entitlement|Granzella Inc.|HDK_1.82.0.17.PUB|LUA-REWARD|Res:0
