0034A777-F38E4B47-96796A89-BCA61C97|kName|kDesc|Deton8 DX Fuel Additive X26|An Explosive Fuel Additive For Your Sodium2 Racer That Focuses On Providing Boosted Acceleration When Added As Well As Increasing Top Speed. This Is A 26 Use Item That Will Be Used Automatically In A Race If Equipped.|Sodium|Sodium - Lockwood|HDK_1.55.0.155.BETA2|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
0755CD76-FDED4547-84C25E39-7DFA6053|kName|kDesc|Turbulence DX Rocket Booster Pair X52|These Are High Power Boosters With A Slightly Delayed Onset. Get The Timing Right And You Can Kiss Your Old Personal Best Goodbye.|Sodium|Sodium - Lockwood|HDK_1.50.0.238.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
0F3F1726-5801447E-A861725E-93F3BF30|kName|kDesc|Sonic Camo - Sodium2 Racer Paint Scheme|This Futuristic Evolution Of The Classic Camo Paint Scheme Will Leave Other Racers Wondering What Just Past Them By.|Sodium|Sodium - Lockwood|HDK_1.50.0.238.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
1347390A-0F3048CC-B9340114-77500F84|kName|kDesc|Titan DX Engine|Control The Lower Turning Speed Into Corners And Your Sodium2 Racer Will Hit Those Higher Velocities.|Sodium|Sodium - Lockwood|HDK_1.50.0.238.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
16EFB4A5-B7804388-A802A605-D4089D32|kName|kDesc|Digital Code Bomb|This Disposable Device Installs A Crude, Yet Effective, Brute-force Software Attack Used For Bypassing A Safes Logic Code And Forcing It Open. Use Of This Device May Cause A Spike In A Facilitys Alarm State. This Is A Conspiracy Game Item And Is Placed In Your Game Characters Inventory When Purchased. It Equips In A Gadget Slot On Raids. Quantity: 3.|Sodium|Jet Set Games, Inc.|HDK_1.40.0.265.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
1BB203AF-C28F4DE3-848DAE8C-78824E2A|kName|kDesc|Terrapin DX Rocket Booster Pair X130|A More Steady Boost Effect But With A Much Longer Duration That Will Give You A Big Advantage If You Can Maintain Your Speed.|Sodium|Sodium - Lockwood|HDK_1.50.0.238.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
20823B91-BBBA44F8-9607B9E8-963659D4|kName|kDesc|Molotov DX Fuel Additive X140|A Balanced Fuel Additive For Your Sodium2 Racer That Marginally Increases Both Your Top Speed And Your Acceleration. This Is A 140 Use Item That Will Be Used Automatically In A Race If Equipped.|Sodium|Sodium - Lockwood|HDK_1.52.0.2.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
2C687690-AF664B0D-9283B076-836861DC|kName|kDesc|Large Pulse Alarm Suppressor|For Use In Extreme Emergencies, This Disposable Item Significantly Reduces The Alarm State Of Any Alerted Facility. This Is A Conspiracy Game Item And Is Placed In Your Game Characters Inventory When Purchased. It Equips In A Gadget Slot On Raids. Quantity: 3.|Sodium|Jet Set Games, Inc.|HDK_1.40.0.265.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
363A35DC-DE9644BC-A9E16D48-453C2E92|kName|kDesc|Dynamite DX Fuel Additive X65|A Highly Unstable And Powerful Fuel Additive For Your Sodium2 Racer That Supplements Your Fuel To Increase Your Top Speed. This Is A 65 Use Item That Will Be Used Automatically In A Race If Equipped.|Sodium|Sodium - Lockwood|HDK_1.55.0.155.BETA2|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
36476F38-A0FB44C8-BEA37778-F69FC9DF|kName|kDesc|Turbulence DX Rocket Booster Pair X280|These Are High Power Boosters With A Slightly Delayed Onset. Get The Timing Right And You Can Kiss Your Old Personal Best Goodbye.|Sodium|Sodium - Lockwood|HDK_1.50.0.238.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
3B49537B-D546484E-8360F7C8-D57F008A|kName|kDesc|Hummingbird DX Hover Engine|Adding The More Powerful Motor In This Hover Engine To Your Sodium2 Racer Will Increase Stability And Reduce Slow-down From Crashes At The Cost Of Turning Response.|Sodium|Sodium - Lockwood|HDK_1.50.0.238.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
3EA70031-5EE0499B-A647470C-1BE7BE0D|kName|kDesc|Vortex DX Hover Engine|This Hover Engine Benefits From Increased Blade Size And Less Weight To Produce A More Stable Craft That Will Cope Better With The Occasional Crash. A Dip In The Craft's Turning Capabilities Will Be Pronounced.|Sodium|Sodium - Lockwood|HDK_1.50.0.238.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
4090B4AB-36A14722-961738BE-E123FBCF|kName|kDesc|Terrapin DX Rocket Booster Pair X280|A More Steady Boost Effect But With A Much Longer Duration That Will Give You A Big Advantage If You Can Maintain Your Speed.|Sodium|Sodium - Lockwood|HDK_1.50.0.238.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
417F1584-16024650-9283E02D-EA36D953|kName|kDesc|Hornet DX Hover Engine|Improved Stability Will Allow Your Sodium2 Racer To Stay On Course At High Speed And Handle Crashes Better. A Decent Set Of Air Brakes To Counteract The Reduced Turning Circle Is Highly Recommended.|Sodium|Sodium - Lockwood|HDK_1.50.0.238.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
41D4359D-E5914C60-928B7344-C2A5CE28|kName|kDesc|Interceptor DX Aerofoils|A More Streamlined Design For Your Sodium2 Racer To Produce Exceptional Straight Line Speed And Turning Power. Turn Too Tightly Though And You'll Lose Momentum.|Sodium|Sodium - Lockwood|HDK_1.50.0.238.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
42C3ADE2-87424DFB-A684075D-A0BA8D6C|kName|kDesc|Vector DX Flight Computer|The Latest In Flight Computer Technology Will Constantly Update The Trajectory Of Your Sodium2 Racer To Greatly Increase Stability And Turn Response, But An Extended Time To Break The Mach 1 Barrier May Let Your Opponents In.|Sodium|Sodium - Lockwood|HDK_1.50.0.238.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
4448F1A0-C268416D-82263EC7-960D1809|kName|kDesc|Inertia DX Air Brakes|Sacrifice A Small Fraction Of Your Sodium2 Racer's Top Speed And You'll Turn More Sharply Into Corners.|Sodium|Sodium - Lockwood|HDK_1.50.0.238.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
48C878C9-72094B97-860F4397-3E20BE20|kName|kDesc|Phoenix - Sodium2 Racer Paint Scheme|Turn Up The Heat On Your Competition With This Firey Paint Scheme For You Velocity Racer.|Sodium|Sodium - Lockwood|HDK_1.50.0.238.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
49B9F674-47A34C8C-8A4DB946-3B048B44|kName|kDesc|Fruit Salad - Sodium2 Racer Paint Scheme|A Paint Scheme That Looks Good Enough To Eat. Don't Though - You'll Break Your Teeth On The Titanium Alloy Bodywork.|Sodium|Sodium - Lockwood|HDK_1.50.0.238.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
4D21F3D1-0743493B-B3B3DB88-CFC630E1|kName|kDesc|Galvonium DX Chassis|Heavier Materials Increase The Stability Of Your Sodium2 Racer As Well As Making It More Resistant To Loss Of Speed During Impacts.|Sodium|Sodium - Lockwood|HDK_1.55.0.155.BETA2|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
4F8131B8-E5914AEA-A57D13D4-D8399B4E|kName|kDesc|Live Wire DX Afterburners|Hold Your Nerve Through The Increased Instability And You Will Control A Higher Level Of Acceleration.|Sodium|Sodium - Lockwood|HDK_1.50.0.238.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
5788783F-E5994747-872ABFCC-706616AF|kName|kDesc|Dynamite DX Fuel Additive X140|A Highly Unstable And Powerful Fuel Additive For Your Sodium2 Racer That Supplements Your Fuel To Increase Your Top Speed. This Is A 140 Use Item That Will Be Used Automatically In A Race If Equipped.|Sodium|Sodium - Lockwood|HDK_1.55.0.155.BETA2|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
584FA265-5D0D49D5-997B4C99-B5CD8F15|kName|kDesc|Molotov DX Fuel Additive X650|A Balanced Fuel Additive For Your Sodium2 Racer That Marginally Increases Both Your Top Speed And Your Acceleration. This Is A 650 Use Item That Will Be Used Automatically In A Race If Equipped.|Sodium|Sodium - Lockwood|HDK_1.52.0.2.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
5A001426-82E84B40-AF0C9CE4-D34F48E0|kName|kDesc|Deton8 DX Fuel Additive X650|An Explosive Fuel Additive For Your Sodium2 Racer That Focuses On Providing Boosted Acceleration When Added As Well As Increasing Top Speed. This Is A 650 Use Item That Will Be Used Automatically In A Race If Equipped.|Sodium|Sodium - Lockwood|HDK_1.55.0.155.BETA2|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
5A5A83FE-31744B44-8C3223A1-65D850AA|kName|kDesc|Salamander - Sodium2 Racer Paint Scheme|This Radical Salamander Paint Scheme Features Go-faster Everything!|Sodium|Sodium - Lockwood|HDK_1.50.0.238.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
6A7D838A-3F464005-A1539E67-1D74727E|kName|kDesc|Equilateral Hacking Script Pack|A Common And Low-powered Hacking Script. Hacking Scripts Provide Different Functions Specific To Each Hacking Mini-game. Code Hacking - Randomly Reveals One Of The Code Symbols. Memory Hacking - Reveals Two Pairs Of Hidden Symbols. Data Pulse Hacking - Empties The Bucket Of All Symbols. Your Amount Of RAM Determines The Maximum Number Of Each Hacking Script You Can Have In A Raid Mission. This Is A Conspiracy Game Item And Is Placed In Your Game Characters Inventory When Purchased. Quantity: 5.|Sodium|Jet Set Games, Inc.|HDK_1.40.0.265.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
6A8FEA41-7F42419E-B8E69AA1-24FB3C64|kName|kDesc|Aerobatic DX Aerofoils|A Minor Improvement To The Straight Line Speed Of The Sodium2 Racer Also Allows You To Cut Smoothly Through The Most Awkward Of Turns.|Sodium|Sodium - Lockwood|HDK_1.50.0.238.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
6C472C37-1E9D46DB-AE408A07-E4A090B1|kName|kDesc|Terrapin DX Rocket Booster Pair X1300|A More Steady Boost Effect But With A Much Longer Duration That Will Give You A Big Advantage If You Can Maintain Your Speed.|Sodium|Sodium - Lockwood|HDK_1.50.0.238.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
6C5DA5CB-E574493C-A7A72130-5AA2648C|kName|kDesc|Classic Green - Sodium2 Racer Paint Scheme|Add A Smooth Green Skin To Your Sodium2 Racer For A More Natural Look Whilst Racing To Winning Times.|Sodium|Sodium - Lockwood|HDK_1.50.0.238.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
6C9E498E-58044EDC-8E14AF10-B18B5E11|kName|kDesc|Nanite Regeneration Kit|Using Advanced Nanite Healing Technology, This Disposable Device Instantly Heals A Substantial Amount Of Your Health. This Is A Conspiracy Game Item And Is Placed In Your Game Characters Inventory When Purchased. It Equips In A Gadget Slot On Raids. Quantity: 3.|Sodium|Jet Set Games, Inc.|HDK_1.40.0.265.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
74AF3FC4-8FB24E8C-82A65B14-BD7984E4|kName|kDesc|Aceso Healing Pack|This Disposable Device Utilizes Specialized Mitochondrial Tissue Regrowth Techniques To Instantly Heal A Moderate Amount Of Your Health. This Is A Conspiracy Game Item And Is Placed In Your Game Characters Inventory When Purchased. It Equips In A Gadget Slot On Raids. Quantity: 5.|Sodium|Jet Set Games, Inc.|HDK_1.40.0.265.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
7895A9C4-FE224928-B29FDE8E-2108B2C0|kName|kDesc|Synapse DX Flight Computer|A Minor Stability Increase Is Offset By A Longer Transonic Period As You Push Through The Speed Of Sound.|Sodium|Sodium - Lockwood|HDK_1.50.0.238.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
7E8BCE04-2F0245CF-89508C58-A506E5EE|kName|kDesc|Dynamite DX Fuel Additive X650|A Highly Unstable And Powerful Fuel Additive For Your Sodium2 Racer That Supplements Your Fuel To Increase Your Top Speed. This Is A 650 Use Item That Will Be Used Automatically In A Race If Equipped.|Sodium|Sodium - Lockwood|HDK_1.55.0.155.BETA2|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
7F3E9C98-97BF4931-A0A60E5E-B0343E31|kName|kDesc|Ignition Afterburners|Adds A Small Level Of Acceleration To Your Sodium2 Racer. Your Ride May Become More Unstable As A Result.|Sodium|Sodium - Lockwood|HDK_1.50.0.238.BETA|AUTO-REWARD|Res:0
8AD342FE-B9914B12-ACC8EDE0-A808C52D|kName|kDesc|Velocity Racer Green - Sodium2 Racer Paint Scheme|Show Your True Colours With This Official Project Velocity Paint Scheme. Emblazoned With The Preferred Colour-scheme Of The Velocity Racing Leagues This Paint-job Goes Perfectly With The Official Project Velocity Racer's Outfit.|Sodium|Sodium - Lockwood|HDK_1.50.0.238.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
8B91AAA0-59374515-BB3D8A2D-70EE4097|kName|kDesc|Orbis Hacking Script Pack|A Rare And Powerful Hacking Script. Hacking Scripts Provide Different Functions Specific To Each Hacking Mini-game. Code Hacking - Reveals All Of The Symbols And Solves The Code. Memory Hacking - Reveals All Hidden Symbols. Data Pulse Hacking - Bypasses The System And Solves The Hack. Your Amount Of RAM Determines The Maximum Number Of Each Hacking Script You Can Have In A Raid Mission. This Is A Conspiracy Game Item And Is Placed In Your Game Characters Inventory When Purchased. Quantity: 1.|Sodium|Jet Set Games, Inc.|HDK_1.40.0.265.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
8F4F9DC5-3656469F-BEEF2AB2-C6965E33|kName|kDesc|Animal Magnetism - Sodium2 Racer Paint Scheme|Not Exactly Camouflage, But Whizzing Past Them In A Velocity Racer Is Going To Get Their Attention Anyway.|Sodium|Sodium - Lockwood|HDK_1.50.0.238.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
9303E5B7-1E894BD3-903B2014-91A057E9|kName|kDesc|Deton8 DX Fuel Additive X65|An Explosive Fuel Additive For Your Sodium2 Racer That Focuses On Providing Boosted Acceleration When Added As Well As Increasing Top Speed. This Is A 65 Use Item That Will Be Used Automatically In A Race If Equipped.|Sodium|Sodium - Lockwood|HDK_1.55.0.155.BETA2|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
95520461-A4CD46BC-AC2FC4AC-354D6DA6|kName|kDesc|Apollo DX Engine|A Noticeable Jump In Top Speed To Pull Your Sodium2 Racer Away From Its Competition On The Straights. An Increase In Weight Will Slow You Down Through The Turns.|Sodium|Sodium - Lockwood|HDK_1.50.0.238.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
9A286E3B-495A41A2-867B9BE7-4C3B8445|kName|kDesc|Omniplex DX Chassis|A Heavy, Sturdy Frame For Your Sodium2 Racer Will Notably Increase Stability But The Increased Weight Will Create A Greater Loss Of Momentum Following Race Impacts.|Sodium|Sodium - Lockwood|HDK_1.55.0.155.BETA2|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
9D9D8B68-9B45461D-AE2E81FA-AA74933D|kName|kDesc|Deton8 DX Fuel Additive X140|An Explosive Fuel Additive For Your Sodium2 Racer That Focuses On Providing Boosted Acceleration When Added As Well As Increasing Top Speed. This Is A 140 Use Item That Will Be Used Automatically In A Race If Equipped.|Sodium|Sodium - Lockwood|HDK_1.55.0.155.BETA2|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
9E0C238F-43944AEF-A56DC751-DBF2B944|kName|kDesc|Star Spangled - Sodium2 Racer Paint Scheme|Represent Your Own Country, Or Just One You Feel A Strong Affinity For, With This Patriotic Paint Scheme.|Sodium|Sodium - Lockwood|HDK_1.55.0.155.BETA2|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
9F6304A6-EAE74FDD-807C7336-5D557B26|kName|kDesc|Scout Go-Faster Stripes|This Custom Livery For Your Trusty Scout Ship Has Go-faster Stripes And Looks Great Too!|Sodium|FluffyLogic Development Ltd.|HDK_1.75.0.85.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
9F85BECF-B9C44ECB-B433C5F7-C937147C|kName|kDesc|Nanofiber DX Chassis|A Lighter Frame That Will Increase The Acceleration Of Your Sodium2 Racer At The Cost Of Stability. Crash Impacts Will Also Reduce Momentum By A Greater Amount.|Sodium|Sodium - Lockwood|HDK_1.55.0.155.BETA2|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
AB858A59-35354127-80DDFA3F-E06F9FCC|kName|kDesc|Mission Pack: Escalation|When The Novus Prime Research Division Picks Up Signs Of A Massive Bot Fleet, It Becomes Clear That The Earth's Days Are Numbered. This Bundle Pack Includes Two Missions For The Novus Prime Campaign: Dark Beacons And The Mysterious Hulk. The Elite Versions Of These Missions Are Also Included, Adding A Total Of Four Missions To Your Game List.|Sodium|Hellfire Games, Inc.|HDK_1.52.0.2.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
B8D6D8D0-B62847D0-B16B423B-8DC37D28|kName|kDesc|Terminus DX Air Brakes|Improved Hydraulics For Your Sodium2 Vehicle Will Give You A Greater Braking Force. You'll Spend Less Time On The Brakes Round The Tight Bends And More Time On The POWER!|Sodium|Sodium - Lockwood|HDK_1.50.0.238.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
C15323D2-C7874183-ADBCF062-425D5898|kName|kDesc|Union Jackson - Sodium2 Racer Paint Scheme|Represent Your Own Country, Or Just One You Feel A Strong Affinity For, With This Patriotic Paint Scheme.|Sodium|Sodium - Lockwood|HDK_1.55.0.155.BETA2|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
C2FBF0D7-A7A2485A-B581376F-5EF3C934|kName|kDesc|Molotov DX Fuel Additive X26|A Balanced Fuel Additive For Your Sodium2 Racer That Marginally Increases Both Your Top Speed And Your Acceleration. This Is A 26 Use Item That Will Be Used Automatically In A Race If Equipped.|Sodium|Sodium - Lockwood|HDK_1.52.0.2.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
C54AFDD6-0BF141BA-90726913-FF0EAFD5|kName|kDesc|Molotov DX Fuel Additive X65|A Balanced Fuel Additive For Your Sodium2 Racer That Marginally Increases Both Your Top Speed And Your Acceleration. This Is A 65 Use Item That Will Be Used Automatically In A Race If Equipped.|Sodium|Sodium - Lockwood|HDK_1.52.0.2.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
CA287F30-8DBF4C9D-9E3B9190-E861B7E6|kName|kDesc|Terrapin DX Rocket Booster Pair X52|A More Steady Boost Effect But With A Much Longer Duration That Will Give You A Big Advantage If You Can Maintain Your Speed.|Sodium|Sodium - Lockwood|HDK_1.50.0.238.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
CB640789-4D404426-8BFAE4A2-BF0FF508|kName|kDesc|Ignition DX Afterburners|Adds A Small Level Of Acceleration To Your Sodium2 Racer. Your Ride May Become More Unstable As A Result.|Sodium|Sodium - Lockwood|HDK_1.50.0.238.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
CD94111B-F1D74F7C-8E52D6EE-C5CD45C4|kName|kDesc|Forefront DX Afterburners|With Great Power Comes Great Instability. Leave Your Opponents Standing But Be Careful That The Reduced Stability Doesnt Slam You Into A Wall. That Would Be Embarrassing.|Sodium|Sodium - Lockwood|HDK_1.50.0.238.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
CF454459-EF654244-AD3854B4-79B550C0|kName|kDesc|Steadfast DX Aerofoils|Improves General Handling Of The Sodium2 Racer And Reduces Drag Through The Sound Barrier.|Sodium|Sodium - Lockwood|HDK_1.50.0.238.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
D3E75DDD-66694B33-9CB58D3D-FC3EF299|kName|kDesc|Dynamite DX Fuel Additive X26|A Highly Unstable And Powerful Fuel Additive For Your Sodium2 Racer That Supplements Your Fuel To Increase Your Top Speed. This Is A 26 Use Item That Will Be Used Automatically In A Race If Equipped.|Sodium|Sodium - Lockwood|HDK_1.55.0.155.BETA2|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
DCEACB45-C32E4508-A6199B85-5B39BB7C|kName|kDesc|Turbulence DX Rocket Booster Pair X130|These Are High Power Boosters With A Slightly Delayed Onset. Get The Timing Right And You Can Kiss Your Old Personal Best Goodbye.|Sodium|Sodium - Lockwood|HDK_1.50.0.238.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
E11F6C2F-EBFD4805-825BEAE8-06878114|kName|kDesc|Hinomaru Racer - Sodium2 Racer Paint Scheme|Represent Your Own Country, Or Just One You Feel A Strong Affinity For, With This Patriotic Paint Scheme.|Sodium|Sodium - Lockwood|HDK_1.55.0.155.BETA2|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
EEDEE103-521A46BE-B92394D7-59724031|kName|kDesc|Turbulence DX Rocket Booster Pair X1300|These Are High Power Boosters With A Slightly Delayed Onset. Get The Timing Right And You Can Kiss Your Old Personal Best Goodbye.|Sodium|Sodium - Lockwood|HDK_1.50.0.238.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
F0B75557-D5E24F98-9AF93276-C40B2C26|kName|kDesc|Medium Pulse Alarm Suppressor|This Disposable Item Moderately Reduces The Alarm State Of Any Facility. This Is A Conspiracy Game Item And Is Placed In Your Game Characters Inventory When Purchased. It Equips In A Gadget Slot On Raids. Quantity: 5.|Sodium|Jet Set Games, Inc.|HDK_1.40.0.265.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
F5254614-5C264087-931140A8-3F220C1F|kName|kDesc|Thor DX Engine|A Large And Powerful Engine To Push Your Sodium2 Racer Towards Mach 2. Don't Forget To Take Account Of The Extra Weight Through The Bends Or A Crash At That Speed Will Leave Nothing But A Smear.|Sodium|Sodium - Lockwood|HDK_1.50.0.238.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
F5FDBE8A-342146BE-B6C24FED-9562DC2F|kName|kDesc|Hydrostatic DX Air Brakes|A Brutally Effective Air Brake System To Get Your Sodium2 Racer Through Tighter Corners At Higher Speeds. Remember To Complement Them With Other Increased Acceleration Components Or Your Rivals Will Make Up Lost Ground As You Struggle To Pull Away.|Sodium|Sodium - Lockwood|HDK_1.50.0.238.BETA|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
