0367F55E-55BD41EC-B3AB9DEA-DD082B22|Name|Desc|SOCOM TOC|SOCOM TOC|Worldmap/Objects|SCEJ|HDK_XX|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
037CB0CC-49F84E1F-B5B4FA54-0EC31C9B|kName|kDescription|Gathering Place For Spelunkers|The Entrance To The Spelunkers' Gathering Place Deep Inside The Earth. It's Filled With Spelunkers Exchanging Information About The Depths Of The Earth And Searching For Exploring Partners.|Worldmap/Objects|IREM SOFTWARE ENGINEERING INC.|HDK_XX|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
03EDB0D6-31E64A64-9DBB6134-57B91231|kName|kDescription|The Nether Institute, Evil Academy|The Nether Institute, Evil Academy In DISGAEA 3 Came To Here As A Lounge!|Worldmap/Objects|NIPPON ICHI SOFTWARE INC.|HDK_XX|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
05D56819-5ACD4932-9658BC3F-43D4DC08|kName|kDesc|Carrot NBGI|This Is Namco Bandai Game's Amusement Space. Popular Characters And Game Machines Are On Exhibit Here.|Worldmap/Objects|NAMCO BANDAI Games Inc.|HDK_XX|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
0BDA051D-B1664E4C-AAC5467E-E493536B|kName|kDesc|Resistance™ Station|A Last Bastion Of Hope For Nathan Hale And The Sentinels Where You'll Need To Fend Off The Chimerian Aerial Forces With Your Trusty Quad Barrel, Quick Repeating, AA Ball-turret Gun.|Worldmap/Objects|Resistance™ Station|HDK_1.3.0.289.CORE|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
0C2A6976-E7814A86-8C3346F1-39957CB5|kName|kDesc|FevaArena Entrance|Sony, An Official FIFA Partner, Is A New Communication Zone For The 2010 FIFA World Cup, Football Stadium, A New Communication Zone For The 2010 FIFA World Cup!|Worldmap/Objects|ソニー|HDK_1.3.0|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
0CD0C26E-52044222-BC23D57F-2FCA4141|kName|kDesc|Mao's Room|Mao's Room In Disgaea 3 Appears As A Lounge!|Worldmap/Objects|NIPPON ICHI SOFTWARE INC.|HDK_XX|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
10C9DA4A-B961422E-A7C1944A-D2DDDFF2|kName|kDesc|Hot Shots Golf Lounge|This Is A Lounge Specially Made For Fans Of Everybody's Golf And Hot Shots Golf. In This Cheerful Space, You Can Exchange Information, Chat About The Game And Have A Good Time. Come And Visit Us Today!|Worldmap/Objects|Hot Shots Golf|HDK_XX|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
13A607AC-B3664AB4-9474B380-492AD869|kName|kDesc|Tekken 6 Mishima Building: Entertainment Floor|This Lounge Is For Tekken 6 Fans. You Can Enjoy The World Of Tekken 6 More Deeply With Various Exhibits.|Worldmap/Objects|NAMCO BANDAI Games Inc.|HDK_XX|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
1512F97E-714C4CA5-B453314F-AFEAE3AD|kName|kDesc|Audi Home Terminal|Discover The Audi Home Terminal. Learn More About Audi And Selected Cars Or Travel To The Audi Vertical Run Game With The Chance To Win An Audi Apartment.|Worldmap/Objects|Audi|HDK_1.3.2.16.BETA1|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
151AEE17-1FD74153-A0682078-E7E8A330|kName|kDesc|Magical Evil Academy|The Magical Evil Academy From Magical Warfare Disgaea 3 Appears As A Lounge!|Worldmap/Objects|NIPPON ICHI SOFTWARE INC.|HDK_XX|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
164F32D6-0B914831-BA3AC659-070E0175|Name|Desc|Seaside Of Memories|Welcome To The Seaside Of Tropical Angels: Blue Seas, White Sandy Beaches And Brilliant Sunshine. Here You Will Find A Place That Reunites You With Those Fond Summer Memories. Colorful Swimsuits Are For Sale!|Worldmap/Objects|Irem|HDK_1.3.2.27.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
1B42C85E-E03A4ED9-BCB87BC2-7B3F4E99|Name|Desc|Red Bull Illume™|Red Bull Illume. Picture This: The Best Action And Adventure Sports Photography, As Never Seen Before. Celebrated, Honored, And Exhibited In A Breathtaking Outdoor Venue.|Worldmap/Objects|Red Bull|HDK_1.3.0.125.BETA1|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
1B9CFD14-F8534594-860CA288-8E70FA71|kName|kDesc|MALL|Looking For Something New? Check Out The Latest Items Available For Purchase In The Mall.|Worldmap/Objects|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_XX|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
1D904759-30A94369-98950074-E6D4469E|kName|kDesc|Gintama Jinjo Shotengai|This Is A Shopping Street Where People Live Full Of Humanity. The Sound Of Music From The Radio On The Street Corner Is Comforting. However, Once You Step Into The Parlor Pachipara, You Will Find That The Game Players Are Fighting Hotly Day And Night....|Worldmap/Objects|IREM SOFTWARE ENGINEERING INC.|HDK_1.3.5|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
1E87E388-C9CB4CA0-8F27DEC1-F7D02280|kName|kDesc|MuiMui Ship|This Great Passenger Ship Built By The MuiMui Is Presently Moored At LocoIsland! Use The Binoculars To Check LocoIsland, And Play LocoReverse With Friends On The Deck While Enjoying The Wonderful View. A Surprise Awaits Those Who Communicate With LocoRoco™ Characters!|Worldmap/Objects|LocoRoco™|HDK_1.3.5|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
20093ACE-C1444471-8BEA2323-16EFB272|kName|kDesc|Namco Arcade Center|Come In, Relax, Chat With Fellow Namco Fans And Play Some Classic Arcade Games. Explore The Arcade Center And Find Namco Themed Items To Personalize Your Avatar.|Worldmap/Objects|NAMCO BANDAI Games Inc.|HDK_XX|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
20F7D7AC-D9334CD0-BE8A14A3-84924958|kName|kDesc|Uncharted™: Sully's Bar|A Social Gathering Spot From The Early 20th Century That Has Somehow Weathered Decades Of Storms And Conflict. Sully's Is A Rustic Lounge And Watering Hole Set Deep In The Tropics.|Worldmap/Objects|Naughty Dog|HDK_XX|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
219C5724-70564BE7-8D932520-712ED974|kName|kDesc|S.I.N.'s Secret Base From Street Fighter IV|Watch Your Step! It's S.I.N.'s Secret Laboratory! Don Your Fighting Gear From Street Fighter IV And Unlock Your Hidden Power!!!|Worldmap/Objects|Capcom Co.,ltd|HDK_XX|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
23491991-F6084E24-B5ABE089-3C45C66D|Name|Desc|Red Bull Air Race|The Red Bull Air Race World Series Is A Motor Sport Requiring Speed, Precision And Skill. Experience The Thrill At Red Bull Home.|Worldmap/Objects|Red Bull|HDK_1.3.0.125.BETA1|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
25F71C3A-70A9453D-824B0FC7-F76C5372|kName|kDesc|Presentation Podium|Equipped With A Jumbo Screen And An Attractive Lounge Area. The Beating Heart Of The PlayStation® Events Space.|Worldmap/Objects|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.3.0.317.CORE|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
2B6CD4E7-D5284AA0-88773CCE-B4D281D8|kName|kDesc|S.I.N.'s Secret Base From Street Fighter IV|Watch Your Step! It's S.I.N.'s Secret Laboratory! Don Your Fighting Gear From Street Fighter IV And Unlock Your Hidden Power!!!|Worldmap/Objects|Capcom Co.,ltd|HDK_XX|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
2CFEE1BB-D4144F72-B07C09B5-8D5DD698|kName|kDesc|The Godfather™ II|Welcome To The Godfather™ II, Casino Havana Poker Room.  Enjoy A Game Of No Limit Texas Hold'em Poker And Be Sure To Check Out Our Promotional Video And Concept Art.|Worldmap/Objects|The Godfather II|HDK_XX|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
2D1DEED6-11424045-BEDC7C17-F1F0CE84|kName|kDesc|Resident Evil 5 Shooting Studio|Sightseeing Spot Where The Kijuju Checkpoint In Resident Evil 5 Was Filmed. Enjoy Going Behind The Scenes Of Resident Evil 5 And Having A Look At The Tools And Devices Used On Location!|Worldmap/Objects|Capcom Co.,ltd|HDK_XX|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
2F878A12-2EB241C2-B8149642-1E4A0230|kName|kDesc|EA SPORTS Golf Complex|Information About The EA Sports Titles Now Available/to Be Released. You Can Play Golf Mini-games.|Worldmap/Objects|Electronic Arts|HDK_XX|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
360F4406-5FD74C96-9ABD06D9-3682E951|Name|Desc|Sodium Hub|Sodium Has Arrived In Your Reality! Welcome To The Entertainment Hub Of The Future – An Ever-evolving World Built Around Creativity And Excitement. Showcase Mini Games, Popular Social Activities, And Addictive Meta-gaming With Community Objectives – Theres Something For Everyone.|Worldmap/Objects|Sodium|HDK_1.3.0.125.BETA1|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
39B16F84-92A24140-93EAF91D-475E56EF|Name|Desc|Red Bull Beach|Red Bull Flugtag Challenges Teams Of Everyday People To Build Homemade, Human-powered Flying Machines And Pilot Them Off A 30-foot High Deck In Hopes Of Achieving Flight!|Worldmap/Objects|Red Bull|HDK_1.3.0.125.BETA1|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
48867A3E-80234854-9759EC44-6A55458D|kName|kDesc|A Place Where Cavers Gather|A Gateway To The Underground Where Spelunkers (cavers) Gather. It Is Crowded With Spelunkers Who Exchange Information About The Underground And Recruit Fellow Explorers.|Worldmap/Objects|IREM SOFTWARE ENGINEERING INC.|HDK_XX|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
547CD656-DCB8405F-8440CAB0-F3446A40|kName|kDesc|EA SPORTS Racing Complex - Poker I|Get Information On Upcoming And Existing EA SPORTS Titles, And Play On The Green Beginner Texas Hold'em Game.|Worldmap/Objects|EA Sports|HDK_XX|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
5E5495B2-0B6F4107-B7320394-B1645FFF|Name|Desc|Red Bull Illume|Red Bull Illume. Picture This: The Best Action And Adventure Sports Photography, As Never Seen Before. Celebrated, Honored, And Exhibited In A Breathtaking Outdoor Venue.|Worldmap/Objects|Red Bull|HDK_1.3.0.125.BETA1|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
65463754-2EFA479E-BF87A3E9-3BEEF674|Name|Desc|TEKKEN 6 Mishima Zaibatsu - Recreation Floor|A Lounge Created Especially For TEKKEN 6 Fans. Enjoy The World Of Tekken Like Never Before!|Worldmap/Objects|NAMCO BANDAI Games Inc.|HDK_1.3.0.125.BETA1|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
6DFA99AD-787E4694-89F75EFD-C91BC3C7|kName|kDesc|Muimui Cruise Ship|Muimui Built This Luxury Cruise Ship. It Is Now Anchored In The Sea Near Loco Island! You Can See Loco Island Through Binoculars And Enjoy A Game Of Reversi With Your Friends On The Deck With A Great View! You Can See LocoRoco® Through The Binoculars And Enjoy A Game Of Reversi With Your Friends On The Deck!|Worldmap/Objects|SCEJ|HDK_1.3.2.27.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
77F4BA90-17734078-98EFCFED-0A3CDAEB|kName|kDesc|EA SPORTS Club Fight Night|Information About EA Sports Titles Now Available/to Be Released. You Can Play With Club DJ Mini-games.|Worldmap/Objects|Electronic Arts|HDK_XX|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
78A63C1E-011C4763-8983F3F1-0BEF50DC|kName|kDesc|Street IV S.I.N.'s Secret Base Secret Laboratory Suddenly Appeared! Dress Up In STREET FIGHTER IV Costumes And Unleash Your Hidden Power!|Worldmap/Objects|Worldmap/Objects|Capcom Co.,ltd|HDK_XX|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
7A44D233-581942A6-899E93BA-3BA6C9BC|kName|kDesc|MuiMui Ship|This Great Passenger Ship Built By The MuiMui Is Presently Moored At Loco Island! Use The Binoculars To Check Loco Island, And Play LocoReverse With Friends On The Deck While Enjoying The Wonderful View. A Surprise Awaits Those Who Communicate With LocoRoco™ Characters!|Worldmap/Objects|LocoRoco™|HDK_1.3.2.27.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
7A7B9816-C3F44CB9-80C7B25C-1BAB45B5|kName|kDesc|S.I.N.'s Secret Base From Street Fighter IV|Watch Your Step! It's S.I.N.'s Secret Laboratory! Don Your Fighting Gear From Street Fighter IV And Unlock Your Hidden Power!!!|Worldmap/Objects|Capcom Co.,ltd|HDK_XX|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
8192D9B0-677349F6-85959FB6-7D14C96C|kName|KDesc|Buzz!™: HQ|Step Off The Red Carpet Into Buzz!™: HQ's Plush Waiting Area Before Heading Into The Studio For A Game.|Worldmap/Objects|Buzz!™|HDK_XX|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
85A69974-C0E0429D-8C86CDD2-30F81A3F|kName|kDesc|EA SPORTS Golf Complex - Poker II|Get Information On Upcoming And Existing EA SPORTS Titles, And Play On The Red Tournament Texas Hold'em Game.|Worldmap/Objects|EA Sports|HDK_XX|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
8A5EEAC1-58614ABE-A16A5C4D-08CF1AC4|kName|kDesc|Backstage With Guitar Hero®|Rock Out With Your Friends Backstage And Challenge The Rock God To An Ear-shattering Guitar Duel For The Ages!|Worldmap/Objects|Guitar Hero|HDK_XX|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
8C94F5B0-A71445B8-9BC6F7E2-D133837F|Name|Desc|Red Bull Air Race|The Red Bull Air Race World Series Is A Motor Sport Requiring Speed, Precision And Skill. Experience The Thrill At Red Bull Home.|Worldmap/Objects|Red Bull|HDK_1.3.0.125.BETA1|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
8D1834E7-ADA54142-8BFEF0D3-B839AAE1|kName|kDesc|EA SPORTS Poker I|Information About EA Sports Titles Now Available/to Be Released. You Can Play Texas Hold'em (poker) For Beginners At The Green Table.|Worldmap/Objects|Electronic Arts|HDK_XX|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
8E27E692-05B3474F-A2C7D6D9-84D2BEAD|kName|kDesc|EA SPORTS Poker II|Information About EA Sports Titles Now Available/to Be Released. You Can Play At Intermediate Texas Hold'em (poker) At The Red Table.|Worldmap/Objects|Electronic Arts|HDK_XX|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
8E6A1A72-FE98496C-AA07941F-DE418AFC|kName|kDesc|LIAR GAME Lounge|The Lounge Is A Recreation Of The Garden Of Eden, The Setting For The Movie Liar Game The Final Stage.|Worldmap/Objects|LIAR GAME|HDK_1.3.5|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
90F952C5-FB2F4D16-A5D662C6-421F014E|kName|kDescription|Hong Kong Lounge|Unlike Other Pan-Asia Spaces Such As The Home Square, This Lounge Is Exclusive To Users Of The Same Region Only. Here You Can Find Users Coming From The Same Region As You, And Learn About Special News For Your Own Region!|Worldmap/Objects|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.3.2.27.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
96842792-F31B4941-94AC4376-212160A5|kName|kDescription|Taiwan Lounge|Unlike Other Pan-Asia Spaces Such As The Home Square, This Lounge Is Exclusive To Users Of The Same Region Only. Here You Can Find Users Coming From The Same Region As You, And Learn About Special News For Your Own Region!|Worldmap/Objects|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.3.2.27.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
980DE849-9EA0414C-860ED29A-94C123FD|kName|kDescription|Irem Square|The Bon Festival Dance Is About To Begin In The Square! The Outdoor Stalls Are Standing By To Welcome Everyone. Please Stop On By. Free Yukatas Are Available!|Worldmap/Objects|IREM SOFTWARE ENGINEERING INC.|HDK_XX|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
9989BEA5-34604CFE-AE406CC7-346C46A3|kName|kDesc|Welcome To That Beach Of Your Memories|Where Tropical Angels Gather. Blue Ocean, White Sandy Beach, And Sunshine. Come Here And You Will Be Reunited With The Memories Of Summer That You Have Deep In Your Heart. Colorful swimsuits Are Now On Sale!|Worldmap/Objects|IREM SOFTWARE ENGINEERING INC.|HDK_XX|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
99D1B4FC-47E440BB-B2FB9045-EE0312B5|kName|kDescription|Korea Lounge|Unlike Other Pan-Asia Spaces Such As The Home Square, This Lounge Is Exclusive To Users Of The Same Region Only. Here You Can Find Users Coming From The Same Region As You, And Learn About Special News For Your Own Region!|Worldmap/Objects|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.3.2.27.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
99FFD0E2-87664E00-9AB73940-1B2B40B6|kName|kDesc|EA SPORTS Racing Complex|Information About EA Sports Titles Now Available/to Be Released. You Can Play With Racing Mini-games.|Worldmap/Objects|Electronic Arts|HDK_XX|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
9FD6C1D1-560E46B4-81AD2A82-0575C0D7|kName|kDescription|Singapore Lounge|Unlike Other Pan-Asia Spaces Such As The Home Square, This Lounge Is Exclusive To Users Of The Same Region Only. Here You Can Find Users Coming From The Same Region As You, And Learn About Special News For Your Own Region!|Worldmap/Objects|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_1.3.2.27.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
A257A95F-80A8415E-9B066FFD-8594EF53|kName|kDesc|SHOPPING CENTRE|Looking For Something New? Check Out The Latest Items Available For Purchase In The Shopping Centre.|Worldmap/Objects|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_XX|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
A36829EA-F7424A0C-894B1D21-6251B46A|kName|kDesc|HOME SQUARE|Meet Up With Your Friends And Make Some New Ones In The Lush Surroundings Of Home Square.|Worldmap/Objects|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_XX|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
A4A7C27C-72A54986-BD917239-13B27B76|Name|Desc|Uncharted 2 Nepalese Village|Become The Ultimate Fortune Hunter In This Nepalese Village Based On The Critically-acclaimed UNCHARTED 2: Among Thieves™. Can You Find All The Pieces To Mask Mayhem? Will You Beat The Highscore In Torch Race? Travel To The Nepalese Village And Further Explore The UNCHARTED Universe.|Worldmap/Objects|Naughty Dog|HDK_1.3.0.125.BETA1|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
A6DE1D95-2C714F3D-8231140D-AAA6FE4B|kName|kDesc|Abandoned Docks|On The Outskirts Of The Electrifying World Of InFAMOUS Sit The Abandoned Docks Of Empire City. Here You Can Practise Your Skills In The Reaper Shock Game And Even Hear From The Developers On The Blog Site.|Worldmap/Objects|INFAMOUS|HDK_XX|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
AD4EA0BC-21D14C78-A50B2A7F-6429CDA3|kName|kDescription|Seaside Of Memories|Welcome To The Seaside Of Tropical Angels: Blue Seas, White Sandy Beaches And Brilliant Sunshine. Here You Will Find A Place That Reunties You With Those Fond Summer Memories. Colourful Swimsuits Are For Sale!|Worldmap/Objects|IREM SOFTWARE ENGINEERING INC.|HDK_XX|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
AE29CB4B-CF204289-903BD829-7C05EF96|kName|kDescription|The Gamer's Lounge|Hang Out, Chat, Socialize, And Attend Special Events At This Café Space.|Worldmap/Objects|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_XX|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
AE9DAB0B-DDFD437C-9D09AC9E-2EBB74D1|kName|kDesc|Resident Evil 5 Shooting Studio|Sightseeing Spot Where The Kijuju Checkpoint In Resident Evil 5 Was Filmed. Enjoy Going Behind The Scenes Of Resident Evil 5 And Having A Look At The Tools And Devices Used On Location!|Worldmap/Objects|Capcom Co.,ltd|HDK_XX|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
B0AE5C2D-CA9244E7-8F811FCB-E4E1DD0E|kName|kDescription|Mao's Room|Mao's Room In DISGAEA 3 Came To Here As A Lounge!|Worldmap/Objects|NIPPON ICHI SOFTWARE INC.|HDK_XX|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
B78C117A-E3874CD0-B129C571-A7C22A51|kName|kDesc|Resident Evil 5 Shooting Studio|Sightseeing Spot Where The Kijuju Checkpoint In Resident Evil 5 Was Filmed. Enjoy Going Behind The Scenes Of Resident Evil 5 And Having A Look At The Tools And Devices Used On Location!|Worldmap/Objects|Capcom Co.,ltd|HDK_XX|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
BB0CD11D-769D4A22-BBD9CBB8-B84EDBE8|Name|Desc|Irem Square|The Bon Festival Dance Is About To Begin In The Square! The Outdoor Stalls Are Standing By To Welcome Everyone,so Go On And Stop By! Free Kimonos Are Available!|Worldmap/Objects|Irem|HDK_1.3.0.125.BETA1|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
C335EC0E-CC634AF7-B09AF8BD-A87D0215|kName|kDesc|EA SPORTS Racing Complex|Get Information On Upcoming And Existing EA SPORTS Titles, And Play Casual Sports Games Like Racing.|Worldmap/Objects|EA Sports|HDK_XX|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
C6132FB3-E50E4D4C-834F99C2-9817C9C0|kName|kDesc|HOME THEATRE|Keep Up With The Latest New Releases. Watch Game And Movie Trailers On Ten Exclusive Screens In The Home Theatre.|Worldmap/Objects|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_XX|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
C7996FE3-030C4D73-915D5F10-5D11E8DE|Name|Desc|PixelJunk™ Exhibition|The PixelJunk™ Home Exhibition Is A Virtual Shrine To All Things PixelJunk™! Stocked With Artifacts And Rarities From The PixelJunk™ Series, You Can Get Up-close And Personal With A Larger Than Life Stone Giant, Kick The Tires Of A Super Slick PixelJunk™ Racer, Or Just Sit Back And Zone Out To The Eden Soundtrack.|Worldmap/Objects|Pixel Junk|HDK_XX|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
C911E527-BA7C4316-B155FF60-BDD8A563|kName|kDesc|Hot Shots Golf|Chat With Other Hot Shots Golf Fans And Enjoy The Sunny Atmosphere In This Idyllic Setting.|Worldmap/Objects|Hot Shots Golf®|HDK_XX|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
C91221E7-62F04092-8C804FB0-60825300|Name|Desc|Red Bull Flugtag|Red Bull Flugtag Challenges Teams Of Everyday People To Build Homemade, Human-powered Flying Machines And Pilot Them Off A 30-foot High Deck In Hopes Of Achieving Flight!|Worldmap/Objects|Red Bull|HDK_1.3.0.125.BETA1|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
CA41A8A6-7CFC4D72-87E6399B-29D3A87C|kName|kDescription|Mishima Zaibatsu - Recreation Floor|A Lounge Created Especially For TEKKEN 6 Fans. Enjoy The World Of Tekken Like Never Before!|Worldmap/Objects|NAMCO BANDAI Games Inc.|HDK_XX|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
CB1F59F9-26554B92-B3B9BF83-ED85EDEC|kName|kDesc|Mishima Zaibatsu - Recreation Floor|A Lounge Created Especially For TEKKEN 6 Fans. Enjoy The World Of Tekken Like Never Before!|Worldmap/Objects|Namco Bandai|HDK_1.3.0.289.CORE|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
CB1F9FE5-DAC6484A-A3F68068-8621E7ED|kName|kDesc|SIREN Lounge|Saiga Hospital, The Ultimate Horror Stage In Siren, Coming To PlayStation®Home! Do You Think You Can Survive In Here!?|Worldmap/Objects|Siren: Blood Curse|HDK_XX|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
CC4BA766-A6A34908-A5D8B030-D4333D36|kName|kDesc|Namco Theatre|Check Out The Latest Trailers For New And Upcoming Namco Bandai Releases In The Theatre.|Worldmap/Objects|NAMCO BANDAI Games Inc.|HDK_XX|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
CDEB5FD3-C0EB4055-8A6F668E-D02CD6FB|Name|Desc|EA SPORTS Club Fight Night|Get Information On The New Fight Night Round 4 Game, Play The Club DJ Game.|Worldmap/Objects|EA Sports|HDK_XX|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
CE1F968F-D1604B80-9C1A250E-BBBBE5F3|kName|kDescription|Sparkle In The Void Of Space|A Confrontation Between An Army Of Fighters And A Battlestar, The Shadow Of A Gargantuan Lifeform In The Wreckage Of A Space Station, Flying Lasers And Missiles, Giving Off Sparkling Flashes Of Light. Will You Lead Your Starship To Victory In Destroying The Enemy Fleet? Will Your Dimensional Fighter Bring Defeat Upon The Vile Lifeforms? The Raising Of The Curtain Of War Is At Hand.|Worldmap/Objects|IREM SOFTWARE ENGINEERING INC.|HDK_XX|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
D1EC133D-60E04752-9E6E94E9-D1707E33|kName|kDesc|Everybody's Golf™ Space|A Lounge For 'Everybody's Golf™' Fans. You Can Exchange Information And Tips As Well As Chat With Your Golfing Friends In This Friendly Lounge! Come And Join The Fun!|Worldmap/Objects|Everybody's Golf™|HDK_XX|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
D287DD69-93D84258-A762B17E-270654DC|kName|kDesc|Irem Square|The Bon Dance Is About To Begin In The Square. Many Night Stalls Will Be Waiting For You. Please Stop By. Free Yukata (casual Kimono) Will Be Given Away!|Worldmap/Objects|IREM SOFTWARE ENGINEERING INC.|HDK_XX|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
D2EA3E02-80E043B7-86A9F8BB-F6449579|kName|kDescription|Game Arena|This Is Namco Bandai Game's Amusement Space. Popular Characters And Game Machines Are On Exhibit Here.|Worldmap/Objects|NAMCO BANDAI Games Inc.|HDK_XX|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
D7AF58BB-1E294EB5-B78A8256-F267B4A7|kName|kDesc|MuiMui Ship|This Great Passenger Ship Built By The MuiMui Is Presently Moored At Loco Island! Use The Binoculars To Check Loco Island, And Play LocoReverse With Friends On The Deck While Enjoying The Wonderful View. A Surprise Awaits Those Who Communicate With LocoRoco™ Characters!|Worldmap/Objects|LocoRoco™|HDK_1.3.2.27.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
D816036C-6CEE4726-8E880554-30C1E084|kName|kDesc|Resident Evil 5 Shooting Studio|Sightseeing Spot Where The Kijuju Checkpoint In Resident Evil 5 Was Filmed. Enjoy Going Behind The Scenes Of Resident Evil 5 And Having A Look At The Tools And Devices Used On Location!|Worldmap/Objects|Capcom Co.,ltd|HDK_XX|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
D87E9A79-D0FE48FE-946F17B3-18254AB1|kName|kDesc|EA SPORTS Golf Complex|Get Information On Upcoming And Existing EA SPORTS Titles, Play The Golf Game, Or Visit The EA SPORTS Pro Shop.|Worldmap/Objects|EA Sports|HDK_XX|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
D8DDC18C-4741453B-8CD2AED0-FC84BC54|kName|kDesc|Audi Vertical Run|Take Control Of The Audi E-tron. Race Through A Vertical Cityscape Against Up To 5 Other Players, Launching Into The Atmosphere For A Chance To Win Your Own Audi Apartment.|Worldmap/Objects|Audi|HDK_1.3.2.16.BETA1|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
E0EE752F-488C4D13-A7613683-05C4E9FE|kName|kDesc|Sparkling Flashes In Space|A Confrontation Between A Space Carrier And A Huge Army Of Fighters, The Shadow Of A Giant Life Form Lurking In The Wreckage Of A Space Base, Lasers And Missiles Flying Past, Each Time A Sparkle. Will You Operate A Space Battleship To Destroy The Enemy Fleet? Or Will You Pilot A Dimensional Fighter Jet To Defeat The Evil Life Forms? The Curtain Is About To Rise On The Battle.|Worldmap/Objects|IREM SOFTWARE ENGINEERING INC.|HDK_XX|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
E68F5989-F8C64239-BEA54937-43EBFFC7|kName|kDescription|SIREN Lounge|Saiga Hospital, The Ultimate Horror Stage In Siren, Coming To PlayStation®Home! Do You Think You Can Survive In Here!?|Worldmap/Objects|死魂曲 SIREN: NEW TRANSLATION|HDK_XX|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
EB597CE1-F6614CAF-B382D551-584285C8|kName|kDesc|Shin Mikuni Musou Online Corridor|A Public Space Featuring A Dragon Fountain Inspired By The Architecture Of The Three Kingdoms Period.|Worldmap/Objects|KOEI|HDK_1.3.2.27.PUB|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
EBC672B4-BD9A4566-8E33849F-357D3BDC|kName|kDesc|The SingStar®Rooms|Get Your Groove On To The Hottest Tracks In The SingStar®Rooms. Listen To Great Music And Get Funky On The Interactive Dance Floor.|Worldmap/Objects|SingStar|HDK_XX|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
EC184E22-ED374F77-9BB418A2-5C0BAF37|Name|Desc|Burn Zombie Burn|Welcome To The Burn Zombie Burn Graveyard – Laugh At Our Zombies, Watch Our Trailer.|Worldmap/Objects|Burn Zombie Burn|HDK_1.3.0.125.BETA1|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
EFE5814C-B1EC4D33-A5409578-24FD6BE2|kName|kDesc|Burn Zombie Burn|Welcome To The Burn Zombie Burn Graveyard – Laugh At Our Zombies, Watch Our Trailer.|Worldmap/Objects|Burn Zombie Burn|HDK_1.3.0.289.CORE|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
F32CB79D-3D734BBE-8574DC8C-62B98FB3|kName|kDesc|BOWLING ALLEY|Have Some Fun And Challenge Other People At The Exciting Games On Offer In The Bowling Alley.|Worldmap/Objects|Sony Computer Entertainment|HDK_XX|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
F7DB9765-36954B3F-B622B413-8B69303C|kName|kDesc|SIREN|SIREN's Most Terrifying Stage, Saiga Clinic, Has Come To The PlayStation®Home World! Can You Survive?|Worldmap/Objects|SCEJ|HDK_XX|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
FB72BDFA-E4974014-BBAB53CD-D6991E1F|kName|kDesc|Warhawk|Socialize, Strategize, Game Launch|Worldmap/Objects|Incognito|HDK_XX|NOT-RWRD|Res:0
